patent_number,date,title,spacy_pos,spacy_label,is_prpn_spacy,is_person_spacy,spacy_pos_len
US3400088A,1964-02-10,"Polyvinyl chloride stabilized with mixtures of a pcl3-bis phenol reaction product, epoxy resin and heavy metal salt","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,21
US3400245A,1967-09-15,Sadiron,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3400262A,1966-12-14,Vehicle lamp mounting and wiring fixture,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3400268A,1963-12-23,System for a. c. operation of an ionization chamber,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3400323A,1964-02-21,Static voltage regulator for a d. c. generator,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3400324A,1966-04-04,Half-wave control of full-wave a. c.,"['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']","['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",1,1,11
US3400351A,1966-10-11,Solenoid plunger stop,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3400401A,1966-01-12,Luneberg lens antenna constructed from two geodesic domes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,9
US3400427A,1964-03-02,Hose curing unit,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3400460A,1965-09-16,Tailor's trouser length and trouser cuff marker,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3400486A,1966-04-11,Cap shooting airplane,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3400617A,1966-07-18,Drill bit tip,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3400665A,1964-08-04,Continuous transport installation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3400804A,1967-04-05,Continuous belt conveyor for unloading granular material from hoppers,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3400855A,1965-06-07,Spillproof containers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3400860A,1966-06-29,Shaker type dispenser,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3400879A,1967-02-28,Carton with cushioning platform and blank for producing the same,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3401040A,1964-07-27,Continuous separation of juice from grape solids,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3401070A,1965-05-19,Resin coating,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3401119A,1965-02-16,Quaternary ammonium compounds and process of making,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3401129A,1964-04-03,"Floor tile comprising polyvinyl chloride, chlorinated polyethylene and filler","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3401136A,1964-01-08,Dipentene polymer compositions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3401147A,1963-04-01,"Epoxy resins from bisphenols of 3, 9-divinyl spirobi","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,12
US3401175A,1965-02-23,Phosphinyloxy-and phosphinothioyloxy-nu-arylphthalimides,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3401257A,1965-08-06,Circuit arrangement for isolating voltage multiplier d. c. signal circuits,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3401267A,1964-06-26,Yarn breakage detector,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3401330A,1965-03-16,Synchro transformer network for deriving an ac voltage that linearly varies in phaseas a function of rotor position,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PRON', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",0,1,19
US3401335A,1966-03-18,Meter circuit for power supply,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3401414A,1966-11-09,Mobile power-operated jack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3401437A,1967-05-10,Hose clamp,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3401443A,1967-04-17,Chuck assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3401475A,1966-07-18,Label and labelled container,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3401508A,1965-08-02,Cotton harvester with means for automatically cleaning trash screen,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3401542A,1965-06-24,Yarn dyeing means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3401684A,1965-12-16,Biopsy capsules,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3401844A,1967-06-09,Leakproof aerosol construction,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3401845A,1965-07-23,Dispensing cap for atomizers,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3401851A,1967-02-17,Dispensing closure for receptacles,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3401894A,1966-12-28,Yarn traverse device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3401899A,1965-12-30,Cartridge and cartridge carrier,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3401901A,1967-01-25,Yarn package support,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3401957A,1966-10-07,Split t,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3401960A,1967-05-31,Rod end fastener,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3401974A,1966-08-19,Tongs for handling heavy products,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3402030A,1964-12-29,Stabilized fuel additive concentrates containing alkyl and/or alkyl aryl phosphates,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3402055A,1962-05-25,Glass composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3402056A,1967-10-18,Methyl cellulose as starch substitute,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3402064A,1964-09-21,Glass fiber reinforced elastomers and composition for sizing and impregnating such glass fiber systems,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3402065A,1950-01-23,Phenyloxyalkanol coating of particle,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3402078A,1968-09-17,Solid stabilized zirconia or thoria having a layer of tantalum pentoxide and titanium oxide thereon,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']","['GPE', 'PERSON']",1,1,16
US3402104A,1965-11-29,Continuous fermentation of glutamic acid,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3402119A,1965-05-10,Unitary corona reactor including opposed planar non-vitric dielectric walls,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3402139A,1965-04-21,"Polyvinyl acetals plasticized with mixtures of an epoxy ester, a non-polymeric ester and a saturated polyester","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,20
US3402142A,1964-07-23,Vinyl aromatic polymers stabilized by phosphorus compounds,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3402174A,1965-08-27,Aminoalkyl pyrrol-3-yl ketones and 3-haloalkanoyl pyrroles,"['PROPN', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,11
US3402256A,1964-04-01,Fm video recording with white level clamping,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3402391A,1965-04-19,Continuous control using alternating or direct current via a single conductor of plural functions at a remote station,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,19
US3402441A,1967-11-02,Clasp and apparatus for molding same,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3402567A,1966-05-28,Freezing kettle for soft ice freezer,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3402663A,1966-11-18,Continuous noncellular rubber foam stamp,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3402858A,1968-09-24,Volumetric measuring unit for materials,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3402881A,1965-05-26,Aircleaner and silencer,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3402882A,1966-10-04,Rigid sleeve fan guard,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3402950A,1967-04-25,Rod assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3402959A,1967-01-13,Torpedo retrieving snare,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3402972A,1966-08-11,Continuous pressure control system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3403016A,1965-04-15,Glassware forming apparatus with blow head control,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3403066A,1964-07-15,Label or tape dispenser and applicator,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3403076A,1967-08-15,Molten salt breeder reactor and fuel cell for use therein,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3403105A,1963-12-27,Transaxle fluid,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3403116A,1962-04-24,Vinylidene chloride-ethylenically unsaturated monomer-ethylenically unsaturated acid-gelatin emulsion polymerized coating composition,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3403123A,1965-09-17,Polyvinyl halide latices stabilized with diammonium phosphate and ammonium hydroxide,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3403126A,1966-02-24,Vinyl chloride plastic compositions and certain plasticizers therefor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3403184A,1966-03-23,Carotenoid compounds,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3403337A,1966-04-18,Frequency meter utilizing a transformer having a non-rectangular hysteresis loop saturable core and a compensation circuit therefor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,20
US3403501A,1966-07-15,"Yarn-treatment, method and apparatus","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3403536A,1967-03-03,Yarn feeding means for raschel knitting machines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3403562A,1967-01-31,Volumetric compensator for temperature changes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3403606A,1966-07-08,Carton feeding and forming apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3403682A,1965-12-22,Incontinence devices,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3403705A,1965-07-29,Dobby for looms,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3403751A,1967-05-11,Scaffold,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3403839A,1966-11-08,Carton and blanks for making same,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3403901A,1965-09-02,Screw clamp,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3403964A,1966-06-17,Oxyacetylene blowpipes,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3403966A,1964-03-11,Dyeing metal-modified polyolefins with o'-(alkyl-and arylaminocarbonyl-) and o'-cyanozaopyrazolone dyes,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'X', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3404027A,1965-06-01,Satin finish vitrifiable enamels,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3404039A,1964-11-18,Electrical device including stabilized zirconia solid electrolyte,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ']","['GPE', 'PERSON']",1,1,8
US3404125A,1963-07-10,Epoxy resin compositions containing dienophile curing agent and polycyclodienes,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3404285A,1965-05-03,Bias supply and line termination system for differential logic,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3404342A,1965-06-15,Galvanometer damping arrangement using adjustable volume fluid damping,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3404370A,1966-08-04,Cap and lead construction for electrical components,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3404405A,1965-04-30,Luneberg lens with staggered waveguide feed,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3404443A,1966-12-20,Sag compensator for gear machine work spindle,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3404545A,1966-10-25,Oldham coupling,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3404677A,1965-07-08,Biopsy and tissue removing device,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3404752A,1966-06-23,Scaffold,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3404805A,1965-11-05,Bottle carrying carton and case,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3404810A,1966-12-30,Powder dispenser,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3404828A,1967-08-02,Dispensing carton with siftproof pouring arrangement,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",0,1,7
US3404829A,1967-07-21,Carton locking cover,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3404842A,1967-02-13,Nozzles for jet engines,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3404868A,1966-06-22,Hydraulic jack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3404896A,1966-08-11,Chuck,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3404944A,1963-08-29,Beautician's appliance,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3404960A,1967-12-11,Continuous process for simultaneously producing coke and carbon black,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3404968A,1964-09-30,Glass-to-metal seals and method for making same,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3404973A,1963-03-05,Glass sheet forming apparatus with coated silica core roller and roller,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,12
US3405084A,1965-06-30,"Neutralized terpolymeric resin of vinyl pyrrolidone, alkyl acrylate or methacrylate,and unsaturated monocarboxylic acid","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3405160A,1964-07-09,Xenyl-alkyl isonitriles,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3405181A,1964-03-16,Polythioether dienes and their preparation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3405491A,1967-04-12,Masonry walls and strengthener,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3405516A,1966-08-22,"Yarn, cordage, ropes, and the like","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3405590A,1965-07-16,Tuner for stringed musical instruments,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3405605A,1966-06-14,Hydraulic pump jack means,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3405844A,1966-06-06,Cartridge dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3405847A,1966-09-10,Screw conveyor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3405906A,1966-08-04,Solenoid pilot operated valve,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3406068A,1951-07-30,Photographic methods of making electron-sensitive mosaic screens,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3406071A,1963-09-14,Naphthol sulfonamides as coupling components for light-sensitive diazotype materials,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3406139A,1963-01-29,Vinylimidazoline and vinyltetrahydropyrimidine polymers,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3406495A,1966-01-24,Carton closer and sealer,"['PROPN', 'ADV', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3406541A,1966-05-31,Yarn feed indexing apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3406626A,1966-05-23,Continuous control register,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3406880A,1966-12-29,Dispensing closure cap,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3406884A,1966-03-16,Holster,['ADJ'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3406985A,1967-04-21,Dolley,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3406987A,1965-04-26,Split-sleeve sheet metal pipe coupling,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3407069A,1965-01-27,Continuous stream brewing process employing permeable yeast plug,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3407157A,1965-05-19,"Tablet coating compositions comprising methyl vinyl ethermaleic anhydride copolymer,plasticizer and surface active agent","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3407166A,1967-02-27,Vinyl chloride resins plasticized with dimethyl fatty amides,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3407188A,1965-09-01,Quaternary ammonium salts of lignin,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3407204A,1967-03-14,Quaternary ammonium aliphatic imides,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3407211A,1961-06-20,Acylaminophenyl heterocyclic ketones,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3407236A,1964-08-12,Fluoroalkyl orthoesters,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3407448A,1967-03-03,Hose clamp with hose-attaching means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3407449A,1967-03-03,Hose clamp with hose-attaching means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3407532A,1966-04-14,Cap-firing device,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3407538A,1966-08-29,Sandblaster for floors,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3407550A,1967-01-23,Continuous one-piece bird repellent structure,"['ADJ', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3407585A,1967-06-07,Yarn handling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3407631A,1966-04-01,Yarn finger selection mechanism,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3407658A,1966-09-13,Flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3407711A,1966-04-25,Swab assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3407712A,1967-01-20,Carton forming machine,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3407755A,1967-10-16,Frozen stick-confection machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3407780A,1965-10-01,Split brake system fluid loss audible warning device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3407842A,1965-10-21,Manifold fitting,"['ADJ', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3407922A,1967-05-22,Dispensing cup assembly with a material-receiving cavity,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3407967A,1967-01-24,Dispensing closure cap,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3408014A,1966-03-28,Yarn traversing mechanism for textile machine,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3408100A,1967-04-17,Tail gate latch mechanism,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3408154A,1967-02-17,Spinner for a liquid fuel burner,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3408164A,1966-07-08,Plasma treatment of carbon blacks,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3408172A,1966-03-01,Diamond and cubic boron nitride grains coated with photopolymerized material,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3408213A,1963-10-10,Glass fiber compositions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3408225A,1963-08-03,Glass fibers sized with polycarbonate,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3408302A,1965-05-24,Thoria/terbium fluoride luminophors,"['PROPN', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3408303A,1965-09-13,Thoria/europium fluoride luminophors,"['PROPN', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3408406A,1966-03-23,Carotenoid compounds,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3408504A,1962-01-10,Amplifier for electrical oscillations,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3408664A,1967-02-16,Stretcher construction,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3408716A,1967-03-24,Yarn processing apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3408789A,1966-03-21,Cap applying method and apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3408799A,1966-09-19,Cotton harvesting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3408800A,1965-04-26,Cotton stripping fingers,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3408832A,1965-05-19,Yarn tensioning regulating apparatus for stocking machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3408892A,1967-06-28,Cartridge reloader and sizer,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3408905A,1966-04-11,Carton forming apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3408907A,1967-03-09,Carton erecting apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3408933A,1966-03-24,Continuous take-up clamping arrangement for blanket in printing press,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3408944A,1966-12-02,Impeller construction for a centrifugal pump,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3409070A,1966-08-05,Continuous casting apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3409129A,1963-06-24,Label scanning device and process,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3409133A,1965-05-26,Screens,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3409177A,1966-01-03,Cartridge loaded hopper apparatus,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3409179A,1966-02-05,Dispensing unit with movably mounted supply container,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3409186A,1966-04-25,Cap for an aerosol container,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3409191A,1967-01-19,Coat hanger,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3409194A,1966-05-26,Yarn tensioning apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3409215A,1966-06-20,Continuous centrifuge,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3409238A,1967-03-28,Continuous yarn windup apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3409403A,1964-10-05,Plasma preparation of carbon black,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3409434A,1965-10-28,Resin precoated diazotype papers,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3409454A,1965-03-31,Alumina coated tio2 pigments,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,5
US3409554A,1964-03-16,Gd or sm doped silicon semiconductor composition,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3409580A,1964-05-01,Polyvinyl halide plastisols containing cyclohexyl amines and cellular products therefrom,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3409620A,1967-02-06,Continuous manufacture in vacuum of nitric esters and/or organic nitro compounds,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3409653A,1963-06-10,"Dibutyltin bis(2, 4-dinitro-6-alkylphenolates)","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,10
US3409655A,1964-02-17,Aluminum n-(3-trifluoromethylphenyl) anthranilate,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3409685A,1966-04-08,Xylene isomerization process,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3409795A,1966-12-27,Continuous burning high-intensity arc lamp,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3409837A,1965-02-01,Amplifier network,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3409860A,1966-05-11,Slidable test jack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3409893A,1965-10-29,Zigzag radiator with panel reflector,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3409957A,1966-08-11,Continuous yarn treatment process and apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3410014A,1965-04-26,Trawl boards,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3410020A,1966-04-18,Jig type fish lure,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3410026A,1966-02-23,Glass door assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3410069A,1966-02-03,Yarn end cutting device in automatic bobbin changing apparatus for textile machinery,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3410087A,1966-03-17,Hydraulic jack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3410114A,1966-05-31,Yarn feed disabling apparatus for hosiery knitting machines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3410117A,1967-04-07,Cap-cleaning apparatus,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3410167A,1965-01-22,Shears for trimming thick metal sheets or plates,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3410236A,1967-08-14,Rug fringe forming sewing machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3410267A,1964-09-18,Cartridge syringe holder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3410273A,1968-01-16,Cigarette,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3410275A,1965-03-30,Cigarette filter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3410301A,1966-09-22,Solenoid or timer operated pilot valve for main valve control,"['ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3410317A,1964-09-16,Solenoid winding machine,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3410517A,1966-03-15,Hose water regulator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3410552A,1966-05-23,Label handling device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3410557A,1965-08-23,Billiard cue tip with a plurality of striking surfaces,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3410672A,1963-01-12,Glass working apparatus with liquid seal,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3410675A,1965-04-15,Glass rod and tube forming with controlled dimensional uniformity,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3410692A,1961-11-14,Continuous manufacture of pre-dough,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3410763A,1963-08-08,Continuous polarographic method,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3410777A,1964-05-18,Glass electrode composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3410828A,1965-09-22,Acrolein-n-vinyl pyrrolidone copolymer and cationic derivative paper wet-strength agents,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3410857A,1964-10-12,2-amino ethyl pyrrol-3-yl ketones,"['NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB']","['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",0,1,9
US3410926A,1964-01-09,Epoxy resin compositions comprising aminoplast resin and polycarboxylic compound,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3410965A,1964-06-20,D. c. signalling system,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3411086A,1964-03-09,D.c. voltage comparator system using a beam deflection tube,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3411174A,1965-10-21,Dirt removal and disposal unit,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3411176A,1966-07-18,Patty mold,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3411278A,1966-04-25,Doffer for cotton harvesters,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3411331A,1967-01-10,Axial pin cylinder device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3411378A,1965-09-24,Split connecting rod,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3411381A,1966-09-08,Split torque transmission,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3411430A,1967-03-22,Continuous grain puffer,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3411535A,1966-08-17,Cartridge valves,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3411564A,1967-05-17,Continuous casting of steel,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3411589A,1966-08-31,Coulter mounting,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3411598A,1966-04-29,Stairclimbing wheelchair,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3411616A,1965-07-26,Cigar overwrapping and banding machine,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3411671A,1967-09-13,Dispensing mechanism for a liquid and a powder,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3411696A,1966-10-11,Carton and blanks for making same,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3411712A,1966-06-23,Bimetallic disc valve flow diverter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3411726A,1966-12-12,Yarn string-up roll,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3411874A,1964-11-09,Zsm-2 zeolite and preparation thereof,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3411878A,1965-03-31,Alumina agglomerates and method for producing same,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3412051A,1963-07-16,Pentaerythritol phosphites as flame-retardants in foams and elastomers,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3412076A,1964-10-29,Resin providing compositions of polyhalomethylated aromatic compounds and hydroxyalkyl mercaptans,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,11
US3412078A,1966-02-16,Polypropylene having a high degree of unsaturation,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3412121A,1966-01-03,"Bis(cyanoalkylene-, hydroxytin) oxides","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,6
US3412125A,1963-10-30,"Coordination complexes of normal halide salts of antimony, tin and titanium and hydroxyalkyl polyphosphates","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3412127A,1965-10-22,Alkylaluminum oxidation process,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3412130A,1966-08-27,Quaternary ammonium dyestuffs of o-nitro-phenyl substituted dilower alkylene triamines,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3412131A,1966-08-02,Alkyl carbonates of salicylic acid,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3412133A,1964-08-07,"Alkyl carbonate esters of 2, 6-dinitro-4-branched alkyl-phenols","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,15
US3412194A,1964-11-20,Glass-melting electrodes for glass-melting furnaces,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3412249A,1964-08-04,Backscatter thickness measuring gauge utilizing different energy levels of bremsstrahlung and two ionization chambers,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,15
US3412281A,1964-09-18,D.c. controlled dynamic focus circuit,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3412319A,1965-02-27,Scr ignitron control circuit having means for controlling the scr as a function of the ignitron anode voltage,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,19
US3412329A,1964-10-28,Frequency meter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3412342A,1966-05-16,Amplifier system for compensation of undesired capacitance and resistance effects,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3412538A,1966-06-21,Harvester with counterbalanced reciprocating members,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3412572A,1966-09-22,Freezing tray,"['VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3412583A,1967-01-27,Yarn tension means for warp knitting machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3412638A,1966-06-16,Tuner for stringed instruments,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3412681A,1965-06-11,Cartridge and a firearm for such a cartridge,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3412711A,1966-07-25,Sow's farrow box,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3412724A,1966-01-10,Soundproofed internal combustion engine,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3412733A,1965-07-08,Acetabulum reamer,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3412760A,1966-01-10,Hose assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3412764A,1967-09-27,Binder control mechanism,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3412767A,1966-06-30,Sabre saw chuck,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3412825A,1967-08-11,Silencer or muffler and method of producing same,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3412849A,1964-10-01,Yarn package,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3412866A,1966-06-27,Ski boot jack,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3412867A,1966-09-13,Glass rack trucks,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3412870A,1967-01-24,End-of-car hydraulic buff and draft cushioning,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3412906A,1966-12-05,Plasma infusor,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3412941A,1966-02-10,Hose nozzle,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3412980A,1966-10-25,Floating gear screw jack,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3413009A,1966-01-11,Chuck,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3413051A,1967-03-07,Rollerway cabinet,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3413075A,1966-02-08,Azo dyestuff mixtures and aromatic polyester fibers colored therewith,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3413108A,1967-06-13,Glass forming machine having molds with movable bottom sections,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3413151A,1966-02-07,Rod and block energy storage apparatus,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3413185A,1964-09-30,Yarn package in the form of a rod-shaped batt,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3413187A,1966-03-31,Glass bonding medium for ultrasonic devices,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3413188A,1963-06-14,Glass fiber-wood laminates and methods of producing such laminates,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3413229A,1964-03-03,Polyvinyl alcohol compositions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3413268A,1965-12-03,Use of aminoalkylamino-s-triazines as hardening agents for epoxy resins and hardenedepoxy resin,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",1,1,17
US3413335A,1964-12-28,Alkyl succinate ester process,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3413461A,1966-01-28,Desk lamp,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3413506A,1966-07-06,Znte:o electroluminescent device,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3413596A,1966-12-08,Continuous wave marine seismic exploration,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3413702A,1965-03-01,Turret machine having tool store,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3413725A,1967-07-28,Dowel assembly with removable positioning means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3413745A,1967-04-05,Blankout sign,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3413784A,1966-04-28,Cotton stripping apparatus,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3413826A,1966-04-04,Yarn stacking device for knitting machines,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3413837A,1965-06-24,Katharometer bridge,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3413946A,1966-08-31,Spar buoy vessel,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3413979A,1959-02-02,Continuous cigarette rod-making machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3413983A,1965-10-21,Bobby pin spreader,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3414112A,1967-06-08,Cap feeding apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3414190A,1967-02-17,Trigonometric computing instrument,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3414317A,1966-12-30,Combination weatherstrip and windshield washer hose,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3414337A,1966-05-18,Rod guide,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3414412A,1963-03-29,Producing a mandarin-like flavoring composition by admixing thymol and methyl-n-methyl anthranilate,"['VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,18
US3414452A,1967-08-22,Labeler,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3414535A,1965-09-27,Polyvinyl chloride stabilized by oxamides,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3414546A,1967-04-14,Aromatic polyamide-esters from amino aryl dicarboxylic acid diesters,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3414549A,1965-09-21,Vinyl-bis (trifluoromethyl) carbinol and copolymers,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,10
US3414577A,1962-01-10,Quaternary ammonium salts of ajmaline,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3414635A,1965-10-18,Hydroxyalkyl esters in surface coatings,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3414754A,1965-11-20,Anode plate for x-ray tubes,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3414859A,1968-12-03,Bimetallic driven time delay relay,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3414906A,1965-02-24,Cap,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3414925A,1966-06-24,Cleaner for meat grinder heads,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3414934A,1966-06-29,Shrimp vein removing apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3415027A,1965-07-30,Truss of spaced pyramidal units,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3415063A,1964-08-12,Shield segment for covering the inner wall of the tunnel made of composite shell units,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3415106A,1965-03-09,Continuous band forging machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3415126A,1964-09-25,Azimuth laying system,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3415127A,1967-03-20,Turret tuner for uhf television and other purposes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3415214A,1967-08-02,Shipboard cargo stowage construction,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3415405A,1965-11-09,Cap,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3415435A,1967-01-30,Capstan,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3415453A,1967-03-13,Swirl device for sprinkler heads,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3415518A,1965-10-22,Golfer's aid,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3415523A,1966-08-17,Golfer's training device,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3415580A,1966-07-07,Shaft with deformable end portion,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3415598A,1965-10-18,Stereo viewing apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3415731A,1965-01-29,Glass electrodes and method for producing the same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3415770A,1963-11-18,Polyvinyl chloride plasticized with mixed alkyl terpene dibasic acid esters,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3415789A,1967-02-08,Polymers from phosphonitrilic halides and tetraalkyl difunctional cyclobutanes,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3415811A,1964-09-28,Antibiotic lincomycin k and process for the production thereof,"['ADJ', 'X', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADV']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",1,1,10
US3415869A,1962-01-23,Dibenzoyl esters of n-(methyl or ethyl)-n-[n'-(methyl or ethyl)-n'-(alpha-ethyl-beta-hydroxyethyl),"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']","['GPE', 'PERSON']",1,1,15
US3415915A,1964-09-10,Continuous method and means for the manufacture of hollow objects,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3415963A,1964-05-15,Ethyl cellulose composition for use in arc extinguishing apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3415976A,1966-07-27,Arc welding electrode,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3416085A,1963-07-03,"Galvanometer suspension assembly having a simplified center of gravity, buoyancy and centerline adjustment","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3416091A,1965-03-05,Amplifier circuit having feedback connection for reducing distortion caused by the non-linear characteristic of its output transformer,"['ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,20
US3416187A,1966-04-18,Patty molding machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3416276A,1966-08-26,Masonry walls and partitions and method of fabricating same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3416294A,1966-08-11,Continuous self-evacuating air cleaner,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3416297A,1966-10-19,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3416298A,1965-04-13,Crop harvesting machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3416381A,1963-12-06,Solenoid actuated valve with manual override,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3416408A,1967-05-04,Vacuum control system with regulating relay valve,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3416471A,1966-01-28,Yarn tensioning apparatus for tufting machines capable of making pile fabrics with repeat patterns thereon of loops of varying lengths,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,21
US3416512A,1967-01-09,Infrared heating system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3416521A,1964-10-06,Breathing mask suspension,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3416541A,1965-10-24,Cigarette filter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3416601A,1967-03-28,Resin composition and method of use,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3416604A,1967-03-20,Epoxy resin grouting fluid and method for stabilizing earth formations,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3416680A,1967-03-13,Bin turning attachment for fork lift vehicle,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3416760A,1966-12-02,Gutter and bracket hanger,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3416880A,1964-10-13,Modification of cellulosic textiles with methylolated hydroxyalkyl carbamates,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3416937A,1965-02-05,Glass composition for use as the face plate of an image orthicon tube and the like,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3416990A,1965-08-06,Glass fiber-reinforced polymers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3417026A,1964-03-17,Glass standard for fluorescence,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3417091A,1965-05-10,Nitro imidazoyl ethyl pyridines and quinolines,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']","['GPE', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US3417129A,1964-06-26,Process for the manufacture of acetoacetic acid methyl ester and acetoacetic acid ethyl ester,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3417136A,1965-10-21,Aminocarboxylic acids and salts thereof,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3417162A,1960-06-02,"Epoxy modified vinyl copolymers of alpha,beta-unsaturated dicarboxylic acid partial esters","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3417180A,1966-01-18,Hydrolyzed polyvinyl acetate resin hair sprays,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['GPE', 'PERSON']",0,1,7
US3417186A,1965-07-06,Glass making apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3417337A,1965-07-30,Homodyne reference generator having voltage controlled phase,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3417395A,1966-08-09,Volumetric display,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3417407A,1966-02-23,Cap construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3417467A,1967-04-26,Shearhead assemblies on electrical and mechanical shavers,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3417503A,1966-12-20,Spinner for fishing by the bait-casting method,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3417553A,1966-07-18,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3417673A,1966-08-01,Swab cup,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3417689A,1967-10-30,Label imprinter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3417707A,1966-06-15,Hose pump,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3417867A,1967-04-12,Hose mounting bracket,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3417882A,1966-06-16,Shaker loader,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3417908A,1966-06-06,Tacker with attachment for outward clinch,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3417983A,1966-02-23,Cupola construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3418017A,1966-02-10,Cylinder spring latch lockset,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3418132A,1965-06-01,Aldehyde gelatin hardening composition with carbocyclic diones,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3418223A,1966-06-08,Continuous process for producing magnesium metal from magnesium chloride including fused bath electrolysis,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3418332A,1966-05-23,Dibenzocycloheptene thiazole derivatives,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3418355A,1964-10-16,Didecyl quaternary ammonium compounds,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3418377A,1965-03-15,Diphenyl ether polyols,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3418428A,1964-10-20,Multifrequency telegraph receiver with damping means for resonant reed detectors,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3418438A,1967-02-13,Jack plug connector,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3418576A,1963-07-11,Meter assembly with expandable clamping ring,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3418593A,1966-04-25,Amplifier circuit with semiconductor device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3418713A,1967-03-24,Blade connection means for power-operated slicing knife,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3418830A,1965-06-22,Yarn feed mechanism for circular knitting machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3418892A,1965-12-20,Carton folding and gluing machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3418893A,1965-12-30,Carton feeding and erecting apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3418958A,1967-05-01,Spar for sailing graft and method of manufacturing same,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3419025A,1966-12-13,Protective sleeve for tarpaulin rigging,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3419135A,1965-10-26,Screw clip or the like including headless screws with cylindrical bore driving means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3419168A,1966-09-08,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3419191A,1967-06-08,Dispensing assembly,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3419250A,1966-10-25,Continuous mixer discharge control,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3419276A,1967-06-27,Golfer's arm bend indicator,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3419277A,1966-05-31,Golfer's arm positioning device comprising elbow bend restraining means,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3419481A,1966-04-08,Electrolyte and process for electroplating black chromium and article thereby produced,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3419503A,1966-06-30,Activating a composite catalyst with hcl prior to a carbon chloride treatment,"['VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3419519A,1963-12-10,Methacrylic resin-vinylidene chloride resin compositions and method of production thereof,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3419542A,1964-09-24,Azo dyestuffs containing a ureido group,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3419562A,1964-03-17,Quaternary ammonium acinitro compounds,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']","['PERSON', 'NORP']",0,1,5
US3419594A,1966-04-08,Continuous process for the halogenation of tolylene diisocyanate,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3419707A,1966-03-07,Rod and tube temperature sensor for controlling the heating means of an oven or the like,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3419793A,1965-04-02,Volumetric flow measuring device employing pulsed paramagnetic resonance,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3419795A,1966-08-03,Nmr flowmeter employing pulsed magnetization,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3419838A,1966-12-19,Trip-free circuit breaker device,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3419839A,1966-04-14,Cartridge fuse holders,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3419872A,1966-06-23,Dipole antenna having coaxial cable arms capacitively coupled to spaced tubular radiators,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3419936A,1967-01-31,Spinneret for melt spinning filaments,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3420031A,1966-11-16,Masonry construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3420155A,1966-10-10,Delay latch for blast valves,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3420260A,1966-12-02,Solenoid valve with integral plastic bobbin and seat,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3420331A,1966-12-12,Segmented mechanical proboscis,"['VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420360A,1967-06-30,Split pack of cigarettes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3420378A,1966-10-05,Gutter guard having removable hinges,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3420415A,1967-06-09,Leakproof dispensing container,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420420A,1967-05-31,Holster for revolver,"['ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420468A,1967-05-10,Crochet caddy,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3420496A,1967-01-09,Solenoid valve assembly,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420536A,1966-06-01,Split ring packing with elastomeric support for rotative and reciprocable parts,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3420538A,1966-01-21,Swivel finger chuck,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420559A,1966-09-29,Dowel locks,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3420639A,1967-10-20,Molten salt method of separation of americium from plutonium,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3420653A,1965-03-08,Glass melting furnace,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420693A,1964-06-05,Glass having dual protective coatings thereon and a method for forming such coatings,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3420696A,1964-06-02,Aldehyde fixation on polymeric material,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3420736A,1965-09-01,Felt cleaner for paper making machine,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3420740A,1963-05-30,Digitalis tetraglycosides and production thereof,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3420798A,1965-06-23,Cross-linked polymers of lactonized poly (methyl propenol/methacrylic acid) and method of preparing by applying heat,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,22
US3420807A,1966-12-19,Vinyl chloride polymerization,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3420828A,1965-08-18,"Process for producing n-methoxy ethyl morpholine substantially free of beta,beta diaminodiethyl ether","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,17
US3420915A,1966-11-17,"Phenol modified hydrocarbon resins and blends thereof with epoxy resin,polyurethane or polythiol","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3420917A,1965-12-02,Tris(disubstituted phosphenyl ethyl) phosphine oxides,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3420965A,1965-04-23,Cartridge tape recorder play-back instrument,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3421061A,1966-04-05,Multifrequency receiving signal summing multiphase induction motor,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3421063A,1967-11-22,Rectifier and controller including triac switch,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US3421076A,1966-10-03,Cable scanning method and apparatus wherein corona discharge is detected only at approximately peak values of an applied voltage,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,20
US3421095A,1966-05-26,Continuous hemispherical contour limit switch for antenna,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3421125A,1967-03-09,Solenoid actuated device,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3421130A,1964-10-12,Fuse and disconnect device for mounting inside a high voltage bushing,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3421143A,1965-10-24,Vehicle lamp electrical warning device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3421150A,1966-08-26,Multiprocessor interrupt directory,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3421181A,1966-06-24,Spinneret plate,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3421191A,1966-12-20,Yarn winding apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3421236A,1967-06-22,Linkage for an ejector type bucket loader,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3421308A,1967-09-06,Traveler for ring spinning and twisting,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3421341A,1966-10-18,Clasp combined with detachably mounted ornament,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3421409A,1967-05-09,Cartridge feed system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3421505A,1966-07-06,Colostomy garment,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3421569A,1966-03-11,Continuous casting,"['ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3421572A,1965-10-06,Continuous casting apparatus having independent transverse and longitudinal mold surface movement,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3421636A,1965-11-05,Automatic trainline connector,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3421649A,1967-12-28,Bottle carrying case,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3421660A,1966-07-18,Dispensing means for washing appliance,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3421680A,1967-09-05,Dispensing containers and blanks therefor,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3421789A,1967-01-19,Carton holder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3421876A,1965-11-04,Glass furnace with two separate throat passages,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,8
US3421920A,1965-05-25,"Tablet coating containing a linear poly-1,3-beta-glucoside","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3421954A,1966-10-28,Melt explosive composition having a matrix of an inorganic oxygen supplying salt,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3422025A,1964-11-10,Glass laserable material,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3422030A,1966-05-11,Alkyl phenyl phosphite inhibitors for alkylated phenols,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3422042A,1961-10-19,Aldehyde-modified unsaturated carboxylic acid amide interpolymer/cellulose acetate butyrate resinous compositions,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3422102A,1963-10-04,Omega tertiary amino-1-methyl alkyl- 4,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NUM']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,7
US3422139A,1964-06-09,Acrylamido-n-glycolic acid and methylol derivative,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3422177A,1966-09-06,Melt elastic extruder and method,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3422178A,1965-10-12,Continuous polymer casting machine and process,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3422198A,1962-01-22,N-methyl 3-methyl-5-ethyl phenyl carbamate as an insecticide,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3422232A,1964-10-08,Speech pattern rearranging communication system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3422341A,1965-06-18,Rectifying apparatus for producing constant d.c. output voltage,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3422386A,1966-10-06,Resistor circuit network and method of making,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3422433A,1967-04-21,Loran receiving system,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3422444A,1966-09-22,Alphanumeric galvanometer recorder,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3422453A,1965-05-27,Di-o-biphenylyl diphenyl bisphenol a bis phosphate and process,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3422469A,1966-02-07,Hose coupling tool,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3422515A,1966-05-23,Method for making porous electrodes comprising freezing wet powder and sintering,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3422516A,1967-09-25,Yarn-treating process,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3422582A,1960-12-30,Multilevel building with stairway,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3422608A,1965-10-21,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3422613A,1967-05-08,Yarn assembly apparatus for false twisting yarn,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3422674A,1965-11-22,Continuous well logging apparatus,"['ADJ', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3422710A,1966-08-25,Turret construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3422729A,1966-09-29,Hose block swivel,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3422746A,1966-08-08,Superbroiler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3422751A,1965-09-07,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3422769A,1966-09-22,Trolley turn-around,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3422803A,1967-06-07,Internal combustion engine construction and method for operation with lean air-fuel mixtures,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3422822A,1962-02-27,Cigarette filter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3422828A,1966-12-30,Cleaner for paint rollers,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3422838A,1965-09-28,Hose reel,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3422867A,1966-12-21,"Device for washing and drying of delicate fabrics such as nylon hose,lingerie,and the like","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,19
US3422982A,1967-04-17,Breather for a gear housing,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3422997A,1967-10-04,Dispensing cap,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3423062A,1967-09-27,Solenoid pilot operated valve,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3423087A,1966-04-06,Billiard ball rack,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3423109A,1966-03-30,Hose fitting,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3423132A,1967-11-13,Cotton harvester delivery conveyor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3423133A,1967-09-29,Cotton harvester delivery conveyor and method of conveying,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3423150A,1965-08-23,Eyeglass frame with adjustable rear view mirrors,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3423164A,1963-06-21,Continuous process of shrinkproofing wool with alkali metal salts of dichlorisocyanuric acid,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3423184A,1963-06-28,Apparatus for the production of finely divided amorphous silica,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3423196A,1965-08-18,Glass article having a birefringence pattern and method of production,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3423246A,1964-01-06,Leakproof electrode,"['ADJ', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3423290A,1966-08-03,Lyophilized reaction mixtures,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3423375A,1963-11-29,Neutron radiation sorbers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3423413A,1964-07-23,"1-hydroxy or chloro benzyl-2-(-4 methyl,ethyl or hydroxyethyl-piperazino methyl) benzimidazoles","['X', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,17
US3423607A,1966-06-29,Josephson current structures,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3423723A,1967-02-13,Jaw construction for bladejaw contacts,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3423731A,1965-05-13,Scanner and resolver combination,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3423795A,1964-12-30,Continuous filamentary cushioning material,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3423985A,1966-02-04,Stripper and pre-draw ring for wall-ironing can bodies,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3423988A,1966-08-01,Meter prover apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424001A,1966-08-02,Flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3424035A,1966-06-11,Spur gear type planetary gearings,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3424044A,1966-03-10,Continuous three-knife trimmer,"['ADJ', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,6
US3424045A,1966-04-19,Shearing machine for plates,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3424048A,1967-10-12,Guitar kit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3424068A,1967-07-26,Carton forming block,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424089A,1965-07-08,Cartridge cases,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3424106A,1966-11-14,Trackman's car,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3424183A,1967-03-15,Solenoid controlled servovalve with lineal output,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3424212A,1967-04-12,Screw wrench device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424224A,1966-12-16,Cord control mechanism for roller shades,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3424251A,1965-07-12,Bulldozer,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3424255A,1966-11-16,Continuous coring jet bit,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3424359A,1967-07-17,Yarn handling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424382A,1966-05-20,Split plug vectorable exhaust nozzle,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3424406A,1966-11-04,Shimmy damper for aircraft dual nosewheels,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3424414A,1966-11-03,Cigar lighter receptacle,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424429A,1965-10-23,Solenoid operated valve,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3424467A,1966-08-25,Chuck construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3424468A,1965-11-11,Power-operable multijaw chuck,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3424487A,1967-04-27,Glass transporting rack,"['NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424569A,1965-11-08,Glass forming container neck ring,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3424608A,1964-09-30,Glass fiber reinforced elastomers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3424666A,1966-04-15,Al-hg-bi alloy galvanic anode,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3424706A,1966-07-08,Vinylidene chloride copolymerization in presence of preformed seed latex,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3424714A,1963-11-13,Methacrolein polymer stabilized with a benzophenone,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3424724A,1965-10-24,Aldehyde-modified carbamates,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3424736A,1960-06-24,Diene polymerization process and catalyst therefor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3424908A,1966-10-19,Amplifier for photocell,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3424959A,1964-09-24,Split phase induction motor solid state position control with braking at balance,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3425091A,1966-12-12,Spinneret and nozzle assembly for the manufacture of composite filaments,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3425281A,1965-01-15,Vacuum gauge apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3425346A,1963-02-27,Label dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3425449A,1966-11-10,Solenoid controlled valve,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3425482A,1965-06-23,Continuous casting of non-ferrous metals,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3425581A,1966-09-21,Cigarette tray,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3425632A,1967-02-27,Hollow pin slip coupler having sprinkler head,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3425683A,1966-07-01,Dispensing unit,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3425705A,1967-03-22,Collet chuck and the like,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3425714A,1967-07-10,Lifting jack for hay balers,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3425716A,1967-03-16,Glass union,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3425757A,1968-01-17,Split drill pipe protector,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3425839A,1965-06-18,Continuous beer making process wherein the wort and yeast are separated by a porous partition,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3425859A,1965-10-23,"Glass surfaces having dual protective,label accepting coatings and method","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3425861A,1964-07-27,Continuous application of substances to travelling materials,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3425895A,1965-09-24,Glass fibers sized with hydroformylated polymer and laminate therefrom,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3425918A,1965-11-12,Electrolyte for the production of selfcolored anodic oxide layers on aluminum and aluminum alloys,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3425972A,1963-06-20,Preparation of water soluble trans parent films from dextrin and polyvinyl alcohol,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3426034A,1966-03-24,Omega-phenyl-omega-pyridyl alkylamine derivatives,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3426107A,1962-04-13,Polypropylene containing partially hydrolyzed ethylene-vinyl acetate copolymer,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3426155A,1964-07-02,Subscriber's line circuit using reed relays,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3426285A,1965-09-07,Amplifier testing apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3426290A,1965-10-20,Amplifier having series regulated voltage supply,"['ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3426334A,1963-12-19,Continuous selective readout for magnetic core systems,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3426401A,1967-02-02,Hose clamp,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3426429A,1965-03-23,Chuck means for dental hand piece,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3426490A,1966-12-23,Masonry veneer siding and mold,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3426498A,1966-07-05,Truss,['ADV'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3426506A,1966-11-22,Carton folding machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3426521A,1966-04-28,Rayon looper clip yarns,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3426575A,1966-11-25,Bending tool for mounted fittings,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3426579A,1965-09-03,Continuous monitor for the rapid detection of hydrogen and oxygen,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3426662A,1966-06-30,Movie camera iris control device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,6
US3426703A,1966-07-28,Monorail vehicle system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3426884A,1967-08-15,Glass bottle handling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3427035A,1965-07-13,Collet chuck for machining thin workpieces,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3427036A,1964-10-27,Hydraulic chuck,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3427207A,1966-10-28,Batteries with halogen fluoride electrolyte,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3427295A,1958-12-10,Pentaerythritol derivatives,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3427298A,1963-03-11,Polyvinyl alcohol materials and compositions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3427316A,1966-05-02,Quaternary ammonium hydroxamates,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427332A,1967-09-05,Perfluoroalkyl amide derivatives of polyoxyalkylene carbamates,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['GPE', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US3427333A,1963-12-19,Propargyl 2-bromodecanoate,"['PROPN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3427342A,1962-12-12,Continuous sulfonation process,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427370A,1962-08-13,Resin recovery system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427423A,1964-08-05,Method of and apparatus for electric discharge machining with air dielectric,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3427680A,1966-05-06,Knob locking device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427813A,1967-02-08,Shield tunneling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427837A,1966-05-06,Solenoid-actuated air cylinder,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3427867A,1965-11-22,Ultrasonic attenuation meter,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427879A,1965-06-25,Flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3427895A,1965-10-14,Splitter damper linkage,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3427922A,1967-11-13,Loader's safety switch,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3428051A,1966-06-20,Cigar shaper,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3428111A,1964-04-20,Continuous casting method using a rotating wheel,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3428153A,1965-11-18,Antiskid brake for a vehicle wheel,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3428165A,1966-02-03,Screw conveyor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3428183A,1968-01-18,Gutter guard,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3428184A,1966-01-14,Screens for removal of liquid from sludge materials,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3428188A,1967-11-07,Yarn supply creel frame,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3428206A,1964-04-25,Bottle crate of synthetic material,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3428248A,1967-09-26,Continuous centrifuge apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3428266A,1967-04-25,Yarn winding apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3428292A,1966-01-03,Unstressed seats for between flange valves,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3428327A,1966-09-19,Quick release rotary tool chuck,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3428340A,1967-03-20,Hose coupling,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3428409A,1966-09-06,"Rigid wick,rigid core-wick and rigidized candle","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3428483A,1965-01-13,Vinylidene chloride copolymer coated polymeric film containing steatite talc in the coating,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3428498A,1964-08-06,Preparation of sintered permanent alnico magnets,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3428502A,1966-10-25,Polyvinyl acetate binder for crystalline explosive,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3428548A,1966-09-27,Plasma reaction system for reacting a gas with a non-gaseous material,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3428560A,1967-02-27,Yarn-lubricating composition,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3428629A,1965-07-13,Halovinyl compounds,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3428732A,1964-12-02,Lincomycin alkylsulfamates,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3428881A,1966-09-02,D.c. motor speed control system,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3428924A,1967-05-08,Solenoid operated impulse relay,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3429109A,1965-05-19,Gang lawnmower,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3429110A,1965-08-09,Gang lawnmower,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3429168A,1967-04-11,Rod bending method and apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3429181A,1965-10-22,Flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3429340A,1966-05-07,Solenoid operated valve with manual override,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3429381A,1966-04-11,Slope grader for bulldozers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3429415A,1967-10-17,Tab programming control system by means of codes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3429435A,1967-06-26,Screw conveyor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3429486A,1966-01-10,Tar impregnated fused silica stopper head,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3429660A,1964-12-08,Alumina production,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3429684A,1962-01-29,Glass melting furnace with vacuum feed means,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3429714A,1965-11-22,"Baker's all-purpose,plastic shortening composition","['PROPN', 'PART', 'PRON', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3429770A,1965-12-14,Plywood glue extender of densified walnut shell flour and compositions containing it,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3429773A,1964-04-16,Continuous cellulose digester with charging device,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3429832A,1966-05-31,Glower lamp and process,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3429839A,1965-04-23,Epoxy polymer derived polymers containing quaternary phosphonium groups,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3429872A,1957-07-02,Azo compounds containing dihydroxyphenyl groups and oxalyl ester groups,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3430032A,1965-11-10,Microflask heating device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3430147A,1966-01-19,Squelch tail preventing circuit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3430247A,1967-09-05,Centerfed travelling wave array having a squinted aperture,"['VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3430253A,1967-11-08,Oscillograph with means for providing second record of the input,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'ORDINAL']",1,1,11
US3430262A,1966-09-12,Welder's face shield mounting bracket for safety hats,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3430278A,1967-10-16,Cleaner for meat products,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3430430A,1968-01-04,Yarn spinning device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3430432A,1964-07-23,Glass yarn having controlled torsional forces,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3430461A,1967-05-18,Blade adapter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3430527A,1967-06-07,Split nut adapter tool,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3430663A,1962-04-12,"Hose line for sucking off hot gases,particularly in the vacuum degassing of large metal and steel batches","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,20
US3430874A,1963-12-27,Continuous muller,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3430924A,1966-12-12,Continuous mixing machine,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3431051A,1967-06-22,Photocopier,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3431095A,1965-11-24,Glass bending furnace,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3431231A,1966-02-09,Silica and silica-containing vulcanizates,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,1,7
US3431241A,1967-05-15,Monoisocyanate condensed resorcinol-aldehyde resins,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3431265A,1964-03-17,Quaternary ammonium salts of glyceryl sulfates and sulfonates,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3431309A,1963-06-28,Trans-di(hydroxyalkyl)cyclobutanes,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3431310A,1967-09-28,Polyalkyl cycloalkyl phenol polymers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3431315A,1967-03-27,Butene-1 purification,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3431341A,1967-06-09,Bacteria inhibiting composition containing polymix b and o-carbamyl-d-serine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3431507A,1964-09-28,Amplifier with temperature compensation lying in the feedback path,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3431664A,1965-10-25,Bucket tooth for excavating equipment,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3431713A,1966-10-05,Crop harvesting and dewatering machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3431727A,1968-01-18,Jack arrangement for trailers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3431764A,1967-03-10,Tube tapering roller chuck,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3431770A,1965-04-05,Analyzer for determining hydrogen-to-carbon ratio in a material,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3431971A,1964-04-20,Continuous casting machine of the rotatable wheel type,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3432053A,1967-06-02,Automotive bin carrying machine,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3432063A,1964-04-25,Bottle crate of synthetic material,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3432086A,1967-09-27,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3432112A,1967-08-10,Expansible chuck for tubular core,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3432113A,1967-07-26,Split reel,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3432140A,1966-06-30,Solenoid valve,"['ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3432238A,1959-05-27,Spectrometric apparatus of high resolving power,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3432247A,1966-06-13,Boiler for heating combustible fluids,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3432296A,1967-07-13,Plasma sintering,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3432352A,1963-05-27,High temperature fuel cell having a palladium film between the anode and electrolyte,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,1,14
US3432440A,1965-02-11,Epoxy curing agents comprising a fluoborate salt and a hydrolyzable ester,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3432483A,1965-02-18,Continuous process for preparing finely divided polymers,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3432490A,1962-11-08,2-(beta-hexamethylene imino ethyl) cyclohexanone,"['NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3432496A,1966-05-19,Alkyl alkenyl arsinic acids and salts thereof,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3432552A,1965-06-09,Dihydrotricyclopentadienylamine and preparation thereof,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3432566A,1966-03-23,Carotenoid compounds,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3432595A,1965-06-30,"Melanoma cell line of canine origin,its propagation and use,and vaccines derived therefrom","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,17
US3432607A,1964-08-17,Bass control of electronic musical instruments,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3432640A,1963-12-26,Infrared heating method for molding machines and the like,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3432646A,1964-06-25,Retina character reader,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3432763A,1966-12-13,Amplifier employing nonlinear dc negative feedback to stabilize its dc operating point,"['ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3432796A,1966-12-14,Multiplanar electrical connection techniques,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3432797A,1966-08-19,Jack-controlled system for multiple connections,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3432816A,1966-01-10,Glass delay line recirculating memory,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3432867A,1967-07-13,Gutter and water supply system for swimming pools,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3433067A,1967-03-22,Meter and side-mounted regulator combination,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3433076A,1966-10-12,Thermometer,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3433081A,1966-10-17,Tuner mechanism,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3433095A,1966-10-21,Split power transmission,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433191A,1966-02-01,Knit stitch machines,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3433247A,1966-02-24,Hose reels and mountings therefor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3433254A,1966-06-24,Vacuum control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3433288A,1964-10-21,Continuous casting apparatus with tiltable intermediate ladle,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3433306A,1967-10-18,Cambered blade for aircraft sustaining rotor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3433314A,1967-08-14,Jack-type weigher with cantilever spring,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3433331A,1967-05-22,Diamond drill bit,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433379A,1967-07-20,Glass preserving jars,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433391A,1966-03-07,Dispensing container with collapsible compartment,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3433394A,1966-12-15,Dispensing closure cap,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433402A,1965-04-23,Carton box and blank therefor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3433406A,1966-04-25,Calorie-gram indicator and alarm,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3433432A,1967-07-20,Yarn package support,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433451A,1966-04-11,Crypt form,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3433458A,1967-01-25,Pneumatic and hydraulic jack for garage use,"['ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3433491A,1966-03-01,Chuck jaws,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3433492A,1966-02-24,Chuck,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3433505A,1965-10-08,Hose fitting for connecting hoses of different sizes,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3433507A,1966-02-24,Split t,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3433561A,1965-10-21,Stereo moving picture camera,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3433607A,1965-08-02,Quaternary ammonium salts of esters of salicylic acid as rust inhibitors,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3433621A,1966-04-28,Halovinyl mercurials as plant defoliants,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3433681A,1964-08-04,Leakproof electrochemical cell and method of making same,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3433697A,1965-07-15,Label applicator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3433749A,1965-06-30,Glass electrode compositions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433819A,1966-09-22,"Hexasubstituted-2-sila-1,3-dioxolanes","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3433847A,1966-09-14,Continuous alkylation process,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3433928A,1967-06-16,Cigar lighter,"['PROPN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3434064A,1966-02-17,Amplifier drift tester,"['ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3434072A,1963-01-18,Continuous wave laser arrangement,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3434094A,1967-07-20,Buss strip,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3434166A,1967-09-22,Houseboat,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3434185A,1967-12-14,Lingerie clasp,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3434266A,1966-05-02,Cap crimping apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3434344A,1966-06-14,Swirl meter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3434355A,1966-05-12,Gyroscope,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3434402A,1966-01-11,Turret font photocomposing machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3434422A,1959-04-22,Continuous rod mat,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3434523A,1965-06-16,Continuous process and plant for polymer separation from polymer solutions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3434565A,1967-12-21,Silencer with angled tuning tube leading to helmholtz resonator,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3434629A,1966-12-13,Mouth wash dispenser,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3434714A,1965-04-21,Teeter-totter with adjustable brake means,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3434771A,1966-05-11,Gyroscopic lens,"['ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3434780A,1967-09-13,Eyeglass frame with pivotally mounted lens,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3434783A,1966-01-31,Cartridge-type motion picture camera having automatically adjustable film gate,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3434869A,1964-11-02,Foley catheter with silicone rubber coating,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3434872A,1964-08-17,Glass fabric reinforced mica tape and process for production thereof,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3434914A,1966-02-01,Glass fiber reinforced thermoplastic polyarylene polyether resin article and process for making same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3434915A,1965-11-17,Glass laminate,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3434974A,1965-07-02,Continuous manufacture of detergent laundry bars,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3435039A,1966-08-31,Quaternary ammonium salts of alcohol ether sulfates,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3435046A,1965-07-02,Trialkyl-silyl ethers of n-carboxy anhydrides of monohydroxy alpha-amino acids and processes for preparing them,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'X', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],1,1,21
US3435098A,1964-03-09,Resin composition of a vinyl chloride polymer blended with an ethylene-vinyl chloride copolymer,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3435118A,1955-05-17,Dibutyltin diacetate as a fungicidal agent,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3435163A,1965-08-25,Phone jack having a hollow housing with contact elements interfittingly secured therein,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3435219A,1967-01-30,Neutron spectrometer for high neutron flux,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3435252A,1964-08-26,D.c. restorer,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3435339A,1966-02-23,Bimetallic thermostatic device having ambient temperature compensation by means of a u-shaped bimetal element with a permanently set leg,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,22
US3435353A,1966-02-04,Amplifier-detector having wide dynamic range,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3435375A,1965-09-20,Controller having fet bridge circuit,"['PROPN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3435402A,1966-03-30,Slip ring assembly and process of manufacturing same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3435588A,1966-07-01,Continuous motion closure apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3435717A,1965-05-24,Label feed and cutting means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3435719A,1967-04-24,Shears for molten glass feeders,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3435765A,1966-04-28,Cartridge,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3435835A,1967-05-10,Cap washing machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3435874A,1965-06-01,Asymmetric tires,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3435879A,1965-01-11,Continuous casting method,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3435986A,1967-11-13,Dispensing mechanism having article distributing cylinder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3436079A,1966-03-09,Billiard cue,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3436117A,1967-07-13,Rod retrieval tool,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3436177A,1968-02-28,Continuous process for removing multivalent impurities from copper-bearing leach solutions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3436398A,1966-05-23,Benzhydrylidene thiazolidinones,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3436407A,1964-12-14,"Hydroxyflavin 3,4-diols,a method of producing them and medicament based thereon","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3436608A,1965-10-21,Trigger circuit for inductive load,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3436659A,1966-04-20,"Meter circuit including synchronized switching means for measuring the ""off"" current in a train of pulses","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,19
US3436789A,1966-10-06,Spinneret cleaning apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3436854A,1966-08-23,Label for holding packing slips,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3436970A,1966-06-26,Continuous and constant variable-ratio transmission mechanism,"['ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3437040A,1967-02-23,Cartridge adapters for high-powered firearms,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
