patent_number,date,title,tokens,nltk_pos,spacy_pos,spacy_label,is_prpn_spacy,is_person_spacy,spacy_pos_len
US1600027A,1925-08-28,Climber's belt,"[""Climber's"", 'belt']","[(""Climber's"", 'NNP'), ('belt', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1600128A,1926-01-20,Jack,['Jack'],"[('Jack', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600142A,1924-11-21,Jeweler's tool,"[""Jeweler's"", 'tool']","[(""Jeweler's"", 'NNP'), ('tool', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1600178A,1922-08-31,Truss,['Truss'],"[('Truss', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600189A,1926-09-14,Allison reginald m,"['Allison', 'reginald', 'm']","[('Allison', 'NNP'), ('reginald', 'VBZ'), ('m', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600193A,1925-10-03,Cartridge and twister holder,"['Cartridge', 'and', 'twister', 'holder']","[('Cartridge', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('twister', 'NN'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1600223A,1926-03-29,Cartridge containing gas-generating chemical,"['Cartridge', 'containing', 'gas-generating', 'chemical']","[('Cartridge', 'NNP'), ('containing', 'VBG'), ('gas-generating', 'JJ'), ('chemical', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1600231A,1926-04-30,Liner inserter for teat cups of milking machines,"['Liner', 'inserter', 'for', 'teat', 'cups', 'of', 'milking', 'machines']","[('Liner', 'NNP'), ('inserter', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('teat', 'NN'), ('cups', 'NNS'), ('of', 'IN'), ('milking', 'VBG'), ('machines', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1600269A,1924-12-22,Harrow,['Harrow'],"[('Harrow', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600275A,1925-02-12,Bricklayer's hammer,"[""Bricklayer's"", 'hammer']","[(""Bricklayer's"", 'NNP'), ('hammer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1600299A,1925-04-10,Antiskid device for automobiles,"['Antiskid', 'device', 'for', 'automobiles']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('device', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('automobiles', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1600324A,1923-10-24,Switch mechanism,"['Switch', 'mechanism']","[('Switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1600331A,1924-09-15,Oiler for springs or other devices to be lubricated,"['Oiler', 'for', 'springs', 'or', 'other', 'devices', 'to', 'be', 'lubricated']","[('Oiler', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('springs', 'NNS'), ('or', 'CC'), ('other', 'JJ'), ('devices', 'NNS'), ('to', 'TO'), ('be', 'VB'), ('lubricated', 'VBN')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1600332A,1926-09-21,Josef haslauer,"['Josef', 'haslauer']","[('Josef', 'NNP'), ('haslauer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600356A,1923-03-07,Cleaner for warping machines and beamers,"['Cleaner', 'for', 'warping', 'machines', 'and', 'beamers']","[('Cleaner', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('warping', 'VBG'), ('machines', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('beamers', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1600360A,1924-12-10,Gutter hanger,"['Gutter', 'hanger']","[('Gutter', 'NNP'), ('hanger', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600367A,1925-02-12,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600382A,1924-06-26,Label holder,"['Label', 'holder']","[('Label', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600397A,1922-06-05,Electrolyte for electrolytic cells,"['Electrolyte', 'for', 'electrolytic', 'cells']","[('Electrolyte', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('electrolytic', 'JJ'), ('cells', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1600482A,1922-02-10,Hose reel,"['Hose', 'reel']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('reel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600525A,1923-02-09,Thiophenol-sulphonic acid tanning and mordanting agents,"['Thiophenol-sulphonic', 'acid', 'tanning', 'and', 'mordanting', 'agents']","[('Thiophenol-sulphonic', 'JJ'), ('acid', 'NN'), ('tanning', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('mordanting', 'NN'), ('agents', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1600541A,1925-04-27,Jar opener,"['Jar', 'opener']","[('Jar', 'NNP'), ('opener', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1600572A,1924-09-17,Jack ladder,"['Jack', 'ladder']","[('Jack', 'NNP'), ('ladder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600576A,1925-12-07,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1600684A,1926-05-18,Lingerie clasp,"['Lingerie', 'clasp']","[('Lingerie', 'NNP'), ('clasp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600715A,1924-05-07,Cap selecting and feeding mechanism,"['Cap', 'selecting', 'and', 'feeding', 'mechanism']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('selecting', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('feeding', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1600759A,1926-09-21,Charles ernest griffiths,"['Charles', 'ernest', 'griffiths']","[('Charles', 'NNP'), ('ernest', 'JJS'), ('griffiths', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600761A,1925-04-01,Meter box,"['Meter', 'box']","[('Meter', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600763A,1923-12-28,Azo dyestuffs and process of making same,"['Azo', 'dyestuffs', 'and', 'process', 'of', 'making', 'same']","[('Azo', 'NNP'), ('dyestuffs', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('process', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('making', 'VBG'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1600765A,1926-04-20,Hose coupling,"['Hose', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'VBG')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1600797A,1926-09-21,Asfllokob to babjkicav kodak ook,"['Asfllokob', 'to', 'babjkicav', 'kodak', 'ook']","[('Asfllokob', 'NNP'), ('to', 'TO'), ('babjkicav', 'VB'), ('kodak', 'NNS'), ('ook', 'VB')]","['ADJ', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,5
US1600798A,1924-06-09,Cap for bottles or other containers,"['Cap', 'for', 'bottles', 'or', 'other', 'containers']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('bottles', 'NNS'), ('or', 'CC'), ('other', 'JJ'), ('containers', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1600840A,1920-07-09,Searchlight,['Searchlight'],"[('Searchlight', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600873A,1920-04-01,Jacquard card-cutting machine,"['Jacquard', 'card-cutting', 'machine']","[('Jacquard', 'NNP'), ('card-cutting', 'NN'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1600886A,1924-05-07,Dispensing machine,"['Dispensing', 'machine']","[('Dispensing', 'VBG'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1600898A,1923-05-18,Carton,['Carton'],"[('Carton', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1600900A,1924-09-24,Quarry block-sawing machine,"['Quarry', 'block-sawing', 'machine']","[('Quarry', 'NNP'), ('block-sawing', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1600929A,1925-03-07,Whistle,['Whistle'],"[('Whistle', 'VB')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601008A,1922-11-13,Cigar lighter,"['Cigar', 'lighter']","[('Cigar', 'NNP'), ('lighter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601047A,1926-01-18,Traveler's bag and case,"[""Traveler's"", 'bag', 'and', 'case']","[(""Traveler's"", 'NNP'), ('bag', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('case', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1601067A,1926-09-28,William w,"['William', 'w']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('w', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601074A,1920-08-17,Multifrequency-current transmission,"['Multifrequency-current', 'transmission']","[('Multifrequency-current', 'JJ'), ('transmission', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1601077A,1925-12-14,Sinew extractor,"['Sinew', 'extractor']","[('Sinew', 'NNP'), ('extractor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601092A,1920-10-21,Hose and means of manufacturing same,"['Hose', 'and', 'means', 'of', 'manufacturing', 'same']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('means', 'NNS'), ('of', 'IN'), ('manufacturing', 'NN'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1601136A,1924-10-29,Silencer,['Silencer'],"[('Silencer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601137A,1924-11-26,Silencer,['Silencer'],"[('Silencer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601138A,1926-03-06,Carpenter's scribing gauge,"[""Carpenter's"", 'scribing', 'gauge']","[(""Carpenter's"", 'NNP'), ('scribing', 'VBG'), ('gauge', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1601160A,1923-05-05,Knob mounting,"['Knob', 'mounting']","[('Knob', 'NNP'), ('mounting', 'VBG')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1601321A,1925-03-17,Liner puller,"['Liner', 'puller']","[('Liner', 'NNP'), ('puller', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601340A,1925-02-07,Cap and ring spinning and like frame,"['Cap', 'and', 'ring', 'spinning', 'and', 'like', 'frame']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('ring', 'VBG'), ('spinning', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('like', 'IN'), ('frame', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1601390A,1926-09-28,James blacklock henderson,"['James', 'blacklock', 'henderson']","[('James', 'NNP'), ('blacklock', 'NN'), ('henderson', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601392A,1922-01-09,Prop for motor cycles and the like,"['Prop', 'for', 'motor', 'cycles', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Prop', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('motor', 'NN'), ('cycles', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1601468A,1926-09-28,Albert joseph brownworth,"['Albert', 'joseph', 'brownworth']","[('Albert', 'NNP'), ('joseph', 'NN'), ('brownworth', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601506A,1926-09-28,George h,"['George', 'h']","[('George', 'NNP'), ('h', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601507A,1926-09-28,Gltje,['Gltje'],"[('Gltje', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1601544A,1925-10-03,Pan,['Pan'],"[('Pan', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601545A,1925-01-16,Yarn-carrier-controlling means for knitting machines,"['Yarn-carrier-controlling', 'means', 'for', 'knitting', 'machines']","[('Yarn-carrier-controlling', 'JJ'), ('means', 'NNS'), ('for', 'IN'), ('knitting', 'VBG'), ('machines', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1601549A,1926-09-28,wurtenberg,['wurtenberg'],"[('wurtenberg', 'NN')]",['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1601550A,1923-08-07,Continuous bias-cutting machine,"['Continuous', 'bias-cutting', 'machine']","[('Continuous', 'JJ'), ('bias-cutting', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1601579A,1926-09-28,William astle,"['William', 'astle']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('astle', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601587A,1926-09-28,Maurice,['Maurice'],"[('Maurice', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1601606A,1923-04-05,Combination test panel and polyphase meter trim,"['Combination', 'test', 'panel', 'and', 'polyphase', 'meter', 'trim']","[('Combination', 'NNP'), ('test', 'NN'), ('panel', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('polyphase', 'NN'), ('meter', 'NN'), ('trim', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1601626A,1924-07-21,Bin,['Bin'],"[('Bin', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1601667A,1926-04-29,Cotton chopper,"['Cotton', 'chopper']","[('Cotton', 'NNP'), ('chopper', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1601673A,1924-10-04,Fuse holder,"['Fuse', 'holder']","[('Fuse', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1601699A,1926-09-28,Victor,['Victor'],"[('Victor', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1601738A,1925-10-24,Rod weeder,"['Rod', 'weeder']","[('Rod', 'NNP'), ('weeder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601743A,1919-10-09,Flow meter,"['Flow', 'meter']","[('Flow', 'NNP'), ('meter', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1601744A,1920-03-15,Thermometer,['Thermometer'],"[('Thermometer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601751A,1925-01-17,Silencer for oil burners,"['Silencer', 'for', 'oil', 'burners']","[('Silencer', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('oil', 'NN'), ('burners', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1601789A,1925-03-09,Bottle crate,"['Bottle', 'crate']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('crate', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1601804A,1926-10-05,Montgomery w,"['Montgomery', 'w']","[('Montgomery', 'NNP'), ('w', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601890A,1925-08-03,Screw jack,"['Screw', 'jack']","[('Screw', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601915A,1921-08-25,Bat,['Bat'],"[('Bat', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1601926A,1924-05-28,Fuse holder,"['Fuse', 'holder']","[('Fuse', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1601953A,1926-03-30,Scaffold,['Scaffold'],"[('Scaffold', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1601960A,1922-03-10,Hose coupling,"['Hose', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'VBG')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1601976A,1924-12-15,Bowdin controller,"['Bowdin', 'controller']","[('Bowdin', 'NNP'), ('controller', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602012A,1926-02-03,Glass mold,"['Glass', 'mold']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('mold', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1602027A,1926-06-09,Catcher's glove,"[""Catcher's"", 'glove']","[(""Catcher's"", 'NNP'), ('glove', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1602032A,1926-04-26,Cleaner and cutter,"['Cleaner', 'and', 'cutter']","[('Cleaner', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('cutter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1602099A,1926-03-16,Cotton chopper,"['Cotton', 'chopper']","[('Cotton', 'NNP'), ('chopper', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1602132A,1922-07-29,Collapsible core and chuck,"['Collapsible', 'core', 'and', 'chuck']","[('Collapsible', 'JJ'), ('core', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('chuck', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1602136A,1920-11-08,Flow meter,"['Flow', 'meter']","[('Flow', 'NNP'), ('meter', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1602168A,1926-10-05,Hqwasd parker,"['Hqwasd', 'parker']","[('Hqwasd', 'NNP'), ('parker', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1602227A,1924-07-09,Fuse holder,"['Fuse', 'holder']","[('Fuse', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1602275A,1924-07-26,Auto jack,"['Auto', 'jack']","[('Auto', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1602289A,1925-09-05,Vehicle lamp,"['Vehicle', 'lamp']","[('Vehicle', 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602314A,1926-10-05,Dispensing machine,"['Dispensing', 'machine']","[('Dispensing', 'VBG'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1602322A,1925-12-12,Drill head,"['Drill', 'head']","[('Drill', 'NNP'), ('head', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602325A,1924-01-08,Bottle crate,"['Bottle', 'crate']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('crate', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1602326A,1925-06-19,Carboy holder,"['Carboy', 'holder']","[('Carboy', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602333A,1926-10-05,Charles ellis bttbke,"['Charles', 'ellis', 'bttbke']","[('Charles', 'NNP'), ('ellis', 'VBZ'), ('bttbke', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602346A,1924-11-17,Glass jar,"['Glass', 'jar']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('jar', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602347A,1926-10-05,Anthony eustace,"['Anthony', 'eustace']","[('Anthony', 'NNP'), ('eustace', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1602381A,1922-05-02,Bill sheet,"['Bill', 'sheet']","[('Bill', 'NNP'), ('sheet', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602420A,1923-02-10,Gutter hanger,"['Gutter', 'hanger']","[('Gutter', 'NNP'), ('hanger', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602432A,1925-03-11,Antiskid device,"['Antiskid', 'device']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('device', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602434A,1925-07-07,Mill,['Mill'],"[('Mill', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1602451A,1926-01-16,Shears,['Shears'],"[('Shears', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1602501A,1926-10-12,peterson,['peterson'],"[('peterson', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1602551A,1925-07-08,Cap and dauber,"['Cap', 'and', 'dauber']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('dauber', 'VB')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1602564A,1925-11-24,Spacing and aligning device,"['Spacing', 'and', 'aligning', 'device']","[('Spacing', 'VBG'), ('and', 'CC'), ('aligning', 'VBG'), ('device', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1602601A,1924-06-30,Fuse for signals or projectiles,"['Fuse', 'for', 'signals', 'or', 'projectiles']","[('Fuse', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('signals', 'NNS'), ('or', 'CC'), ('projectiles', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1602626A,1925-07-06,Bark press,"['Bark', 'press']","[('Bark', 'NNP'), ('press', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602707A,1925-11-30,Motor-vehicle jack,"['Motor-vehicle', 'jack']","[('Motor-vehicle', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1602708A,1924-11-05,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1602739A,1925-04-13,Hose bracket,"['Hose', 'bracket']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('bracket', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602748A,1923-09-22,Sprinkler nozzle,"['Sprinkler', 'nozzle']","[('Sprinkler', 'NNP'), ('nozzle', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602827A,1926-10-12,Adolph gk xthpetz,"['Adolph', 'gk', 'xthpetz']","[('Adolph', 'NNP'), ('gk', 'NN'), ('xthpetz', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1602839A,1924-01-21,Whistle,['Whistle'],"[('Whistle', 'VB')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1602861A,1924-09-15,Cap,['Cap'],"[('Cap', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1602926A,1918-08-19,Glass-forming apparatus,"['Glass-forming', 'apparatus']","[('Glass-forming', 'JJ'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1602941A,1926-10-12,Joseph rosman,"['Joseph', 'rosman']","[('Joseph', 'NNP'), ('rosman', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1602951A,1919-12-09,Electrolyte for electrolytic cells,"['Electrolyte', 'for', 'electrolytic', 'cells']","[('Electrolyte', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('electrolytic', 'JJ'), ('cells', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1602961A,1925-10-05,Jack,['Jack'],"[('Jack', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1603012A,1923-05-03,Switch mechanism,"['Switch', 'mechanism']","[('Switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1603158A,1923-09-12,Bending fibrous materials,"['Bending', 'fibrous', 'materials']","[('Bending', 'VBG'), ('fibrous', 'JJ'), ('materials', 'NNS')]","['VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1603288A,1926-05-17,Glass washer,"['Glass', 'washer']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('washer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1603301A,1925-06-02,Double-acting lock for autotruck cabs,"['Double-acting', 'lock', 'for', 'autotruck', 'cabs']","[('Double-acting', 'JJ'), ('lock', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('autotruck', 'JJ'), ('cabs', 'NNS')]","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1603316A,1925-08-25,Thermometer,['Thermometer'],"[('Thermometer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1603391A,1923-02-19,Spring jack,"['Spring', 'jack']","[('Spring', 'NN'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1603497A,1924-06-25,Magnetic chuck with fine-mesh faceplate,"['Magnetic', 'chuck', 'with', 'fine-mesh', 'faceplate']","[('Magnetic', 'JJ'), ('chuck', 'NN'), ('with', 'IN'), ('fine-mesh', 'JJ'), ('faceplate', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1603510A,1924-09-25,Carton,['Carton'],"[('Carton', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1603531A,1920-07-12,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1603548A,1926-10-19,Mahlcxkt e,"['Mahlcxkt', 'e']","[('Mahlcxkt', 'NNP'), ('e', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1603580A,1924-03-13,Meter-sealing means,"['Meter-sealing', 'means']","[('Meter-sealing', 'JJ'), ('means', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1603677A,1926-10-19,Charles francis,"['Charles', 'francis']","[('Charles', 'NNP'), ('francis', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1603744A,1926-10-19,burton,['burton'],"[('burton', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1603753A,1925-06-19,Bucket box for tank wagons and the like,"['Bucket', 'box', 'for', 'tank', 'wagons', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Bucket', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('tank', 'NN'), ('wagons', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1603772A,1924-05-12,Reflux column,"['Reflux', 'column']","[('Reflux', 'NNP'), ('column', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1603794A,1923-12-21,Hatband,['Hatband'],"[('Hatband', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1603836A,1924-03-29,Counterbalanced pumping jack,"['Counterbalanced', 'pumping', 'jack']","[('Counterbalanced', 'NNP'), ('pumping', 'VBG'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1603889A,1926-10-19,Porationi,['Porationi'],"[('Porationi', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1603906A,1925-08-27,Vacuum fluid burner,"['Vacuum', 'fluid', 'burner']","[('Vacuum', 'NNP'), ('fluid', 'NN'), ('burner', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1603926A,1925-08-18,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1603965A,1926-10-19,Bsake,['Bsake'],"[('Bsake', 'VB')]",['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1603979A,1926-10-19,peiler,['peiler'],"[('peiler', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1604018A,1925-10-16,Cartridge syringe,"['Cartridge', 'syringe']","[('Cartridge', 'NNP'), ('syringe', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604057A,1925-08-19,Barrel stand,"['Barrel', 'stand']","[('Barrel', 'NNP'), ('stand', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604061A,1926-06-28,Derailer,['Derailer'],"[('Derailer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1604068A,1926-10-19,William h,"['William', 'h']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('h', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1604119A,1925-08-27,Theftproof lamp,"['Theftproof', 'lamp']","[('Theftproof', 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1604139A,1926-10-26,Onhnnoh unfl jaiiowomv,"['Onhnnoh', 'unfl', 'jaiiowomv']","[('Onhnnoh', 'NNP'), ('unfl', 'JJ'), ('jaiiowomv', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604145A,1926-02-09,Powder holding and control mechanism,"['Powder', 'holding', 'and', 'control', 'mechanism']","[('Powder', 'NNP'), ('holding', 'VBG'), ('and', 'CC'), ('control', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1604211A,1925-07-01,Hose coupling,"['Hose', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'VBG')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604252A,1922-05-05,Hose nozzle,"['Hose', 'nozzle']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('nozzle', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604307A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604308A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604309A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604310A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604311A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604312A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604313A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604314A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604315A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604316A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604317A,1922-04-17,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604366A,1926-05-21,Coat,['Coat'],"[('Coat', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1604506A,1922-08-23,Marker for corn planters,"['Marker', 'for', 'corn', 'planters']","[('Marker', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('corn', 'NN'), ('planters', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1604611A,1926-10-26,Ray simpson,"['Ray', 'simpson']","[('Ray', 'NNP'), ('simpson', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1604664A,1922-07-26,Casein glue,"['Casein', 'glue']","[('Casein', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604687A,1926-04-15,Jar opener,"['Jar', 'opener']","[('Jar', 'NNP'), ('opener', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1604715A,1925-10-22,Jack,['Jack'],"[('Jack', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1604743A,1925-12-07,"Fiber-removing machine for flax, hemp, ramie, and other textile plants","['Fiber-removing', 'machine', 'for', 'flax,', 'hemp,', 'ramie,', 'and', 'other', 'textile', 'plants']","[('Fiber-removing', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('flax,', 'JJ'), ('hemp,', 'NN'), ('ramie,', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('other', 'JJ'), ('textile', 'NN'), ('plants', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US1604768A,1920-09-13,Cap for lamp sockets and the like,"['Cap', 'for', 'lamp', 'sockets', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('lamp', 'JJ'), ('sockets', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1604798A,1925-03-10,Jack receptacle-testing device,"['Jack', 'receptacle-testing', 'device']","[('Jack', 'NNP'), ('receptacle-testing', 'JJ'), ('device', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1604829A,1922-08-03,Boiler baffle,"['Boiler', 'baffle']","[('Boiler', 'NNP'), ('baffle', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1604859A,1922-04-08,Switch handle,"['Switch', 'handle']","[('Switch', 'NNP'), ('handle', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1604897A,1925-09-16,Harrow seat,"['Harrow', 'seat']","[('Harrow', 'NNP'), ('seat', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1604934A,1924-12-13,Antiskid and punctureproof device,"['Antiskid', 'and', 'punctureproof', 'device']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('punctureproof', 'JJ'), ('device', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1604976A,1926-04-09,Jockey's handhold,"[""Jockey's"", 'handhold']","[(""Jockey's"", 'NNP'), ('handhold', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1604999A,1926-11-02,William schmitz,"['William', 'schmitz']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('schmitz', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605055A,1925-02-07,Cigar-bunch machine,"['Cigar-bunch', 'machine']","[('Cigar-bunch', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1605059A,1924-09-13,Cigarette,['Cigarette'],"[('Cigarette', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605084A,1921-02-21,Switch mechanism,"['Switch', 'mechanism']","[('Switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1605148A,1925-10-10,Chuck for rock drills,"['Chuck', 'for', 'rock', 'drills']","[('Chuck', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('rock', 'NN'), ('drills', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1605168A,1924-11-25,Switch box,"['Switch', 'box']","[('Switch', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1605183A,1925-07-16,Harrow,['Harrow'],"[('Harrow', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605466A,1924-03-08,Thermometer,['Thermometer'],"[('Thermometer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605492A,1924-02-11,Vehicle lamp,"['Vehicle', 'lamp']","[('Vehicle', 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1605502A,1920-11-24,Fertilizer distributor,"['Fertilizer', 'distributor']","[('Fertilizer', 'NNP'), ('distributor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1605505A,1924-05-01,Acetylene lamp,"['Acetylene', 'lamp']","[('Acetylene', 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1605709A,1926-02-04,Harrow,['Harrow'],"[('Harrow', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605756A,1924-07-19,Electrolyte and method of making the same,"['Electrolyte', 'and', 'method', 'of', 'making', 'the', 'same']","[('Electrolyte', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('method', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('making', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1605761A,1926-11-02,Harald nielsen,"['Harald', 'nielsen']","[('Harald', 'NNP'), ('nielsen', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605777A,1926-11-02,richardson,['richardson'],"[('richardson', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1605781A,1923-12-21,Walter koqowski aitd waltes gbossee,"['Walter', 'koqowski', 'aitd', 'waltes', 'gbossee']","[('Walter', 'NNP'), ('koqowski', 'NNP'), ('aitd', 'NN'), ('waltes', 'NNS'), ('gbossee', 'VBP')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1605788A,1926-11-02,Cotton cleaneb,"['Cotton', 'cleaneb']","[('Cotton', 'NNP'), ('cleaneb', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1605789A,1926-11-02,Henry m,"['Henry', 'm']","[('Henry', 'NNP'), ('m', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605790A,1926-11-02,Banjo amplifier,"['Banjo', 'amplifier']","[('Banjo', 'NNP'), ('amplifier', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1605795A,1926-11-02,Kotaby hakbow,"['Kotaby', 'hakbow']","[('Kotaby', 'NNP'), ('hakbow', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605798A,1923-05-03,Marcel charles van cbombb,"['Marcel', 'charles', 'van', 'cbombb']","[('Marcel', 'NNP'), ('charles', 'NNS'), ('van', 'VBP'), ('cbombb', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']","['PRODUCT', 'PERSON']",1,1,4
US1605803A,1926-11-02,William wilegtts,"['William', 'wilegtts']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('wilegtts', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605809A,1926-11-02,Jacob l,"['Jacob', 'l']","[('Jacob', 'NNP'), ('l', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605811A,1926-11-02,danielson,['danielson'],"[('danielson', 'NN')]",['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1605812A,1926-11-02,William kennedy davidson and george smith muir,"['William', 'kennedy', 'davidson', 'and', 'george', 'smith', 'muir']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('kennedy', 'NNP'), ('davidson', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('george', 'NN'), ('smith', 'NNS'), ('muir', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US1605815A,1926-11-02,Joseph dekuy,"['Joseph', 'dekuy']","[('Joseph', 'NNP'), ('dekuy', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605831A,1926-11-02,Peter robeb-tsolsr gasdher aktd david wyllie,"['Peter', 'robeb-tsolsr', 'gasdher', 'aktd', 'david', 'wyllie']","[('Peter', 'NNP'), ('robeb-tsolsr', 'NN'), ('gasdher', 'NN'), ('aktd', 'NN'), ('david', 'NN'), ('wyllie', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1605835A,1926-11-02,hamilton,['hamilton'],"[('hamilton', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1605836A,1926-11-02,Fabrik,['Fabrik'],"[('Fabrik', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1605864A,1924-10-18,Bubou  steineggeb,"['Bubou', 'steineggeb']","[('Bubou', 'NNP'), ('steineggeb', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1605866A,1926-11-02,hew yoek,"['hew', 'yoek']","[('hew', 'NN'), ('yoek', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605868A,1925-06-29,Clasp for bracelets and wrist watches,"['Clasp', 'for', 'bracelets', 'and', 'wrist', 'watches']","[('Clasp', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('bracelets', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('wrist', 'NN'), ('watches', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1605876A,1926-11-02,Skikt-mabking apparatus,"['Skikt-mabking', 'apparatus']","[('Skikt-mabking', 'JJ'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1605881A,1926-11-02,Johastn martin weber,"['Johastn', 'martin', 'weber']","[('Johastn', 'NNP'), ('martin', 'NN'), ('weber', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1605885A,1926-11-02,Glass furnace,"['Glass', 'furnace']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('furnace', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1605895A,1925-08-06,Xslahb,['Xslahb'],"[('Xslahb', 'NN')]",['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1605944A,1926-11-09,Assighos to eodgeb ballast cab,"['Assighos', 'to', 'eodgeb', 'ballast', 'cab']","[('Assighos', 'NNP'), ('to', 'TO'), ('eodgeb', 'VB'), ('ballast', 'NN'), ('cab', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1605975A,1926-11-09,Geobge robert o neal,"['Geobge', 'robert', 'o', 'neal']","[('Geobge', 'NNP'), ('robert', 'NN'), ('o', 'NN'), ('neal', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1605986A,1926-11-09,redfield,['redfield'],"[('redfield', 'NN')]",['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1605988A,1926-11-09,op bolton,"['op', 'bolton']","[('op', 'IN'), ('bolton', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1605995A,1926-11-09,Blowee,['Blowee'],"[('Blowee', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1606013A,1926-11-09,Robert g,"['Robert', 'g']","[('Robert', 'NNP'), ('g', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606036A,1926-11-09,Calogeeo mtjuia,"['Calogeeo', 'mtjuia']","[('Calogeeo', 'NNP'), ('mtjuia', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606038A,1926-11-09,Max norman,"['Max', 'norman']","[('Max', 'NNP'), ('norman', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606039A,1926-11-09,Max norman,"['Max', 'norman']","[('Max', 'NNP'), ('norman', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606054A,1926-11-09,Diamond power,"['Diamond', 'power']","[('Diamond', 'NN'), ('power', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1606090A,1926-11-09,Unit ed s,"['Unit', 'ed', 's']","[('Unit', 'NNP'), ('ed', 'VBZ'), ('s', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606128A,1925-08-13,Chuck for stem ware,"['Chuck', 'for', 'stem', 'ware']","[('Chuck', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('stem', 'NN'), ('ware', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1606209A,1924-12-24,Azo dyestuff from barbituric acid and process of making the same,"['Azo', 'dyestuff', 'from', 'barbituric', 'acid', 'and', 'process', 'of', 'making', 'the', 'same']","[('Azo', 'NNP'), ('dyestuff', 'NN'), ('from', 'IN'), ('barbituric', 'JJ'), ('acid', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('process', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('making', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1606240A,1924-07-28,Angler's float,"[""Angler's"", 'float']","[(""Angler's"", 'NNP'), ('float', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1606263A,1926-05-21,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606320A,1924-08-23,Hose coupling,"['Hose', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'VBG')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1606330A,1926-11-09,Edward b,"['Edward', 'b']","[('Edward', 'NNP'), ('b', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606395A,1925-02-11,Bottle stopper and process for producing the same,"['Bottle', 'stopper', 'and', 'process', 'for', 'producing', 'the', 'same']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('stopper', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('process', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('producing', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1606398A,1925-05-06,Marker for fur skins,"['Marker', 'for', 'fur', 'skins']","[('Marker', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('fur', 'NN'), ('skins', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1606449A,1925-04-14,Culinary signal utensil,"['Culinary', 'signal', 'utensil']","[('Culinary', 'JJ'), ('signal', 'NN'), ('utensil', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1606469A,1926-11-09,John s,"['John', 's']","[('John', 'NNP'), ('s', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606504A,1926-11-09,Edward l,"['Edward', 'l']","[('Edward', 'NNP'), ('l', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1606565A,1926-03-13,Clasp for wrist-watch bracelets and the like,"['Clasp', 'for', 'wrist-watch', 'bracelets', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Clasp', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('wrist-watch', 'JJ'), ('bracelets', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1606569A,1924-10-04,Jar wrench,"['Jar', 'wrench']","[('Jar', 'NNP'), ('wrench', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606593A,1926-01-18,Sprinkler top for containers,"['Sprinkler', 'top', 'for', 'containers']","[('Sprinkler', 'NNP'), ('top', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('containers', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1606613A,1925-02-24,Cotton chopper,"['Cotton', 'chopper']","[('Cotton', 'NNP'), ('chopper', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606615A,1926-02-05,Rod clamp,"['Rod', 'clamp']","[('Rod', 'NNP'), ('clamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1606622A,1926-04-02,Antiskid device or extricator,"['Antiskid', 'device', 'or', 'extricator']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('device', 'NN'), ('or', 'CC'), ('extricator', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1606689A,1926-11-09,John willabd bolte,"['John', 'willabd', 'bolte']","[('John', 'NNP'), ('willabd', 'NN'), ('bolte', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1606801A,1923-08-25,Switch mechanism,"['Switch', 'mechanism']","[('Switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606802A,1925-11-21,Glass cutter,"['Glass', 'cutter']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('cutter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1606838A,1925-04-22,Cigar and cigarette holder,"['Cigar', 'and', 'cigarette', 'holder']","[('Cigar', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('cigarette', 'NN'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1606893A,1923-09-15,Meter installation,"['Meter', 'installation']","[('Meter', 'NNP'), ('installation', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1606923A,1926-07-08,Tee mold,"['Tee', 'mold']","[('Tee', 'NNP'), ('mold', 'NN')]","['DET', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606934A,1925-09-21,Footboard brace,"['Footboard', 'brace']","[('Footboard', 'NNP'), ('brace', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1606942A,1925-09-16,Tail gate,"['Tail', 'gate']","[('Tail', 'NNP'), ('gate', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1606972A,1926-01-02,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607078A,1924-03-01,Glass-molding machine,"['Glass-molding', 'machine']","[('Glass-molding', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1607132A,1926-05-17,Cigar and cigarette holder,"['Cigar', 'and', 'cigarette', 'holder']","[('Cigar', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('cigarette', 'NN'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1607140A,1926-11-16,Keinhold h,"['Keinhold', 'h']","[('Keinhold', 'NNP'), ('h', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607184A,1924-10-08,Truss structure,"['Truss', 'structure']","[('Truss', 'NN'), ('structure', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1607209A,1925-02-05,Truss construction,"['Truss', 'construction']","[('Truss', 'NNP'), ('construction', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1607210A,1925-02-05,Truss construction,"['Truss', 'construction']","[('Truss', 'NNP'), ('construction', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1607211A,1925-02-24,Truss,['Truss'],"[('Truss', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607261A,1926-11-16,Walter s,"['Walter', 's']","[('Walter', 'NNP'), ('s', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607378A,1920-05-18,Gang lawn mower,"['Gang', 'lawn', 'mower']","[('Gang', 'NNP'), ('lawn', 'NN'), ('mower', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1607434A,1925-04-20,Antiskid mechanism,"['Antiskid', 'mechanism']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1607443A,1926-06-28,Lobster trap,"['Lobster', 'trap']","[('Lobster', 'NNP'), ('trap', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1607551A,1926-11-16,hew jeesey,"['hew', 'jeesey']","[('hew', 'NN'), ('jeesey', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607568A,1925-09-10,Yarn-dyed fabric and method of manufacturing the same,"['Yarn-dyed', 'fabric', 'and', 'method', 'of', 'manufacturing', 'the', 'same']","[('Yarn-dyed', 'JJ'), ('fabric', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('method', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('manufacturing', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US1607640A,1926-11-23,Heateb cowtbol,"['Heateb', 'cowtbol']","[('Heateb', 'NNP'), ('cowtbol', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607643A,1926-02-24,Glass-forming machine,"['Glass-forming', 'machine']","[('Glass-forming', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1607651A,1922-02-23,Glass-blowing machine,"['Glass-blowing', 'machine']","[('Glass-blowing', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1607656A,1924-11-18,Powder distributor,"['Powder', 'distributor']","[('Powder', 'NNP'), ('distributor', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1607709A,1925-02-04,Adjustable drill chuck,"['Adjustable', 'drill', 'chuck']","[('Adjustable', 'JJ'), ('drill', 'NN'), ('chuck', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1607727A,1925-04-15,Bottle rinser,"['Bottle', 'rinser']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('rinser', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1607758A,1926-11-23,John junkunc,"['John', 'junkunc']","[('John', 'NNP'), ('junkunc', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607761A,1925-07-20,Shaker screen,"['Shaker', 'screen']","[('Shaker', 'NNP'), ('screen', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1607765A,1924-10-22,Scoop,['Scoop'],"[('Scoop', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1607794A,1921-07-11,Chin rest for violins,"['Chin', 'rest', 'for', 'violins']","[('Chin', 'NNP'), ('rest', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('violins', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1607817A,1925-01-14,Glass containing germanium,"['Glass', 'containing', 'germanium']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('containing', 'VBG'), ('germanium', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1607819A,1922-02-20,Clasp for lingerie ribbons and the like,"['Clasp', 'for', 'lingerie', 'ribbons', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Clasp', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('lingerie', 'JJ'), ('ribbons', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1608067A,1925-05-21,Hose apparatus,"['Hose', 'apparatus']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1608071A,1922-01-31,Cigar-wrapping mechanism,"['Cigar-wrapping', 'mechanism']","[('Cigar-wrapping', 'JJ'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1608077A,1924-10-03,Antiskid tire,"['Antiskid', 'tire']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('tire', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1608113A,1924-05-15,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608194A,1922-11-06,Split-foot stocking-knitting machine,"['Split-foot', 'stocking-knitting', 'machine']","[('Split-foot', 'JJ'), ('stocking-knitting', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1608199A,1926-11-23,Said wilson,"['Said', 'wilson']","[('Said', 'NNP'), ('wilson', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1608257A,1925-01-02,Dimmer cap for headlight bulbs,"['Dimmer', 'cap', 'for', 'headlight', 'bulbs']","[('Dimmer', 'NNP'), ('cap', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('headlight', 'NN'), ('bulbs', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1608280A,1926-11-23,Antiskid bblt,"['Antiskid', 'bblt']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('bblt', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608364A,1925-03-30,Inside pipe wrench and nipple chuck,"['Inside', 'pipe', 'wrench', 'and', 'nipple', 'chuck']","[('Inside', 'NNP'), ('pipe', 'NN'), ('wrench', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('nipple', 'JJ'), ('chuck', 'NN')]","['ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1608386A,1926-07-15,Coupler shank and yoke connection,"['Coupler', 'shank', 'and', 'yoke', 'connection']","[('Coupler', 'NNP'), ('shank', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('yoke', 'NN'), ('connection', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1608411A,1926-11-23,Theopiiil joseph mateju,"['Theopiiil', 'joseph', 'mateju']","[('Theopiiil', 'NNP'), ('joseph', 'NN'), ('mateju', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1608462A,1921-07-08,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608463A,1923-03-23,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608464A,1923-03-23,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608518A,1926-11-30,William mineath,"['William', 'mineath']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('mineath', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608615A,1923-02-05,Cigarette dispenser and lighter,"['Cigarette', 'dispenser', 'and', 'lighter']","[('Cigarette', 'NNP'), ('dispenser', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('lighter', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1608619A,1923-09-28,Silencer,['Silencer'],"[('Silencer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608663A,1924-05-07,Boiler for heating systems,"['Boiler', 'for', 'heating', 'systems']","[('Boiler', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('heating', 'VBG'), ('systems', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1608710A,1922-10-14,Glass-feeding apparatus,"['Glass-feeding', 'apparatus']","[('Glass-feeding', 'JJ'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1608821A,1925-01-27,Playground plaything,"['Playground', 'plaything']","[('Playground', 'NN'), ('plaything', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1608826A,1926-11-30,Hotjse electeic,"['Hotjse', 'electeic']","[('Hotjse', 'NNP'), ('electeic', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608890A,1923-12-18,Pickproof cylinder lock,"['Pickproof', 'cylinder', 'lock']","[('Pickproof', 'NNP'), ('cylinder', 'NN'), ('lock', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1608927A,1924-10-09,Truss,['Truss'],"[('Truss', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1608941A,1924-09-27,Cap for flexible tubes,"['Cap', 'for', 'flexible', 'tubes']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('flexible', 'JJ'), ('tubes', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1609013A,1926-05-21,Blowgun,['Blowgun'],"[('Blowgun', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1609026A,1923-01-24,Billiard cue,"['Billiard', 'cue']","[('Billiard', 'NNP'), ('cue', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609087A,1926-05-13,Carpenter's bench vise,"[""Carpenter's"", 'bench', 'vise']","[(""Carpenter's"", 'NNP'), ('bench', 'NN'), ('vise', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1609114A,1925-03-18,Culinary utensil,"['Culinary', 'utensil']","[('Culinary', 'JJ'), ('utensil', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609143A,1924-09-12,Jacquard for circular-knitting machines,"['Jacquard', 'for', 'circular-knitting', 'machines']","[('Jacquard', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('circular-knitting', 'JJ'), ('machines', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1609176A,1924-02-04,Dimmer switch,"['Dimmer', 'switch']","[('Dimmer', 'NNP'), ('switch', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1609184A,1925-08-05,Windmill wheel,"['Windmill', 'wheel']","[('Windmill', 'NNP'), ('wheel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609250A,1924-09-23,Pull rod pump jack,"['Pull', 'rod', 'pump', 'jack']","[('Pull', 'NNP'), ('rod', 'NN'), ('pump', 'NN'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1609261A,1926-06-07,Whistle,['Whistle'],"[('Whistle', 'VB')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1609329A,1923-10-10,Glass composition,"['Glass', 'composition']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('composition', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1609333A,1925-04-27,Garage jack,"['Garage', 'jack']","[('Garage', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1609359A,1926-12-07,humphrey,['humphrey'],"[('humphrey', 'NN')]",['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1609454A,1926-12-07,barratt,['barratt'],"[('barratt', 'NN')]",['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1609553A,1924-08-04,Cigar lighter,"['Cigar', 'lighter']","[('Cigar', 'NNP'), ('lighter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609606A,1925-08-25,Thermometer fitting,"['Thermometer', 'fitting']","[('Thermometer', 'NN'), ('fitting', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609622A,1925-03-18,Hose supporter,"['Hose', 'supporter']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('supporter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609623A,1925-03-18,Hose supporter,"['Hose', 'supporter']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('supporter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1609677A,1925-05-25,Swimmer's safety belt,"[""Swimmer's"", 'safety', 'belt']","[(""Swimmer's"", 'NNP'), ('safety', 'NN'), ('belt', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1609691A,1922-07-15,Glass-working apparatus,"['Glass-working', 'apparatus']","[('Glass-working', 'JJ'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1609707A,1924-07-17,Glass mold,"['Glass', 'mold']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('mold', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1609715A,1926-06-21,Hatband,['Hatband'],"[('Hatband', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1609883A,1925-09-10,Windmill,['Windmill'],"[('Windmill', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1609886A,1923-06-29,Jack,['Jack'],"[('Jack', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1609915A,1926-01-28,Freezing apparatus,"['Freezing', 'apparatus']","[('Freezing', 'VBG'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1609965A,1926-12-07,Donald,['Donald'],"[('Donald', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610043A,1926-06-24,Eyeglass attachment,"['Eyeglass', 'attachment']","[('Eyeglass', 'NNP'), ('attachment', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1610053A,1926-05-15,Cotton and air separator,"['Cotton', 'and', 'air', 'separator']","[('Cotton', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('air', 'NN'), ('separator', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1610118A,1926-12-07,brockett,['brockett'],"[('brockett', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1610179A,1923-11-20,Flow meter and the like,"['Flow', 'meter', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Flow', 'NNP'), ('meter', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1610222A,1926-07-06,Cotton-hull separator,"['Cotton-hull', 'separator']","[('Cotton-hull', 'JJ'), ('separator', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1610266A,1926-08-14,Slicker,['Slicker'],"[('Slicker', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610292A,1925-09-11,Cigar and cigarette holder and protector,"['Cigar', 'and', 'cigarette', 'holder', 'and', 'protector']","[('Cigar', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('cigarette', 'NN'), ('holder', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('protector', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1610297A,1926-12-14,Vibkatoey convebtee,"['Vibkatoey', 'convebtee']","[('Vibkatoey', 'NNP'), ('convebtee', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610299A,1924-12-04,Truss,['Truss'],"[('Truss', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610304A,1926-04-24,Meter,['Meter'],"[('Meter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610432A,1923-09-08,Yarn reel or winder,"['Yarn', 'reel', 'or', 'winder']","[('Yarn', 'NNP'), ('reel', 'NN'), ('or', 'CC'), ('winder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1610445A,1926-12-14,William f,"['William', 'f']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('f', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610547A,1923-11-12,Glass-cutting device,"['Glass-cutting', 'device']","[('Glass-cutting', 'JJ'), ('device', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1610565A,1923-05-24,Meter structure,"['Meter', 'structure']","[('Meter', 'NN'), ('structure', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1610598A,1925-02-18,Collapsible lifting jack and bumper bracket for motor vehicles,"['Collapsible', 'lifting', 'jack', 'and', 'bumper', 'bracket', 'for', 'motor', 'vehicles']","[('Collapsible', 'JJ'), ('lifting', 'VBG'), ('jack', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('bumper', 'NN'), ('bracket', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('motor', 'NN'), ('vehicles', 'NNS')]","['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1610623A,1925-12-02,Tie-branding apparatus,"['Tie-branding', 'apparatus']","[('Tie-branding', 'JJ'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1610658A,1925-05-22,Glass-polishing apparatus,"['Glass-polishing', 'apparatus']","[('Glass-polishing', 'JJ'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1610662A,1925-12-01,Slip sheeter and drier,"['Slip', 'sheeter', 'and', 'drier']","[('Slip', 'NNP'), ('sheeter', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('drier', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1610729A,1926-12-14,Egbert elmee bakek,"['Egbert', 'elmee', 'bakek']","[('Egbert', 'NNP'), ('elmee', 'NN'), ('bakek', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1610745A,1926-02-20,Cap,['Cap'],"[('Cap', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1610753A,1925-12-31,Dispensing and display stand for wire or the like,"['Dispensing', 'and', 'display', 'stand', 'for', 'wire', 'or', 'the', 'like']","[('Dispensing', 'VBG'), ('and', 'CC'), ('display', 'NN'), ('stand', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('wire', 'NN'), ('or', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1610758A,1924-06-10,Shaft coupling or the like,"['Shaft', 'coupling', 'or', 'the', 'like']","[('Shaft', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'NN'), ('or', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1610763A,1923-11-23,Stereotyper's casting machine,"[""Stereotyper's"", 'casting', 'machine']","[(""Stereotyper's"", 'NNP'), ('casting', 'NN'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1610824A,1925-04-04,Bin,['Bin'],"[('Bin', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1611070A,1926-08-20,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1611113A,1926-06-02,Raker gauge and jointer,"['Raker', 'gauge', 'and', 'jointer']","[('Raker', 'NNP'), ('gauge', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('jointer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1611114A,1924-06-09,Windmill gearing and oiling system,"['Windmill', 'gearing', 'and', 'oiling', 'system']","[('Windmill', 'NNP'), ('gearing', 'VBG'), ('and', 'CC'), ('oiling', 'VBG'), ('system', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1611115A,1924-07-22,Windmill pull-out,"['Windmill', 'pull-out']","[('Windmill', 'NNP'), ('pull-out', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1611125A,1925-07-10,Truss,['Truss'],"[('Truss', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1611166A,1923-02-03,Cap-twisting machine,"['Cap-twisting', 'machine']","[('Cap-twisting', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1611286A,1925-01-26,Hose coupling,"['Hose', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'VBG')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1611289A,1924-10-09,Cartridge-feed device for automatic firearms,"['Cartridge-feed', 'device', 'for', 'automatic', 'firearms']","[('Cartridge-feed', 'JJ'), ('device', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('automatic', 'JJ'), ('firearms', 'NNS')]","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1611366A,1926-01-19,Tractor jack,"['Tractor', 'jack']","[('Tractor', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1611383A,1922-10-10,Traveler's check,"[""Traveler's"", 'check']","[(""Traveler's"", 'NNP'), ('check', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1611389A,1925-06-17,Pug mill,"['Pug', 'mill']","[('Pug', 'NNP'), ('mill', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1611391A,1925-08-04,Knob or handle lock,"['Knob', 'or', 'handle', 'lock']","[('Knob', 'NNP'), ('or', 'CC'), ('handle', 'VB'), ('lock', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1611415A,1926-12-21,cheney,['cheney'],"[('cheney', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1611417A,1926-04-08,Mill conveyer,"['Mill', 'conveyer']","[('Mill', 'NNP'), ('conveyer', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1611439A,1925-02-07,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1611475A,1922-03-23,Silencer,['Silencer'],"[('Silencer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1611548A,1925-06-10,Smelter-smoke precipitator and dust collector,"['Smelter-smoke', 'precipitator', 'and', 'dust', 'collector']","[('Smelter-smoke', 'NNP'), ('precipitator', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('dust', 'NN'), ('collector', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1611581A,1922-08-14,Eyeglass construction,"['Eyeglass', 'construction']","[('Eyeglass', 'NNP'), ('construction', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1611591A,1926-07-13,Stockman's stove,"[""Stockman's"", 'stove']","[(""Stockman's"", 'NNP'), ('stove', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1611607A,1925-09-12,Dimmer for headlights,"['Dimmer', 'for', 'headlights']","[('Dimmer', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('headlights', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1611703A,1924-12-05,Jack,['Jack'],"[('Jack', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1611760A,1925-07-23,Cotton and kapok bat for upholstery,"['Cotton', 'and', 'kapok', 'bat', 'for', 'upholstery']","[('Cotton', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('kapok', 'VB'), ('bat', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('upholstery', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US1611775A,1926-12-21,louis,['louis'],"[('louis', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1611780A,1926-05-28,Dispensing receptacle,"['Dispensing', 'receptacle']","[('Dispensing', 'VBG'), ('receptacle', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1611828A,1925-03-30,Shade-cord fastener,"['Shade-cord', 'fastener']","[('Shade-cord', 'NNP'), ('fastener', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1611833A,1922-07-28,Meter,['Meter'],"[('Meter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1611914A,1925-05-27,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612124A,1925-03-30,Hand jack,"['Hand', 'jack']","[('Hand', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1612144A,1925-02-18,Bottle cap and capping process,"['Bottle', 'cap', 'and', 'capping', 'process']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('cap', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('capping', 'NN'), ('process', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1612167A,1925-03-09,Dinitrobenzene pellet,"['Dinitrobenzene', 'pellet']","[('Dinitrobenzene', 'NNP'), ('pellet', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612183A,1925-03-26,Cleaner for gasoline-measuring tanks,"['Cleaner', 'for', 'gasoline-measuring', 'tanks']","[('Cleaner', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('gasoline-measuring', 'JJ'), ('tanks', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1612191A,1926-12-28,Spacing and pulling device for service cars,"['Spacing', 'and', 'pulling', 'device', 'for', 'service', 'cars']","[('Spacing', 'VBG'), ('and', 'CC'), ('pulling', 'VBG'), ('device', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('service', 'NN'), ('cars', 'NNS')]","['VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1612192A,1926-12-28,johnson,['johnson'],"[('johnson', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1612196A,1926-03-01,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612348A,1919-09-25,Switch box,"['Switch', 'box']","[('Switch', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612385A,1924-04-08,Tailor's transfer,"[""Tailor's"", 'transfer']","[(""Tailor's"", 'NNP'), ('transfer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1612416A,1925-04-04,Barber chair,"['Barber', 'chair']","[('Barber', 'NNP'), ('chair', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1612446A,1925-06-12,Jack handle,"['Jack', 'handle']","[('Jack', 'NNP'), ('handle', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1612478A,1924-10-31,Hoop coiler,"['Hoop', 'coiler']","[('Hoop', 'NNP'), ('coiler', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612511A,1925-06-03,Coat,['Coat'],"[('Coat', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1612584A,1922-09-30,Silencer for internal-combustion engines,"['Silencer', 'for', 'internal-combustion', 'engines']","[('Silencer', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('internal-combustion', 'NN'), ('engines', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1612606A,1926-07-12,Shears,['Shears'],"[('Shears', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1612694A,1923-05-02,Miner's lamp,"[""Miner's"", 'lamp']","[(""Miner's"", 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1612695A,1925-05-06,Miner's acetylene lamp,"[""Miner's"", 'acetylene', 'lamp']","[(""Miner's"", 'NNP'), ('acetylene', 'NN'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1612696A,1925-04-04,Airscrew,['Airscrew'],"[('Airscrew', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1612732A,1925-11-03,Cotton comber and cleaner,"['Cotton', 'comber', 'and', 'cleaner']","[('Cotton', 'NNP'), ('comber', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('cleaner', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1612852A,1924-12-05,Dimmer switch,"['Dimmer', 'switch']","[('Dimmer', 'NNP'), ('switch', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612886A,1925-12-03,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1612927A,1926-03-02,Bottle cap or closure,"['Bottle', 'cap', 'or', 'closure']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('cap', 'NN'), ('or', 'CC'), ('closure', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1612933A,1927-01-04,metzgar,['metzgar'],"[('metzgar', 'NN')]",['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US1613045A,1926-04-03,Scalp-treatment device,"['Scalp-treatment', 'device']","[('Scalp-treatment', 'JJ'), ('device', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1613046A,1921-10-24,Cigar-banding machine,"['Cigar-banding', 'machine']","[('Cigar-banding', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1613057A,1926-06-01,Load-bracing jack,"['Load-bracing', 'jack']","[('Load-bracing', 'JJ'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1613160A,1925-10-24,Sadiron holder,"['Sadiron', 'holder']","[('Sadiron', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613189A,1925-12-11,Trolley wheel,"['Trolley', 'wheel']","[('Trolley', 'NNP'), ('wheel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613221A,1927-01-04,cobiella y vasconcelos,"['cobiella', 'y', 'vasconcelos']","[('cobiella', 'NN'), ('y', 'NN'), ('vasconcelos', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613323A,1927-01-04,of albert lea,"['of', 'albert', 'lea']","[('of', 'IN'), ('albert', 'JJ'), ('lea', 'NN')]","['ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613346A,1923-05-31,Silencer for valve-in-head motors,"['Silencer', 'for', 'valve-in-head', 'motors']","[('Silencer', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('valve-in-head', 'JJ'), ('motors', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1613380A,1925-11-27,Card case,"['Card', 'case']","[('Card', 'NNP'), ('case', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1613411A,1922-10-30,Fertilizer distributor,"['Fertilizer', 'distributor']","[('Fertilizer', 'NNP'), ('distributor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613455A,1925-12-17,Trip head and rope attachment for hay carriers,"['Trip', 'head', 'and', 'rope', 'attachment', 'for', 'hay', 'carriers']","[('Trip', 'NNP'), ('head', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('rope', 'NN'), ('attachment', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('hay', 'NN'), ('carriers', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1613514A,1922-10-27,Dispensing cabinet,"['Dispensing', 'cabinet']","[('Dispensing', 'VBG'), ('cabinet', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1613561A,1923-12-21,Ethyl alcohol paint and varnish remover,"['Ethyl', 'alcohol', 'paint', 'and', 'varnish', 'remover']","[('Ethyl', 'NNP'), ('alcohol', 'NN'), ('paint', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('varnish', 'JJ'), ('remover', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1613601A,1925-10-30,Sluiceway construction,"['Sluiceway', 'construction']","[('Sluiceway', 'NNP'), ('construction', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613644A,1925-01-23,Hose and pipe coupling,"['Hose', 'and', 'pipe', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('pipe', 'NN'), ('coupling', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1613741A,1922-08-17,Amplifier,['Amplifier'],"[('Amplifier', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1613751A,1926-07-28,"Knob for bag fasteners, etc.","['Knob', 'for', 'bag', 'fasteners,', 'etc.']","[('Knob', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('bag', 'NN'), ('fasteners,', 'NN'), ('etc.', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'X', 'X', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1613765A,1924-08-29,Eyeglass construction,"['Eyeglass', 'construction']","[('Eyeglass', 'NNP'), ('construction', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1613799A,1924-11-12,Hose supporter,"['Hose', 'supporter']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('supporter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613816A,1925-03-30,Runner for turbines,"['Runner', 'for', 'turbines']","[('Runner', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('turbines', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1613919A,1924-02-08,Azo dyestuffs and process of making same,"['Azo', 'dyestuffs', 'and', 'process', 'of', 'making', 'same']","[('Azo', 'NNP'), ('dyestuffs', 'NNS'), ('and', 'CC'), ('process', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('making', 'VBG'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1613968A,1927-01-11,Charles lawrence stokes,"['Charles', 'lawrence', 'stokes']","[('Charles', 'NNP'), ('lawrence', 'NN'), ('stokes', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1613982A,1926-03-25,Whistle pin wheel,"['Whistle', 'pin', 'wheel']","[('Whistle', 'NNP'), ('pin', 'NN'), ('wheel', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1613983A,1925-11-02,Ruching forming and applying machine,"['Ruching', 'forming', 'and', 'applying', 'machine']","[('Ruching', 'VBG'), ('forming', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('applying', 'NN'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1614063A,1923-08-23,Sulphur compound and method of making the same,"['Sulphur', 'compound', 'and', 'method', 'of', 'making', 'the', 'same']","[('Sulphur', 'NNP'), ('compound', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('method', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('making', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1614067A,1925-01-29,Ampulla for injection liquids comprising separated compartments,"['Ampulla', 'for', 'injection', 'liquids', 'comprising', 'separated', 'compartments']","[('Ampulla', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('injection', 'NN'), ('liquids', 'NNS'), ('comprising', 'VBG'), ('separated', 'VBD'), ('compartments', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1614155A,1922-07-11,Trolley wheel,"['Trolley', 'wheel']","[('Trolley', 'NNP'), ('wheel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1614156A,1925-05-18,Meter-window structure,"['Meter-window', 'structure']","[('Meter-window', 'JJ'), ('structure', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1614188A,1925-01-08,Gang saw or other saw guide,"['Gang', 'saw', 'or', 'other', 'saw', 'guide']","[('Gang', 'NNP'), ('saw', 'VBD'), ('or', 'CC'), ('other', 'JJ'), ('saw', 'NN'), ('guide', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1614202A,1924-06-06,Frequency meter,"['Frequency', 'meter']","[('Frequency', 'NN'), ('meter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1614217A,1924-01-26,Flow meter and the like,"['Flow', 'meter', 'and', 'the', 'like']","[('Flow', 'NNP'), ('meter', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('the', 'DT'), ('like', 'JJ')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'INTJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1614243A,1925-07-13,Tailor's cutting knife,"[""Tailor's"", 'cutting', 'knife']","[(""Tailor's"", 'NNP'), ('cutting', 'VBG'), ('knife', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1614351A,1927-01-11,davis,['davis'],"[('davis', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1614358A,1927-01-11,Pierre albert gandillon,"['Pierre', 'albert', 'gandillon']","[('Pierre', 'NNP'), ('albert', 'NN'), ('gandillon', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1614410A,1923-07-14,Yarn rack for dyeing machines,"['Yarn', 'rack', 'for', 'dyeing', 'machines']","[('Yarn', 'NNP'), ('rack', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('dyeing', 'VBG'), ('machines', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1614467A,1921-08-10,Cap delivery and applying mechanism,"['Cap', 'delivery', 'and', 'applying', 'mechanism']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('delivery', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('applying', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1614502A,1927-01-18,Diamond sower,"['Diamond', 'sower']","[('Diamond', 'NN'), ('sower', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1614546A,1925-01-07,Multiplex telegraphy with magnitude discrimination,"['Multiplex', 'telegraphy', 'with', 'magnitude', 'discrimination']","[('Multiplex', 'NNP'), ('telegraphy', 'NN'), ('with', 'IN'), ('magnitude', 'NN'), ('discrimination', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1614610A,1922-11-21,Tongs or wrench,"['Tongs', 'or', 'wrench']","[('Tongs', 'NNS'), ('or', 'CC'), ('wrench', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1614632A,1926-04-26,Glass-forming machine,"['Glass-forming', 'machine']","[('Glass-forming', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1614647A,1924-12-12,Recooler,['Recooler'],"[('Recooler', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1614678A,1921-02-09,nelson,['nelson'],"[('nelson', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1614804A,1921-09-14,Windmill,['Windmill'],"[('Windmill', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1614843A,1925-01-31,Carton,['Carton'],"[('Carton', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1614848A,1923-07-16,Eyeglass construction,"['Eyeglass', 'construction']","[('Eyeglass', 'NNP'), ('construction', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1614883A,1927-01-18,Processes of making ethylene glycol monoalkyl ethers,"['Processes', 'of', 'making', 'ethylene', 'glycol', 'monoalkyl', 'ethers']","[('Processes', 'NNS'), ('of', 'IN'), ('making', 'VBG'), ('ethylene', 'JJ'), ('glycol', 'NN'), ('monoalkyl', 'NN'), ('ethers', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1614906A,1927-01-18,Egbert von lepel,"['Egbert', 'von', 'lepel']","[('Egbert', 'NNP'), ('von', 'NNP'), ('lepel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1614936A,1922-06-12,Glass feeder,"['Glass', 'feeder']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('feeder', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1614972A,1926-07-31,Carton,['Carton'],"[('Carton', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1614986A,1927-01-18,John victoe howey,"['John', 'victoe', 'howey']","[('John', 'NNP'), ('victoe', 'NN'), ('howey', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1615040A,1925-08-13,Cap-feeding appliance,"['Cap-feeding', 'appliance']","[('Cap-feeding', 'JJ'), ('appliance', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1615045A,1921-04-11,Truss,['Truss'],"[('Truss', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1615142A,1926-04-30,Hose clamp,"['Hose', 'clamp']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('clamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1615150A,1923-02-24,Breaker and stopper extractor,"['Breaker', 'and', 'stopper', 'extractor']","[('Breaker', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('stopper', 'JJR'), ('extractor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1615154A,1926-04-08,Antiskid device,"['Antiskid', 'device']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('device', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1615159A,1924-10-31,Knapsacklike carrying frame and camp stool,"['Knapsacklike', 'carrying', 'frame', 'and', 'camp', 'stool']","[('Knapsacklike', 'IN'), ('carrying', 'VBG'), ('frame', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('camp', 'NN'), ('stool', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1615181A,1925-07-31,Meter lock cock,"['Meter', 'lock', 'cock']","[('Meter', 'NNP'), ('lock', 'NN'), ('cock', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1615196A,1924-07-18,Jar opener,"['Jar', 'opener']","[('Jar', 'NNP'), ('opener', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1615247A,1922-11-02,Glass composition,"['Glass', 'composition']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('composition', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1615332A,1926-01-25,Label holder,"['Label', 'holder']","[('Label', 'NNP'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1615448A,1925-07-06,Ray-filter glass,"['Ray-filter', 'glass']","[('Ray-filter', 'JJ'), ('glass', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1615506A,1925-12-08,Cap attachment for fountain pens,"['Cap', 'attachment', 'for', 'fountain', 'pens']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('attachment', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('fountain', 'NN'), ('pens', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1615533A,1925-10-05,Cap for receptacles,"['Cap', 'for', 'receptacles']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('receptacles', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1615595A,1925-02-12,Hose coupling,"['Hose', 'coupling']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('coupling', 'VBG')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1615704A,1921-03-23,Meter-testing-switch mechanism,"['Meter-testing-switch', 'mechanism']","[('Meter-testing-switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1615817A,1920-09-08,Switch box,"['Switch', 'box']","[('Switch', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1615820A,1925-08-25,Windmill attachment,"['Windmill', 'attachment']","[('Windmill', 'NNP'), ('attachment', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1615832A,1923-08-18,Glass-melting tank,"['Glass-melting', 'tank']","[('Glass-melting', 'NNP'), ('tank', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1615833A,1924-12-31,Glass-grinding process and apparatus,"['Glass-grinding', 'process', 'and', 'apparatus']","[('Glass-grinding', 'JJ'), ('process', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('apparatus', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1615870A,1927-02-01,Arthur w,"['Arthur', 'w']","[('Arthur', 'NNP'), ('w', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1615882A,1926-01-18,Shears,['Shears'],"[('Shears', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1615978A,1923-09-14,Glass-cutting machine,"['Glass-cutting', 'machine']","[('Glass-cutting', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1615998A,1921-02-09,nelson,['nelson'],"[('nelson', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1616025A,1924-03-17,Keyboard,['Keyboard'],"[('Keyboard', 'NNP')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616042A,1927-02-01,Hami to chii,"['Hami', 'to', 'chii']","[('Hami', 'NNP'), ('to', 'TO'), ('chii', 'VB')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1616060A,1925-05-16,Diamond gauge,"['Diamond', 'gauge']","[('Diamond', 'NNP'), ('gauge', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1616098A,1926-05-14,Meter case,"['Meter', 'case']","[('Meter', 'NNP'), ('case', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1616103A,1927-02-01,James hill,"['James', 'hill']","[('James', 'NNP'), ('hill', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616173A,1925-11-04,Dashboard attachment for cigar lighters,"['Dashboard', 'attachment', 'for', 'cigar', 'lighters']","[('Dashboard', 'NNP'), ('attachment', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('cigar', 'NN'), ('lighters', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1616261A,1926-06-09,Harrow,['Harrow'],"[('Harrow', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616282A,1927-02-01,Kabl schbanz,"['Kabl', 'schbanz']","[('Kabl', 'NNP'), ('schbanz', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616298A,1925-08-14,Meter-box lid and lock therefor,"['Meter-box', 'lid', 'and', 'lock', 'therefor']","[('Meter-box', 'NNP'), ('lid', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('lock', 'NN'), ('therefor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1616308A,1925-09-05,Glass-molding machine,"['Glass-molding', 'machine']","[('Glass-molding', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1616321A,1927-02-01,John j,"['John', 'j']","[('John', 'NNP'), ('j', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616360A,1927-02-01,William foster,"['William', 'foster']","[('William', 'NNP'), ('foster', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616396A,1925-11-30,Cigar or cigarette holder,"['Cigar', 'or', 'cigarette', 'holder']","[('Cigar', 'NNP'), ('or', 'CC'), ('cigarette', 'NN'), ('holder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1616414A,1927-02-01,Assichstob to wieed badio,"['Assichstob', 'to', 'wieed', 'badio']","[('Assichstob', 'NNP'), ('to', 'TO'), ('wieed', 'VB'), ('badio', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1616539A,1923-07-26,Cigar-banding machine,"['Cigar-banding', 'machine']","[('Cigar-banding', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1616561A,1927-02-08,van ackeren,"['van', 'ackeren']","[('van', 'NN'), ('ackeren', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616605A,1924-12-12,Glass-container box car,"['Glass-container', 'box', 'car']","[('Glass-container', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN'), ('car', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1616614A,1927-02-08,Egbert edwardson,"['Egbert', 'edwardson']","[('Egbert', 'NNP'), ('edwardson', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1616695A,1927-02-08,Kelson littell,"['Kelson', 'littell']","[('Kelson', 'NNP'), ('littell', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616698A,1927-02-08,David miller,"['David', 'miller']","[('David', 'NNP'), ('miller', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616743A,1922-12-29,Scaffold,['Scaffold'],"[('Scaffold', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1616750A,1923-11-03,Glass hopper,"['Glass', 'hopper']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('hopper', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1616851A,1926-02-10,Cigar,['Cigar'],"[('Cigar', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1616859A,1925-05-11,Capo tasto,"['Capo', 'tasto']","[('Capo', 'NNP'), ('tasto', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1616886A,1924-10-14,Jockey-arch disk adjustment,"['Jockey-arch', 'disk', 'adjustment']","[('Jockey-arch', 'JJ'), ('disk', 'NN'), ('adjustment', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1616969A,1926-02-24,Printer's chase for storage,"[""Printer's"", 'chase', 'for', 'storage']","[(""Printer's"", 'NNP'), ('chase', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('storage', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1617061A,1926-05-29,Bather's safety appliance,"[""Bather's"", 'safety', 'appliance']","[(""Bather's"", 'NNP'), ('safety', 'NN'), ('appliance', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1617085A,1926-08-20,Trolley wheel,"['Trolley', 'wheel']","[('Trolley', 'NNP'), ('wheel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617093A,1927-02-08,Howard d,"['Howard', 'd']","[('Howard', 'NNP'), ('d', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617106A,1924-02-04,Glass-grinding machine,"['Glass-grinding', 'machine']","[('Glass-grinding', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1617120A,1925-06-25,Culinary utensil,"['Culinary', 'utensil']","[('Culinary', 'JJ'), ('utensil', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617228A,1924-08-25,Fertilizer distributor,"['Fertilizer', 'distributor']","[('Fertilizer', 'NNP'), ('distributor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617239A,1926-04-14,Shield-lifting mechanism for cultivators,"['Shield-lifting', 'mechanism', 'for', 'cultivators']","[('Shield-lifting', 'JJ'), ('mechanism', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('cultivators', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1617347A,1924-11-20,Stationary yarn guide for weaving looms,"['Stationary', 'yarn', 'guide', 'for', 'weaving', 'looms']","[('Stationary', 'NNP'), ('yarn', 'NNP'), ('guide', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('weaving', 'VBG'), ('looms', 'NNS')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1617363A,1923-02-20,Switch mechanism,"['Switch', 'mechanism']","[('Switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1617385A,1926-04-10,Windmill,['Windmill'],"[('Windmill', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617406A,1924-11-21,Meter-operated circuit closer,"['Meter-operated', 'circuit', 'closer']","[('Meter-operated', 'JJ'), ('circuit', 'NN'), ('closer', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1617407A,1926-02-04,Meter,['Meter'],"[('Meter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617423A,1923-03-26,Vehicle lamp,"['Vehicle', 'lamp']","[('Vehicle', 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617456A,1923-11-17,Carboy bottle,"['Carboy', 'bottle']","[('Carboy', 'NNP'), ('bottle', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617461A,1926-01-25,Shears for rice straw,"['Shears', 'for', 'rice', 'straw']","[('Shears', 'NNS'), ('for', 'IN'), ('rice', 'NN'), ('straw', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1617472A,1924-09-03,Carton,['Carton'],"[('Carton', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617477A,1924-01-14,Spring jack,"['Spring', 'jack']","[('Spring', 'NN'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617481A,1922-06-20,Detachable connecter for hose supporters,"['Detachable', 'connecter', 'for', 'hose', 'supporters']","[('Detachable', 'JJ'), ('connecter', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('hose', 'JJ'), ('supporters', 'NNS')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1617672A,1925-10-15,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617677A,1927-02-15,Assickctob,['Assickctob'],"[('Assickctob', 'NN')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1617745A,1927-02-15,Albert cotysinard,"['Albert', 'cotysinard']","[('Albert', 'NNP'), ('cotysinard', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617753A,1926-06-22,Vehicle jack,"['Vehicle', 'jack']","[('Vehicle', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617848A,1926-05-15,Stuffer horn,"['Stuffer', 'horn']","[('Stuffer', 'NNP'), ('horn', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617896A,1925-08-28,Laundry collar-finishing machine,"['Laundry', 'collar-finishing', 'machine']","[('Laundry', 'JJ'), ('collar-finishing', 'NN'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1617932A,1926-06-15,Meter and meter-reading device,"['Meter', 'and', 'meter-reading', 'device']","[('Meter', 'NNP'), ('and', 'CC'), ('meter-reading', 'JJ'), ('device', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1617935A,1925-01-07,Multiplex telegraphy by phase discrimination,"['Multiplex', 'telegraphy', 'by', 'phase', 'discrimination']","[('Multiplex', 'NNP'), ('telegraphy', 'NN'), ('by', 'IN'), ('phase', 'NN'), ('discrimination', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1617952A,1922-08-23,Rod packing,"['Rod', 'packing']","[('Rod', 'NNP'), ('packing', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1617997A,1925-05-22,Harrow,['Harrow'],"[('Harrow', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1617998A,1925-11-25,Chuck,['Chuck'],"[('Chuck', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618097A,1926-03-22,Pan,['Pan'],"[('Pan', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618103A,1920-05-17,Searchlight,['Searchlight'],"[('Searchlight', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618138A,1926-05-01,Label folding and packing machine,"['Label', 'folding', 'and', 'packing', 'machine']","[('Label', 'NNP'), ('folding', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('packing', 'NN'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1618156A,1925-11-16,Antiskid device,"['Antiskid', 'device']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('device', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1618161A,1923-06-07,Antiskid device for automobiles,"['Antiskid', 'device', 'for', 'automobiles']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('device', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('automobiles', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1618232A,1923-08-02,Oil-well jack,"['Oil-well', 'jack']","[('Oil-well', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1618260A,1925-11-02,Laundry assorter,"['Laundry', 'assorter']","[('Laundry', 'NNP'), ('assorter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1618261A,1927-02-22,Viscera retainer for use in abdominal operations,"['Viscera', 'retainer', 'for', 'use', 'in', 'abdominal', 'operations']","[('Viscera', 'NNP'), ('retainer', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('use', 'NN'), ('in', 'IN'), ('abdominal', 'JJ'), ('operations', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1618313A,1924-03-03,Glass feeder,"['Glass', 'feeder']","[('Glass', 'NNP'), ('feeder', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1618355A,1926-01-15,Dimmer control for headlights,"['Dimmer', 'control', 'for', 'headlights']","[('Dimmer', 'NNP'), ('control', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('headlights', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1618370A,1927-02-22,Max engelmann,"['Max', 'engelmann']","[('Max', 'NNP'), ('engelmann', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618393A,1924-03-21,"Cap for covering the opening ends of jars, cans, etc.","['Cap', 'for', 'covering', 'the', 'opening', 'ends', 'of', 'jars,', 'cans,', 'etc.']","[('Cap', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('covering', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('opening', 'NN'), ('ends', 'VBZ'), ('of', 'IN'), ('jars,', 'NN'), ('cans,', 'NN'), ('etc.', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'X', 'X', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US1618401A,1924-02-11,Cargo fleet for water navigation and method of operating said fleet,"['Cargo', 'fleet', 'for', 'water', 'navigation', 'and', 'method', 'of', 'operating', 'said', 'fleet']","[('Cargo', 'NNP'), ('fleet', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('water', 'NN'), ('navigation', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('method', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('operating', 'NN'), ('said', 'VBD'), ('fleet', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1618406A,1926-06-28,Vulcanizer for pneumatic tubes,"['Vulcanizer', 'for', 'pneumatic', 'tubes']","[('Vulcanizer', 'NNP'), ('for', 'IN'), ('pneumatic', 'JJ'), ('tubes', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1618435A,1926-08-04,Hose supporter,"['Hose', 'supporter']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('supporter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1618438A,1925-12-30,Coat collar and method of forming the same,"['Coat', 'collar', 'and', 'method', 'of', 'forming', 'the', 'same']","[('Coat', 'NNP'), ('collar', 'NN'), ('and', 'CC'), ('method', 'NN'), ('of', 'IN'), ('forming', 'VBG'), ('the', 'DT'), ('same', 'JJ')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1618480A,1927-02-22,Cap wrench,"['Cap', 'wrench']","[('Cap', 'NNP'), ('wrench', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618549A,1926-02-20,Windmill,['Windmill'],"[('Windmill', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618578A,1927-02-22,Robert t,"['Robert', 't']","[('Robert', 'NNP'), ('t', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1618608A,1927-02-22,William,['William'],"[('William', 'NNP')]",['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1618817A,1926-06-18,Shears,['Shears'],"[('Shears', 'NNS')]","['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US1618868A,1923-12-21,Ethyl acetate varnish remover,"['Ethyl', 'acetate', 'varnish', 'remover']","[('Ethyl', 'NNP'), ('acetate', 'VBP'), ('varnish', 'JJ'), ('remover', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1618879A,1925-07-11,Bottle capper,"['Bottle', 'capper']","[('Bottle', 'NNP'), ('capper', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1618910A,1926-06-19,Hose supporter,"['Hose', 'supporter']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('supporter', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1618977A,1925-01-05,Capped swab or dauber,"['Capped', 'swab', 'or', 'dauber']","[('Capped', 'NNP'), ('swab', 'NN'), ('or', 'CC'), ('dauber', 'VB')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,1,5
US1619030A,1926-05-26,Masonry jointing tool,"['Masonry', 'jointing', 'tool']","[('Masonry', 'NNP'), ('jointing', 'NN'), ('tool', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1619109A,1920-07-07,Thermometer,['Thermometer'],"[('Thermometer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1619133A,1922-01-07,Blade fastening,"['Blade', 'fastening']","[('Blade', 'NNP'), ('fastening', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619231A,1923-09-12,Vulcanizer,['Vulcanizer'],"[('Vulcanizer', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1619242A,1926-10-21,Lingerie clasp,"['Lingerie', 'clasp']","[('Lingerie', 'NNP'), ('clasp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619287A,1923-08-10,Hose-repair clamp,"['Hose-repair', 'clamp']","[('Hose-repair', 'NN'), ('clamp', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1619307A,1923-08-02,Shelf,['Shelf'],"[('Shelf', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1619315A,1926-10-29,Dispensing receptacle,"['Dispensing', 'receptacle']","[('Dispensing', 'VBG'), ('receptacle', 'NN')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1619439A,1925-02-10,Hose connection,"['Hose', 'connection']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('connection', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619463A,1918-06-04,Boiler baffle,"['Boiler', 'baffle']","[('Boiler', 'NNP'), ('baffle', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1619499A,1924-05-22,Continuous lath-expanding machine,"['Continuous', 'lath-expanding', 'machine']","[('Continuous', 'JJ'), ('lath-expanding', 'JJ'), ('machine', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1619543A,1925-05-08,Bill folder,"['Bill', 'folder']","[('Bill', 'NNP'), ('folder', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619592A,1926-03-31,Antiskid chain,"['Antiskid', 'chain']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('chain', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619622A,1925-09-22,Cigarette box,"['Cigarette', 'box']","[('Cigarette', 'NNP'), ('box', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619640A,1920-06-24,Explosionproof fuse,"['Explosionproof', 'fuse']","[('Explosionproof', 'NNP'), ('fuse', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1619648A,1922-05-11,Method of incorporating a. shank stiffener with a shoe sole,"['Method', 'of', 'incorporating', 'a.', 'shank', 'stiffener', 'with', 'a', 'shoe', 'sole']","[('Method', 'NNP'), ('of', 'IN'), ('incorporating', 'VBG'), ('a.', 'NN'), ('shank', 'VBD'), ('stiffener', 'NN'), ('with', 'IN'), ('a', 'DT'), ('shoe', 'NN'), ('sole', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US1619664A,1927-03-01,And william h,"['And', 'william', 'h']","[('And', 'CC'), ('william', 'NN'), ('h', 'NN')]","['CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619766A,1923-07-20,Hose clamping tool,"['Hose', 'clamping', 'tool']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('clamping', 'VBG'), ('tool', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1619795A,1924-12-01,Fertilizer distributor,"['Fertilizer', 'distributor']","[('Fertilizer', 'NNP'), ('distributor', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619841A,1923-09-26,Hose clamp,"['Hose', 'clamp']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('clamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1619989A,1923-10-17,Kniff glue clamp,"['Kniff', 'glue', 'clamp']","[('Kniff', 'NNP'), ('glue', 'NN'), ('clamp', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1620009A,1926-12-07,Pump jack,"['Pump', 'jack']","[('Pump', 'NNP'), ('jack', 'NN')]","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1620019A,1925-03-11,Beet harvester,"['Beet', 'harvester']","[('Beet', 'NNP'), ('harvester', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1620076A,1926-03-05,Antiskid chain for tires,"['Antiskid', 'chain', 'for', 'tires']","[('Antiskid', 'NNP'), ('chain', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('tires', 'NNS')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1620114A,1922-01-23,Hose fitting,"['Hose', 'fitting']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('fitting', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1620145A,1924-08-04,Windmill,['Windmill'],"[('Windmill', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1620160A,1925-08-05,Hose or sock,"['Hose', 'or', 'sock']","[('Hose', 'NNP'), ('or', 'CC'), ('sock', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1620167A,1922-02-13,Switch mechanism,"['Switch', 'mechanism']","[('Switch', 'NN'), ('mechanism', 'NN')]","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1620174A,1920-05-20,Carton,['Carton'],"[('Carton', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1620176A,1926-02-19,Dobby finger for looms,"['Dobby', 'finger', 'for', 'looms']","[('Dobby', 'NNP'), ('finger', 'NN'), ('for', 'IN'), ('looms', 'NNS')]","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1620202A,1921-07-29,Vehicle lamp,"['Vehicle', 'lamp']","[('Vehicle', 'NNP'), ('lamp', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1620203A,1924-01-28,Trolley wheel,"['Trolley', 'wheel']","[('Trolley', 'NNP'), ('wheel', 'NN')]","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
