patent_number,date,title,spacy_pos,spacy_label,is_prpn_spacy,is_person_spacy,spacy_pos_len
US3100016A,1960-10-24,Rod centralizer,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3100033A,1960-03-04,Jack rod support,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3100074A,1962-10-05,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3100091A,1961-03-20,Yarn tensioning device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3100150A,1960-11-02,"Stencil screen coating comprising polyvinyl alcohol, polyvinyl acetate, and a light sensitizing agent","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'GPE']",1,1,16
US3100186A,1960-06-24,Method of making lamellar sheets of fluorphlogopite mica,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3100222A,1958-12-19,"Alkoxyalkyl 3,4-dichlorocarbanilates","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3100263A,1962-02-21,Continuous rotation scattering chamber,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3100374A,1962-07-11,Traveler ring assemblies,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3100415A,1955-10-14,Piano case,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3100428A,1960-11-14,Knob for setting diaphragm aperture on camera equipped with exposure meter,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3100543A,1957-03-08,Drill bit for cutting cores,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3100584A,1959-10-07,Dispensing machine operating on volumetric principle,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3100623A,1961-04-04,Mold positioning jack for horizontal injection molding machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3100629A,1957-06-13,Continuous mining machine having lateral levelling means,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3100630A,1963-08-13,kqmmel,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3100650A,1961-03-01,Percussion drill chuck,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3100662A,1961-04-03,Sucker rod safety joint,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3100768A,1958-08-11,Azo dyestuffs,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3100976A,1960-02-16,Yarn severing device for a circular knitting machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3100977A,1960-02-15,Yarn severing device for circular knitting machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3101007A,1957-01-19,"Knob arrangement, particularly for motor vehicles","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3101147A,1961-05-17,Glass container inspecting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3101196A,1961-09-18,Bowler's posture corrective apparatus,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3101268A,1959-06-26,Continuous process for reducing iron ores,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3101299A,1960-11-17,Silica-gel powder tablet compositions,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3101337A,1963-08-20,Hsc chz chz,"['PROPN', 'X', 'X']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3101398A,1960-11-14,Fuse holders for electric circuits,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3101450A,1955-03-30,Amplifier comprising time dependent reactors,"['ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3101460A,1957-05-07,Hermetically sealed waveguide window with non-sputtering iris,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3101566A,1961-11-30,Vacuum cup holding device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3101567A,1961-11-30,Vacuum cup holding device having improved holding means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3101611A,1960-07-20,Analyzer for internal combustion engines,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3101616A,1959-05-08,Volumetric positive displacement flow meter,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3101745A,1960-02-12,Dobby for a weaving machine,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3101746A,1960-02-12,Dobby,['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3101892A,1960-12-01,Bill-receiving cash boxes,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3101995A,1960-09-28,Continuous treatment of food containers,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3102016A,1956-12-07,Glass bending method,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3102067A,1960-06-20,Vinyl phosphates,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3102111A,1959-08-17,Azo sulfonamide derivatives,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3102140A,1961-02-27,Quaternary ammonium superoxide compounds and their preparation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3102178A,1960-06-29,Fuse tube construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3102213A,1960-05-13,Multiplanar printed circuits and methods for their manufacture,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3102233A,1961-07-14,Galvanometer with discrete liquid globule damping means,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3102236A,1960-05-05,Squelch circuit controlled by demodulated voice signal,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3102329A,1958-12-12,Sinter electrode,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3102405A,1961-02-20,Yarn lever control mechanism,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3102430A,1960-05-20,Gyroscope,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3102566A,1960-12-23,Blade control mechanism for citrus fruit sectionizing machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3102674A,1962-01-18,Strawberry tray,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3102675A,1961-06-29,Dispensing carton,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3102691A,1962-06-05,Hose nozzle,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3102702A,1960-03-07,Yarn retaining device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3102746A,1960-11-18,Dowel pin,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3102842A,1962-03-19,Dialkyl alpha-(trihalophenyl)-beta-(halo)-vinyl phosphates,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3102987A,1960-09-12,Tuner having variable capacitance diode and saturable inductor varied together by potentiometer tap movement and varied oppositely by battery drift,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,21
US3102988A,1961-09-12,Split core transformer with remotely actuated mounting structure,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3103044A,1959-07-09,Mould stripping machine,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3103048A,1961-04-25,Buckles for automobile safety belts and the like,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3103097A,1959-11-28,Yarn twisting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3103221A,1960-04-06,Cigarette filter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3103256A,1959-11-09,Silencer or muffler,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3103433A,1963-09-10,Boron trifluoride s,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3103452A,1960-02-24,Milton comanor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3103475A,1963-09-10,Szilard,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3103550A,1963-09-10,Ellett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3103564A,1963-09-10,Solenoid switch operating mechanism,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3103573A,1963-09-10,Liter,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3103577A,1959-07-13,willard,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3103609A,1963-09-10,zitelli,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3103612A,1963-09-10,Solenoid operated valve,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3103615A,1961-05-17,Amplifier and two-phase motor control circuit,"['ADV', 'CCONJ', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,9
US3103772A,1961-03-22,Cigar packaging machines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3103816A,1960-11-25,Cap and gauge structure for crankcase fill opening,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3103839A,1963-09-17,Mancuso,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3103884A,1962-03-16,Cartridge for more nearly uniform projectile velocities,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3104034A,1960-10-24,Cap construction for aerosol devices,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3104035A,1961-10-25,Bin closure assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3104081A,1959-11-27,Solenoid operated three-position pneumatic actuator,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,8
US3104135A,1960-02-26,Bimetallic bearing structure and method for producing same,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3104248A,1960-12-30,Acetatozirconyl halides,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3104345A,1961-12-07,Plasma generator for a highly ionized electrical plasma,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3104372A,1961-02-02,Multilevel quantizing for character readers,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3104409A,1960-10-21,Boiler tube scale remover,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3104419A,1962-08-24,Spinneret pack,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3104444A,1961-12-12,Tenter clip gate,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3104447A,1960-02-01,Corpse hand securing method,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3104448A,1961-09-21,Mortician's body cavity injector,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3104467A,1961-04-10,"Glass cutting guides, gauges and jigs","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3104523A,1959-10-01,Rigid cellular propellent supports,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3104583A,1960-10-31,Screw connection having coil spring thread means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3104595A,1961-04-24,Swab cup structures,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3104740A,1963-09-24,Koffler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104767A,1963-09-24,Bassett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104768A,1963-09-24,Bassett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104797A,1963-09-24,Langenfeld,['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3104822A,1963-09-24,muschett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104854A,1963-09-24,von saurma,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3104881A,1963-09-24,Ferris,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104886A,1963-09-24,Chuck,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104892A,1963-09-24,graham,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104894A,1963-09-24,henry,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3104905A,1961-02-09,Ttnttpn,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3104967A,1956-11-13,Glass furnace bubbler patterns,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3105071A,1962-06-01,"Nitro 2-oxo-2h-1, 4 benzoxazines","['PROPN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,8
US3105085A,1961-07-21,"Bissil ylcyclohexandienes, their preparation and use","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3105171A,1960-07-08,High voltage d. c. transmission systems,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3105202A,1961-05-25,Amplifier with regulated output level,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3105340A,1962-07-13,Cotton recovering machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3105386A,1961-06-20,Solenoid operated actuator device,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3105418A,1961-04-03,Carton gluing and forming machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3105440A,1960-01-29,Fuse,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3105449A,1961-03-16,Zigzag actuating mechanism for sewing machines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3105497A,1959-03-13,Cigar making machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3105611A,1962-06-19,Cartridge carrier and dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3105625A,1961-11-16,Rod mill loop control by imaging loop on differential detector system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3105655A,1958-07-17,Yarn spool,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3105663A,1962-04-16,Kite trolley,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3105880A,1960-09-14,Ikuro,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3105889A,1957-08-17,Bimetallic starter switch for gas discharge tubes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3105944A,1961-06-29,Bridge type d. c. to a. c. inverter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,9
US3105947A,1960-03-11,"Wavemeter having strip-line resonator capacitively coupled to feed, with movable dielectric effectively varying resonator length","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,19
US3105950A,1960-04-19,Bandwidth compression system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3105996A,1960-12-19,Sliver coiler,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3106006A,1961-07-24,Troweler,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3106101A,1960-12-06,Split sprocket,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3106131A,1961-05-24,Cartridge actuated device,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3106152A,1961-10-18,Continuous fruit press,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3106270A,1960-12-08,Cap construction for building columns,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3106377A,1961-01-31,Lashing anchorage for freight stowage compartments of aircraft and other vehicles,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3106464A,1958-02-18,Glass sheet bending apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3106535A,1959-08-24,Neutron radiation shielding material,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3106536A,1960-03-21,Epoxy esters of polyhalopolycyclic acids,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3106537A,1959-01-19,"Cellular reaction product of alkyd resin, polyhydric alcohol and arylene polyisocyanate and method of preparation","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3106555A,1960-09-02,"Novel amino chlorosulfenyl-s-triazines, their hydrochlorides and process for their production","['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3106681A,1961-03-06,R. f. amplifier automatic frequency tuning,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3106682A,1960-08-01,Current peaked pulse generator providing switched d. c. potential of a charged capacitor through an rlc circuit,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,18
US3106684A,1960-07-15,Amplifier with interrupted positive feedback,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3106761A,1959-08-03,Mounting means for tenter pin plates,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3106764A,1959-04-20,Continuous process for producing semiconductor devices,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3106780A,1961-02-08,Glass container inspecting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3106793A,1962-03-19,Bulldozer blade structure,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3106820A,1959-01-19,Afterburner control method and apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3107067A,1958-06-25,Slip sleeve textile bobbin,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3107138A,1957-08-30,Oscillograph containing a silver halide recording medium plus heat sensitive or fluorescent material,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3107228A,1956-12-12,Polypropylene containing a dye-receptive modifier which comprises polyal-kyleneimine or mixztures thereof with an epoxy resin,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,20
US3107253A,1961-10-12,Epoxy acetals,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3107344A,1959-09-29,Self-synchronizing delay line data translation,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3107386A,1960-05-05,Cleaner nozzle with pulsating jet,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3107450A,1961-05-19,Glass fiber sight rib for firearm barrels having an outer jacket of glass fibers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3107455A,1962-10-29,Continuous metal cleaning apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3107473A,1959-11-06,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3107485A,1959-05-27,Propulsion means and method for space vehicles employing a volatile alkene and metalcarbonyl,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3107528A,1960-03-10,Meter for registering selected-rate flow volume,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3107540A,1961-12-04,Gyroscope pickoff and torquer,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,5
US3107613A,1961-02-17,Boron compound,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3107734A,1961-02-06,Drill marker lift,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3107757A,1958-11-05,Glass-to-metal seals,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3107771A,1961-02-09,Keyboard lock,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3107784A,1960-09-08,Polypropylene film package,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3107788A,1960-03-28,Carton inspecting machine,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3107812A,1961-03-24,Dispensing mechanism for articles in staggered stack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3107813A,1961-09-11,Dispensing mechanisms for articles in side by side staggered stacks,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3107834A,1959-01-19,Glass cutting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3107882A,1962-08-10,Yaw control system for vtol tilt wing aircraft,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,9
US3107893A,1961-08-31,Solenoid actuated fluid valve,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3107897A,1961-08-24,Gas turbine nozzle and vane assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3107954A,1960-10-28,Split ball spherical bearing,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3108215A,1956-06-11,Electronic control circuit for a. c. motors,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3108228A,1961-12-18,Delay compensation by distributed synchronous pulses,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3108232A,1960-07-06,Ultra high frequency amplifier,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3108273A,1958-03-31,Continuous wave narrow recognition zone radar system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3108278A,1958-12-01,Surface wave luneberg lens antenna system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3108380A,1958-11-10,Glass cutting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3108412A,1960-10-13,Chuck for gears and the like,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3108416A,1961-04-10,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3108445A,1958-07-14,Acetylene transport system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3108466A,1961-02-24,Blast yield meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3108475A,1961-02-13,Gyroscopic mass flowmeter,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3108504A,1963-10-29,Jig for modifying spectacle frames,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3108512A,1962-04-24,Hydraulic jack of follow-up type,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3108626A,1959-05-27,Continuous chopper,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3108638A,1957-10-14,Liner hanger and packer construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3108682A,1961-02-16,Glass jar grippers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3108735A,1961-04-25,Dispensing carton,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3108784A,1961-12-01,Vehicle jack structure with adjustable effective length lift means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3108802A,1961-12-06,Teeter scooter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3108957A,1962-01-11,Milori blue grease,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3109006A,1961-07-03,Benzyl heterocyclicamino-carbothiolates,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3109057A,1960-12-08,Stereo scanning unit and system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3109075A,1961-07-25,Skier alarm switch,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3109080A,1958-09-02,Continuous di-electric heating of electrically non-conductive material,"['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3109121A,1961-09-15,Arc welding control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3109172A,1960-08-10,Low altitude f. m. altimeter,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3109176A,1960-07-22,Cap and tie cord combination,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3109189A,1959-12-01,Bricklayer's mortar joint tool,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3109195A,1961-02-13,Spinneret plate,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3109208A,1960-11-17,Ridge beam hanger,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3109248A,1961-11-15,Bucket grader attachment,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3109271A,1959-05-11,Ramie harvesting machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3109283A,1961-06-15,Cartridge actuated thruster,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3109287A,1961-11-02,Split system power brake,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3109321A,1961-09-19,Balancer for a rotating shaft,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3109330A,1960-08-24,Continuous mill control means,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3109416A,1960-05-09,Multicylinder inline overhead valve engine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3109461A,1960-12-06,Hose structure,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3109463A,1960-02-19,Dispensing nozzle with grease fitting receiving means,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3109476A,1960-05-24,Shearing or bending presses,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3109538A,1961-01-31,Blade dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3109626A,1957-08-26,Jack,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3109830A,1959-03-18,Pentaerythritol-acrolein reaction products and their production,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3109937A,1962-02-05,Diode parametric amplifier upconverter,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3109967A,1962-06-11,Permanent magnetic chuck with nonmagnetic barrier channel for holding magnetic pack,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3109977A,1960-05-26,Silicon controlled rectifier d. c. to a. c. inverter utilizing bridge type arrangement with single commutating capacitor,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,18
US3109994A,1960-06-30,Multivibrator and amplifier powered by pulsating d. c.,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3110072A,1960-02-01,Buckles,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3110077A,1961-03-15,Jigs for making pompons,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3110150A,1962-05-01,Yarn spinning machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3110185A,1960-10-10,Split anode plasma accelerometer,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3110187A,1959-03-10,Gyroscope,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3110204A,1960-12-05,Continuous rolling mill,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3110239A,1960-11-28,Cap for vertical exhaust pipe of internal combustion engine,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3110289A,1955-10-21,Boiler with novel gas recirculation arrangement,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3110328A,1962-08-21,Dobby chain bar and linkage,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3110419A,1959-11-30,Continuous weigh feeder,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3110445A,1962-12-10,Combination aerator and hose coupling device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3110449A,1962-07-30,Breaker plate structure,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3110511A,1960-05-18,Yarn-tying device,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3110594A,1960-11-14,Continuous prescreening of film,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3110692A,1961-01-17,Polyvinyl fluoride film-forming compositions,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3110742A,1960-07-20,Polyalkyl benzene manufacture,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3110769A,1959-01-17,Stereo sound control system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3110922A,1959-10-26,Hose construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3110941A,1960-10-03,Continuous metal casting machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3110949A,1962-09-13,Gang mold for casting concrete and the like,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3110956A,1961-08-25,Jig loading apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3111015A,1961-01-24,Cigar lighter,"['PROPN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3111149A,1960-05-02,"Continuous ball-bearing-type press for making composition board, plywood and like products","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3111169A,1959-06-19,Continuous retrievable testing apparatus,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3111232A,1961-03-21,Jack for light fixtures,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3111255A,1961-02-16,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3111288A,1962-11-28,Yarn package holder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3111326A,1961-05-15,Collet chuck construction,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3111328A,1961-07-03,Multiuse adapter for manipulators,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3111382A,1962-01-18,Alumina from impure aluminum salts,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3111393A,1959-09-03,Continuous counter current extractor,"['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3111437A,1960-01-09,Cap sensitive ammonium nitrate-fuel oil explosive and a method of manufacturing the same,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3111446A,1961-09-28,Label applying machines,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3111450A,1961-02-01,Polyvinyl fluoride film capable of being adhesively secured and method,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'AUX', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3111536A,1960-07-22,Arylmethyl isothiocyanates,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3111538A,1957-02-07,Continuous manufacture of explosive liquid nitric acid esters,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3111570A,1957-12-27,Glass sandwiches primarily for windows of optical instruments,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3111641A,1961-02-03,Plug and jack resistor,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3111687A,1961-09-19,Stretcher,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3111700A,1960-07-07,Yarn mop,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3111761A,1961-03-27,Chalkboard compass,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3111798A,1959-06-02,Dispensing fitment applying machine,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3111851A,1961-04-03,Throttle control,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3111862A,1961-02-08,Collet chuck,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3111913A,1960-10-21,Device for automatic production of baker's ware,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3111927A,1961-11-07,Cartridge for multiple mine anchor cutter,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3111950A,1959-11-16,Cigar,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3111957A,1957-02-28,Chatter-proof vacuum controller unit,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3112117A,1960-11-08,Geared-key operated jawless quick release chuck,"['VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3112194A,1960-10-19,Molten bath treating method and apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3112287A,1958-03-10,Vinyl chloride-vinylidene chloride co-,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3112290A,1961-01-03,Vinyl chloride polymer and ethylene/vinyl chloride polymer compositions and processes,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3112361A,1963-02-14,Ryomei kubota etal,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3112447A,1961-03-09,Antenna float with actuating system,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3112481A,1957-12-20,Continuous wave frequency modulation distance measuring apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3112591A,1961-07-06,Cap applicator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3112803A,1962-01-02,Diamond drill bit,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3112897A,1962-03-20,Glass filament tensioning system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3112937A,1960-12-19,Hose fitting having connecting means for an internal reinforcing member and method of assembly,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3113012A,1960-05-11,Glass-working apparatus,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3113026A,1959-01-19,Polyvinyl alcohol photographic silver halide emulsions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3113065A,1961-06-12,Resin bonded fibreboard and the process of making the same,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3113067A,1959-08-27,Alkanolamine salts of salicyl anilides and process for their production,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3113072A,1961-11-13,Nitro-substituted heterocyclic nitrogen compounds as bird management chemicals,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3113080A,1961-05-22,Continuous decontamination of the hydrogen acquiring surface of a palladium diaphragm used for the transfer of atomic hydrogen,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,19
US3113127A,1959-12-31,"Azo, nitro, anthraquinone, and phthalocyanine dyestuffs having a triazine or pyrimidine ring carrying a thioacylamide substituent","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,20
US3113177A,1960-12-09,D. c. insertion apparatus for a colortelevision receiver,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3113181A,1960-11-25,Amplifier arrangement,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3113195A,1962-02-05,Fuse structures for elevated circuit voltages,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3113369A,1960-05-02,Yarn manufacture and products obtained thereby,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3113423A,1960-10-10,"Tricyclo-[7.1.0.4,0]-decane as a high energy fuel","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3113521A,1959-02-02,Silica heat barrier,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3113599A,1960-11-03,Dispensing nozzle with resilient tank cap holder,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3113677A,1961-07-10,Mug holder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3113757A,1961-01-18,Solenoid-operated gate valve,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3113870A,1961-05-08,Continuous process for the preparation of smoked sausage products,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3114061A,1961-04-20,Refiner construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3114078A,1956-06-05,Amplifier apparatus for measuring currents and/or voltages on high voltage transmission lines,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3114094A,1961-11-02,Adjustable speed brushless a. c. motor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3114262A,1959-05-15,Volumetric gage for conductive liquids,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3114265A,1960-10-03,Barometer,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3114269A,1961-03-22,Gyroscope caging mechanism,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3114416A,1961-11-13,Liner hanger and liner milling tool,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3114610A,1961-05-17,Continuous sampling gas analyzer,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3114649A,1960-05-03,Fatty derivatives of aminoalkyl and hydroxyalkyl heterocyclic amine bases as asphalt additives,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3114727A,1960-10-03,Resin composition and process for preparing the same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3114771A,1963-12-17,Bimetallic salts of z-aminodihydroxy-,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3114804A,1961-05-23,Bin level indicator,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3114829A,1961-11-10,Arc welding method and apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3114950A,1962-07-06,Knot keeper,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3114984A,1960-04-25,Traveler for fishing lines,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3115041A,1960-05-06,thomas,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3115073A,1962-04-18,Carton folding machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3115136A,1962-03-12,Cartridge,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3115158A,1962-03-01,Airfoam liquid proportioning system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3115192A,1960-07-13,Coulter mounting means for moldboard plow,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3115262A,1961-01-09,Carton clamp for lift trucks,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3115284A,1957-07-15,Dispensing spout for metallic containers,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3115403A,1960-12-21,Glass bending mold,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3115437A,1959-05-01,Nubby yarns,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3115505A,1960-06-08,Halogenated epoxy spiro insecticidal compounds,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3115602A,1960-02-01,Continuous mud resistivity measuring device with electricity conductive current confining means,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3115692A,1960-05-24,Yarn break isolating arrangement for beaming apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3115707A,1958-01-31,Carpenter's framing scale,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3115848A,1960-05-11,Monorail vehicle,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3115856A,1957-08-23,Yarn clamp for tufting machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3115861A,1960-02-29,Locating elements of construction beneath the surface of earth soils,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3115875A,1960-11-14,Cartridge syringes,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3115895A,1963-02-28,Leakproof dual valve,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3115899A,1960-02-20,Dobbie mechanism,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3115940A,1961-08-03,Rod weeder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3115943A,1960-12-02,Weigher controlled bagging machine,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3115979A,1962-11-13,Cap for containers,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3116047A,1960-03-16,Solenoid actuated control valve,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3116050A,1961-01-26,Capstan for faired cable,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3116138A,1960-04-04,Molten glass conditioning apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3116192A,1959-07-07,Glass fiber treatiment,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3116215A,1960-05-05,Omega conversion of fatty acid derivatives,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3116296A,1963-12-31,Pymdyl-methyl,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3116423A,1959-01-20,Keying circuit with four terminal network for independent keying of plural repeaters without interference,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,15
US3116459A,1959-12-24,Amplifier having variable input impedance,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3116486A,1961-12-29,Luneberg lens system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3116516A,1960-12-23,Bottle blowing machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3116517A,1960-07-28,Continuous run sliver cans,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3116531A,1960-11-17,Yarn crimping apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3116550A,1960-04-30,Cap having a series of comb teeth for a razor,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3116583A,1960-07-05,Gang rotary mower,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3116674A,1962-06-27,Magnetic override mechanism for camera iris,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3116766A,1960-03-18,Dispensing machine for filling containers,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3116789A,1960-03-14,"Heat exchange apparatus, e. g. for use in gas turbine engines","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3116882A,1962-01-25,Turret-nozzle for paint spray guns,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3116887A,1960-05-19,Yarn winding apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3116908A,1961-04-04,Split wheel gas turbine assembly,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3116914A,1959-12-10,Continuous mining machine having a single adjustable conveyor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3116918A,1960-10-14,Vacuum spring control apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3116993A,1959-02-04,Glass bending,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3116998A,1959-12-31,Continuous vacuum and inert gas process for treating titanium and other metals,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3117013A,1961-11-06,Glass composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3117070A,1960-03-07,Bronze half-cell for cathodic protection system,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3117103A,1960-07-21,Binary blends of styrene/acrylonitrile copolymer and (cyanoethoxy) ethyl acrylate polymer and methods for preparing the same,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,21
US3117148A,1961-08-09,Butadiene iron subgroup tricarbonyl hydrohalide compounds and their preparation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3117158A,1959-03-16,Aminoarylsulfur pentafluorides,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3117193A,1961-07-06,Self-normalling video jack,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3117257A,1962-02-02,Solenoid having a rotatable back stop for the plunger,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3117286A,1960-09-02,Turret-type tuner amplifier,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3117361A,1960-02-11,Yarn heat treatment apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3117450A,1961-01-31,Thermometer pacifier,"['PROPN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3117454A,1962-07-24,Deep sea densimeter,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3117528A,1964-01-14,rosaen,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3117599A,1960-05-12,Jacquard machines,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3117689A,1962-10-16,Prop for trunk compartment lids,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3117701A,1958-04-11,Dispensing closure and container,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3117788A,1959-06-01,Puck construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3117809A,1959-05-15,Hose and fitting construction,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3117944A,1960-07-28,Coagula of colloidal fibrous boehmite and acrylamide polymers and processes for making same,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3117962A,1959-08-20,Azo dyes containing a halomethylbenzoylamino radical,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3118012A,1959-05-01,Melt spinning process,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3118040A,1957-07-02,H. f. dielectric heating apparatus,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3118087A,1960-06-17,Meter relay system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3118111A,1960-12-01,Pulse synchronizing means for multiroute p. c. m. system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3118195A,1960-04-05,Continuous casting apparatus and method,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3118231A,1964-01-21,Rathsmill,['ADV'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3118257A,1964-01-21,Csnteslsss control yi hesl bbf,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3118291A,1964-01-21,Axiajxy movable coupling,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3118311A,1964-01-21,francis,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3118327A,1964-01-21,eastman,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3118344A,1964-01-21,Hoglund,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3118347A,1960-03-14,Earlajhompson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3118393A,1960-12-27,Xhiving  means in a track system,"['VERB', 'SPACE', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3118405A,1960-04-04,Schenkengel,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3118409A,1945-06-22,Torpedo control circuit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3118428A,1962-10-31,Powder dispenser for animals,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3118507A,1961-12-20,Gang holding means for disk harrows,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3118533A,1962-03-09,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3118600A,1961-08-28,Continuous flow fluid heater control,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3118667A,1961-06-28,"Mouth exerciser for strengthening face, neck and lip muscles","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3118691A,1960-01-15,Hose fitting,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3118887A,1961-03-06,O-hydroxy substituted tris aryl-s-triazines,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3118904A,1964-01-21,Amidoximo alkyl,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3118939A,1960-06-29,Quaternary ammonium hexaborates,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3118992A,1962-09-05,Fuse construction having a resilient rod including a connection provided with mechanical advantage levers and a spring button,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,19
US3119083A,1960-10-11,Mechanical shutter for iris in which shutter blade edge moves while remaining parallel to electric field,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,17
US3119106A,1960-01-11,Radar terrain contour display system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3119112A,1959-12-23,Stapler,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3119120A,1962-04-11,Jockey type shorts,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3119139A,1961-02-06,Bottle case inverter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3119148A,1961-03-14,Continuous sheet extrusion apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3119170A,1960-04-01,Turret indexing control device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3119256A,1960-08-01,Prony brake apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3119287A,1959-10-27,Jig bushes,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3119297A,1962-10-11,Banjo fifth string tuning peg,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'ORDINAL']",0,1,6
US3119361A,1961-04-24,Yarn feed apparatus with detachable template,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3119483A,1961-04-10,Escrow bucket and coin guide,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3119587A,1962-10-08,Hose holding fixture,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3119598A,1962-08-28,Air film supported weighing jack,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3119648A,1958-02-24,Salt rinse,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3119681A,1960-03-28,Glass forming molds,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3119697A,1962-01-09,Agar preparation and process of producing the same,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3119703A,1961-07-31,Infrared transmitting glasses,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3119783A,1959-10-30,Polypropylene stabilized with a mixture of a para-tertiaryalkylphenol-formaldehyde resin and an organic phosphite,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,18
US3119864A,1961-01-03,Haloalkyl substituted borazines,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3119865A,1960-06-15,Arylene-bis nitroso ureas,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3119954A,1961-04-04,Solenoid with molded plunger guide,"['ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3119963A,1961-01-31,Galvanometer with filar suspended coil and the coil ends being connected to wires wrapped about the suspensions,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,18
US3120037A,1961-11-01,Continuous casting,"['ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3120081A,1962-01-22,Sprung axle for toy vehicle,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3120176A,1961-07-28,Carton marking machines,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3120209A,1960-11-23,Torpedo power circuit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3120309A,1961-09-28,Coat hanger bar,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3120358A,1962-02-23,Cable reel jack,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3120373A,1962-11-28,Leakproof vacuum valve,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3120381A,1961-12-04,Glass fiber pad construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3120388A,1961-06-15,Golfer's helper,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3120430A,1960-10-10,Continuous gas process and apparatus for practicing same,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3120580A,1962-03-23,Stereo signal generator,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3120607A,1959-01-12,Volumetric dispensing device with radioactive control means,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3120688A,1961-12-21,Auxiliary closing mechanisms for tenter clips,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3120701A,1961-06-02,Puller for hydraulic valve lifter plungers,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3120788A,1959-07-07,Double-acting fluid-pressure jack,"['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3120808A,1960-05-09,Stud cartridge shell,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3120828A,1959-10-20,Roof seaming machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3120862A,1957-11-05,Continuous chain press,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3120927A,1963-01-14,Spraybar,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3121000A,1960-11-09,Laundry dryer or washer-dryer,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3121051A,1964-02-11,Decanols prefared by aldol condensation of aldehydes,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3121082A,1962-05-22,Phosphites and phosphonates of hydroxyalkyl and hydroxyalkoxyalkyl isocyanurates,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,9
US3121138A,1959-05-28,Continuous scanning apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3121147A,1960-11-07,Glass-sealed reed type relay module,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3121261A,1960-02-25,Glass door construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3121299A,1962-07-19,Glass grinding runner,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3121356A,1962-06-14,Slip-proof wrench,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3121361A,1959-09-17,Shearing machine with rotating and translating blades,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3121447A,1959-04-13,Tab bender and locator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3121556A,1961-11-02,Airplane jack assembly with spring compressor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3121576A,1959-10-12,Binder case construction convertible to easel form,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'AUX', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3121584A,1963-02-06,Jettison hook for external cargo load,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3121636A,1961-04-06,Dispensing cup assembly containing a food concentrate,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3121640A,1964-02-18,Alumina refractories,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3121684A,1961-01-04,Gutter and downspout strainer,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3121719A,1960-11-23,Ceramidonine vat dyes and process of preparing same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3121724A,1961-09-20,Aminoalkyl ethers of 6-halobenzyl-5-indanol and 7-halobenzyl-4-indanol,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,15
US3121790A,1959-10-09,Infrared analyser with signal ratio indicating means,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3121844A,1959-08-04,Amplifier control system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3121881A,1961-05-15,Stretcher with canopy,"['ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3121912A,1961-10-18,Continuous vulcanization of sheeted rubber,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3121984A,1961-03-22,Cap brake for sealing machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3122114A,1961-05-01,Continuous tube forming and galvanizing,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3122191A,1962-03-30,Antiskid appliance device for vehicles,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3122256A,1959-03-09,Cap seal,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3122282A,1960-10-14,Fertilizer distributor or planter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3122311A,1962-04-10,Striker bar suspension for selective punch device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3122365A,1962-06-11,Bat,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3122392A,1962-12-14,Cartridge operated parachute release mechanism,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3122434A,1960-06-03,Continuous process of producing strips and sheets of ferrous metal directly from metal powder,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3122510A,1960-09-07,Method of removing nickel and vanadium from synthetic gel silica-based catalysts,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3122516A,1961-02-20,Organosiloxane elastomers reinforced with modified silica fillers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3122563A,1962-02-12,Pyran derivatives of synthetic diphenyl estrogens,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']","['FAC', 'PERSON']",0,1,7
US3122568A,1959-05-22,Epoxy esters of polycarboxylic acids,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3122575A,1961-03-22,Diphenyl ether derivatives,"['PROPN', 'ADV', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3122685A,1961-02-09,"Semiconductor rectifier device, particularly of miniature type","['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3122874A,1960-05-20,Yarn handling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3122877A,1960-10-12,Yarn winding device for spinning machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3122897A,1962-03-05,Freezing tunnel for comestibles,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3122915A,1964-03-03,Haller,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3122932A,1964-03-03,kopczynski,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3122945A,1964-03-03,Jackson chung,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3122966A,1964-03-03,butterfield,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3122971A,1964-03-03,russell,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3122975A,1964-03-03,williams,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3122977A,1964-03-03,Graham,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3122989A,1964-03-03,Continuous manufacture of sausage,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3122999A,1964-03-03,Cylinder heating means for rotary printing press,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3123009A,1964-03-03,watson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123014A,1964-03-03,Gregor,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123019A,1964-03-03,blair,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123023A,1964-03-03,Bronson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123033A,1964-03-03,Weigert,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123037A,1964-03-03,jensen,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123055A,1964-03-03,Boiler having refractory headers,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3123074A,1964-03-03,Colostomy aid,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3123097A,1964-03-03,kennedy,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123114A,1964-03-03,Richard a,"['PROPN', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123144A,1964-03-03,Znventors,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123176A,1964-03-03,greenberg,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123185A,1964-03-03,van der rust,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3123194A,1964-03-03,Manifold control for typewriters,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3123255A,1964-03-03,martin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123259A,1964-03-03,Dispensing closure for a container,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3123269A,1959-05-25,Handler for folding tape,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3123282A,1964-03-03,Impeller brake,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123289A,1964-03-03,Jean-baptiste astier,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3123299A,1964-03-03,douglas,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123329A,1964-03-03,pruehs,['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123343A,1964-03-03,Harry h,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123344A,1964-03-03,Glass bending furnaces,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3123359A,1964-03-03,lindgren,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123368A,1964-03-03,Chuck,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123370A,1964-03-03,Anchor chuck and anchor,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",1,1,4
US3123371A,1964-03-03,Chuck arrangement,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123375A,1964-03-03,courtney,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123377A,1964-03-03,hutchens,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3123384A,1964-03-03,Baker,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123400A,1964-03-03,Invalid s chair,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3123404A,1964-03-03,William g,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123412A,1964-03-03,Tsutomu takao,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123415A,1964-03-03,carter,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123425A,1957-12-11,Blanchet,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123452A,1964-03-03,Glass polish and process of polishing,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3123459A,1952-04-05,Carl hens,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123482A,1961-01-16,R lieberman,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3123490A,1961-05-04,Nacreous pigment and method for preparing same,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3123527A,1964-03-03,Antibacterkl compositions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3123609A,1964-03-03,Benzo,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123610A,1964-03-03,Alkanoylpiperidinoalkyl,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123642A,1964-03-03,Indanyl and tetrahydronaphthyl,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3123651A,1964-03-03,Impeller device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123719A,1964-03-03,lee iii,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123727A,1960-06-15,Kritz,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123731A,1964-03-03,Gordon,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123774A,1964-03-03,davis,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123780A,1964-03-03,Futterman,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123797A,1964-03-03,Ehrman,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123829A,1964-03-03,Bronson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123859A,1961-03-27,Barainsky,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123882A,1964-03-10,Meyerson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123894A,1964-03-10,Von bonin,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3123921A,1964-03-10,Bartelson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123925A,1964-03-10,johnson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123926A,1964-03-10,Jacobson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3123963A,1964-03-10,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3123969A,1964-03-10,Yarn twisting device,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3123975A,1964-03-10,Ebert,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3123979A,1960-05-13,Bilge blocks and dry docks utilising such bilge blocks.,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3123999A,1964-03-10,Amplifier-,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124000A,1964-03-10,Melas,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3124015A,1960-12-21,Mottu,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124039A,1964-03-10,anderson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124056A,1961-08-29,Hayes,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124109A,1964-03-10,Von benten,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124147A,1964-03-10,hallett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124195A,1964-03-10,anderson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124223A,1964-03-10,Klsovec,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124225A,1964-03-10,Rosenberg,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124230A,1964-03-10,Bustamante,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124242A,1964-03-10,Yarn shipping package,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3124264A,1964-03-10,Waisberg,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124274A,1964-03-10,de biasi,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3124294A,1964-03-10,Zerlin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124300A,1964-03-10,Fig-ij,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3124301A,1964-03-10,Helmbold,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124302A,1962-05-16,arnett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124307A,1964-03-10,Vapor lamp units,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3124314A,1964-03-10,Klein,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124315A,1960-09-27,Siebert,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3124316A,1964-03-10,Knot counting attachment for textile winders,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3124324A,1964-03-10,Martin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124333A,1964-03-10,Split ball valves having cam sealing,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3124337A,1964-03-10,Fritz,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124347A,1964-03-10,haddad,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124357A,1964-03-10,Shqhb,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124367A,1964-03-10,kaynor,['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3124370A,1964-03-10,traugott,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124374A,1964-03-10,John t,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124389A,1964-03-10,mi kan,"['NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124445A,1964-03-10,Hideo tatibana,"['VERB', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3124484A,1964-03-10,magnusson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3124494A,1964-03-10,Nhxgiox,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124498A,1964-03-10,Ziegler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124500A,1964-03-10,Dj benedetto,"['ADV', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3124514A,1964-03-10,koutz etal,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3124551A,1964-03-10,Xpxox,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124567A,1964-03-10,Azo dyes containing a diqxopyrazolbdine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3124577A,1964-03-10,Hydroxyalkyl cyclic amlno,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3124586A,1964-03-10,Conhz,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3124594A,1964-03-10,Cyanoalkyl,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124615A,1964-03-10,Carotenoid compounds,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3124655A,1964-03-10,Feiner,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124667A,1958-07-26,Holzer,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124686A,1959-09-24,Goorissen,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124701A,1964-03-10,Richard l,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124711A,1959-05-05,Reifenschweiler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124737A,1964-03-10,Miller,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124753A,1961-08-21,Methpuira,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124766A,1964-03-10,edelson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124774A,1961-07-05,Lafont,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124775A,1964-03-10,Hamelberg,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124813A,1964-03-17,graef,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3124833A,1964-03-17,altenpohl,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3124840A,1964-03-17,taylor etal,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3124859A,1959-11-03,Yarn drawing apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3124893A,1964-03-17,glenn,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3124932A,1964-03-17,nelson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124948A,1956-05-15,Levin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124951A,1964-03-17,Marik,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124960A,1964-03-17,Clark,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3124984A,1964-03-17,Anderson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125089A,1964-03-17,taylor,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125105A,1964-03-17,Fig-z a,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3125140A,1964-03-17,nichols,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125153A,1964-03-17,Backfire torch,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3125171A,1964-03-17,stewart iii,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125180A,1964-03-17,Markowitz,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125182A,1964-03-17,earley,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125183A,1964-03-17,Mcrae,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125189A,1964-03-17,Graham,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125199A,1964-03-17,Thompson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125205A,1964-03-17,kinney,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125218A,1964-03-17,Floyd,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125252A,1964-03-17,Dispensing machine with nozzle cleaner,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3125253A,1964-03-17,Dispensing head mounting assembly,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3125258A,1964-03-17,Dispensing container and blank therefor,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3125260A,1964-03-17,Shaker or sifter-type dispensers,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3125262A,1964-03-17,Goodwin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125269A,1964-03-17,Dispensing machine x,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3125282A,1964-03-17,Janicke,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125293A,1964-03-17,burdett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125299A,1964-03-17,Vehicle lamp mounting,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3125312A,1964-03-17,mcduffie,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125321A,1964-03-17,Solenoid activated flow valve,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3125324A,1964-03-17,Vivier,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125327A,1964-03-17,williams,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125343A,1964-03-17,Improper gxlf  swing is executed,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'SPACE', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3125348A,1964-03-17,Zimmerman,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125381A,1964-03-17,anderson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125402A,1964-03-17,Xcx ch,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125422A,1964-03-17,Comparator control for a tumbling drier,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3125479A,1964-03-17,finan,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125499A,1964-03-17,Richard b,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125553A,1960-06-22,Continuous Polymerization process for vinyl mononers,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3125563A,1964-03-17,Azo dyes containing a benzo-,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3125565A,1964-03-17,Hjcxghz,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125586A,1960-01-08,Quaternary ammonium salts of z-amino-,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3125598A,1958-12-06,Dialkylaminoaryl arylcarbamates,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125613A,1964-03-17,Mccartney,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125617A,1964-03-17,Hoppe,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125634A,1962-06-05,Cshs cahs,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125642A,1962-01-15,Aev-zj,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3125643A,1964-03-17,Solenoid,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125662A,1964-03-17,Portae,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125679A,1964-03-17,Ryohei,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125716A,1964-03-17,Machlis,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125725A,1959-07-20,chang,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125774A,1964-03-24,Schmitt,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125784A,1964-03-24,Macdonald,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125816A,1964-03-24,Gartner,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125821A,1964-03-24,Repeating gun with cartridge lifter and cartridge stop member,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3125832A,1964-03-24,Fouquet,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125833A,1964-03-24,Jdiajq dninjjhvhs jivhs,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3125835A,1964-03-24,Ralph e,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125848A,1964-03-24,Yarn and fabric product and process,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3125871A,1964-03-24,Schur,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125894A,1964-03-24,Derailer change-speed for mechanisms for cycles,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3125905A,1964-03-24,Stein,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125913A,1964-03-24,smrekar,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3125948A,1964-03-24,Cleaner bar for upper baler drive roller,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3125953A,1964-03-24,Amplifier,['ADP'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3125966A,1964-03-24,johnson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125971A,1964-03-24,wetherill,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3125980A,1964-03-24,Azimuth control system for towed submersible bodies,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3125990A,1964-03-24,van peursem etal,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3125991A,1964-03-24,van dusen,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3125994A,1964-03-24,Ruskin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126000A,1964-03-24,Carl-anker mejyr,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3126004A,1964-03-24,Cartridge with antipilfering pistojf,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3126022A,1964-03-24,thompson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126027A,1964-03-24,blair,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126029A,1964-03-24,Englesson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126076A,1964-03-24,Koffler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126077A,1964-03-24,Marshall,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126091A,1964-03-24,kuhnl,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126093A,1964-03-24,Cigar box,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3126108A,1964-03-24,Glass handling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3126111A,1964-03-24,Lewis,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126127A,1964-03-24,lovendusky,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3126133A,1964-03-24,richardson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126134A,1964-03-24,Hose seam flattening device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3126151A,1964-03-24,Barry,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126165A,1961-01-31,Jan van euk,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3126173A,1964-03-24,Alvarez-calderdn,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3126177A,1964-03-24,Markowitz,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126178A,1964-03-24,hamilton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126193A,1964-03-24,atherton,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126204A,1964-03-24,Devlin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126222A,1964-03-24,Stuart,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126223A,1964-03-24,kughler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126226A,1964-03-24,johnson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126238A,1964-03-24,acton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126266A,1959-08-18,Meisler,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126269A,1964-03-24,Glass feeder intended for a continuous,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3126301A,1961-09-11,Molten salt spray process for descaling stainless steel,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3126309A,1964-03-24,Label machine registering means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3126347A,1964-03-24,swoboda,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126356A,1964-03-24,Pentaerythritol condensation products,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3126358A,1964-03-24,Polypropylene,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126391A,1964-03-24,Alkoxyalkyl ib-o-alkoxyalkyl,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3126406A,1964-03-24,Alkoxyalkyl estehs of tfflolcarbamates,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3126437A,1964-03-24,Radii,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126457A,1964-03-24,jones,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126458A,1960-08-19,Bowen,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126487A,1964-03-24,jorgensen,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126501A,1964-03-24,Flora,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126514A,1964-03-24,John w,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3126515A,1959-11-06,Berman,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126519A,1964-03-24,burley,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126547A,1959-08-31,Rosenberg,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126582A,1964-03-31,Scott,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126591A,1964-03-31,Hamilton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126607A,1961-05-03,Jenny,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126625A,1964-03-31,Mkthob qf joining and bonding together,"['PROPN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3126636A,1964-03-31,Glass cutter assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3126700A,1964-03-31,Rene -philippe jaccard,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3126711A,1960-04-29,E miller,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3126728A,1964-03-31,nehls,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126747A,1964-03-31,James r,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3126773A,1964-03-31,taylor,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126776A,1964-03-31,Lawrence v whistler sr,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3126783A,1964-03-31,Solenoid means and solenoid mounting means for pianos,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3126792A,1960-09-07,Zwick,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126801A,1964-03-31,Tatsuo kobayashi,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3126811A,1964-03-31,kennedy,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126832A,1964-03-31,Mencarelli,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126866A,1964-03-31,Shoshichl kubota,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3126881A,1964-03-31,Blotsky,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126887A,1964-03-31,gordon,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3126918A,1964-03-31,Slip ring spacer for insulated conduit systems,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3126923A,1964-03-31,thatcher,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3126933A,1964-03-31,Traveller s canine canteen,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3127015A,1964-03-31,schieren,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3127033A,1964-03-31,Glass furnace batch charging apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3127036A,1964-03-31,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3127053A,1964-03-31,Cap feeding machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3127083A,1964-03-31,Dispensing carton,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3127088A,1964-03-31,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127099A,1964-03-31,la barre,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3127103A,1964-03-31,Continuous switching for control systems,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3127108A,1964-03-31,Sprinkler control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3127121A,1964-03-31,Babin,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127143A,1964-03-31,Terman,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127151A,1964-03-31,klawitter,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3127173A,1964-03-31,Siverling,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3127180A,1964-03-31,Lehmann,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127200A,1964-03-31,Sayag,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127204A,1964-03-31,Knot stripper for balers,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3127218A,1964-03-31,banke,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127250A,1964-03-31,Heinemann,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127252A,1964-03-31,bennett,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127268A,1964-03-31,Hellmig,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127277A,1964-03-31,Glass composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3127343A,1964-03-31,Invert emulsion well fluid,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3127391A,1964-03-31,Azo pigment,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3127433A,1958-07-16,"1, 1-bis(trifluoromethyl) ethyl silanes and siloxanes","['NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB']","['CARDINAL', 'QUANTITY', 'PERSON']",1,1,11
US3127434A,1959-10-20,Dihydrovitamin k monophosphate compounds and preparation thereof,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3127476A,1964-03-31,david,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3127560A,1952-05-24,Amplifier for photoelectric bridge spectrophotometer,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3127576A,1962-02-09,D.c. to a.c. converter with negative feedback stabilization,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PART', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3127650A,1961-03-13,Buckles,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3127717A,1963-05-27,Grinder attachment fixture,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3127772A,1960-06-06,Barometer for indicating sea level pressure,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3128012A,1961-10-31,Label dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3128031A,1960-08-10,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3128032A,1962-08-01,Dispensing container and one piece blank,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3128055A,1961-05-31,Refiner plate,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3128060A,1962-09-27,Yarn cake holder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3128082A,1962-03-02,Shaker,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3128085A,1960-08-29,Continuous mixer,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3128160A,1959-04-17,Glass fiber filter for hot gas distribution in driers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3128289A,1962-12-14,"Pentaerythritol and trimethylolalkane poly(2,3-epoxyalkanoates)","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3128345A,1960-11-01,Limiter control system for stereophonic radio receiver,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3128434A,1960-04-28,Transfluxor with amplitude modulated driving pulse input converted to alternating sine wave output,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3128562A,1961-06-30,Azimuth compass,"['ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3128587A,1960-04-01,Cotton harvester with trash discharge means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3128600A,1960-05-18,Multilevel solid propellant rocket motor,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3128664A,1962-07-13,Bass bow holder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3128666A,1960-07-21,Split bolt anchor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3128774A,1956-05-24,Toscani cigar machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3128807A,1960-07-15,Fail safe valve for tire chuck on post-inflation machine,"['VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3128816A,1964-04-14,van witteloostuyn,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3128858A,1964-04-14,Ikuro,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128874A,1964-04-14,hanna,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128881A,1964-04-14,Kghnle,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128894A,1964-04-14,nelson,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128926A,1964-04-14,Holster for firearms,"['ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3128930A,1964-04-14,Lehnert,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128943A,1961-07-10,stewart,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128954A,1961-03-17,davidson,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3128957A,1964-04-14,Fallscheer,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3128960A,1964-04-14,jones,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US3128966A,1964-04-14,Alvarez-calderon,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3128969A,1964-04-14,Cartridge inflated balloon,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3129008A,1960-02-27,Stereo pickup device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3129073A,1961-07-25,Continuous grain dryer,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3129079A,1961-08-07,Aircleaner hold-down bracket,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3129198A,1960-02-08,Quaternary monoimidazoline salts as thermosetting catalysts for resinous blends comprising polyepoxide polymers and acrylic polymers having a plurality of carboxyl groups therein,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADV']",['PERSON'],1,1,23
US3129200A,1958-08-14,Polyurethane prepolymers cured with butene or butyne diol,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3129247A,1962-04-05,Cyclopropyl sulfonyl ureas,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3129255A,1959-12-01,Alkylation of benzene with propylene in the presence of ticl4 and alkyl aluminum sesquichloride,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3129272A,1960-05-19,Melt-spinning synthetic polymer filaments,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3129296A,1960-10-10,Stereo tape recorder system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3129351A,1961-12-21,Multielectrode arc assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3129379A,1962-02-28,D.c. to a.c. converter,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PART', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3129423A,1955-10-21,Target cancelling radar systems,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3129431A,1962-10-30,Welder's helmet,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3129500A,1960-08-29,Jig for assembling ratchet mechanisms,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3129543A,1961-10-16,Cap applicator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3129579A,1962-02-01,Latchbolt holdback for doorlocks,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3129618A,1961-05-23,Continuous rolling mill drive,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3129724A,1960-08-13,Solenoid controlled distributing valve,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3129808A,1961-05-03,Cap,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3129843A,1963-05-09,Carton,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3129898A,1961-04-18,Refiner construction,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3129950A,1962-07-16,Center-adjustable chuck adapter,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3129959A,1961-08-01,Hose coupling,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3129966A,1961-10-09,Crosshead wrist pin assembly,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,5
US3130028A,1959-05-26,Glass feeding,"['NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3130076A,1961-09-29,Continuous vinyl grafting of cellulose,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3130097A,1961-09-20,Boron containing fuels,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3130126A,1962-09-14,Oral pharmaceutical products prepared with carboxymethyl benzyl dextran having a low carboxymethyl d. s. of 0.15,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM']","['PERSON', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,17
US3130180A,1957-09-18,Continuous method and apparatus for the production of polyhexamethylene adipamide,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3130243A,1962-08-21,Separation of hydrocarbons by silver dialkyl phosphates,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3130282A,1961-07-14,Solenoid operated switches,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3130307A,1962-03-02,Neutron flux intensity detection,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3130358A,1960-01-25,D. c. motor for position control with dynamic and mechanical braking,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3130447A,1960-08-03,Continuous vulcanization,"['ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3130476A,1958-06-18,Scoop cutting and bottom stop machines combination the machines and control means therefor,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3130499A,1960-10-05,Glass cutting apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3130695A,1962-12-19,Machine for sewing imitation moccasin seams,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3130776A,1960-06-23,Venetian blind cord guide,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",0,1,5
US3130836A,1961-09-26,Dispensing rack,"['VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3130848A,1963-06-11,Bottle cap with interrupted threads,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3130893A,1962-08-22,Cigarette box,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3130921A,1961-09-13,Vehicle lamp mounting,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3130955A,1961-05-09,Runner blade servo system for turbines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3130956A,1962-05-21,Jack device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3130988A,1959-10-14,Hose coupling,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3130990A,1961-09-11,Knob spring,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3131089A,1961-01-25,"Carbon article coated with boron carbide and boron nitride, and process of making the same","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,17
US3131094A,1961-06-21,Electrolyte retracting paper spacer for spin activated batteries,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3131114A,1959-12-21,Glass-included integrated mica sheet and method of production,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3131124A,1956-06-15,Bagacidin and process for its manufacture,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3131193A,1964-04-28,Isojticotijsroyl-x-jvibthoxy-urbenztlajhne,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3131299A,1961-12-29,Ray-tracing method for ion-optical measurements,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3131333A,1964-04-28,stevens,['VERB'],['PERSON'],0,1,1
US3131357A,1959-06-08,D. c. amplifier,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3131403A,1962-02-06,Adult urine specimen collector,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3131428A,1958-12-19,Spinneret and spinning method,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3131500A,1961-03-21,Cartridge loader for revolvers and carrying case therefor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3131533A,1961-02-13,Afterburner and method for purifying polluted exhaust gases,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3131555A,1961-05-18,Knit shirt or like garment,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3131740A,1961-09-08,Rice huller having a feed screw on the hulling cylinder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3131790A,1961-02-02,Spacing and locking device for roof arch centers,"['ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3131830A,1961-07-31,Continuous package dispensing machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3131835A,1960-10-13,Mouth lid means of iris stop type,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,8
US3131879A,1961-07-13,Yarn winding machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3131883A,1961-01-25,Hose retrieving device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3131933A,1962-05-21,Cue stick chalking device,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3131948A,1962-03-26,Retractable chuck jaw,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3131975A,1960-04-21,Slope control wheel brake control system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3132051A,1960-06-09,Continuous process for extracting pentoses from substances containing hemicelluloses,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3132096A,1961-11-21,Continuous saline water purification,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3132121A,1961-04-13,Epoxy containing resins,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3132129A,1959-03-21,Azo phthalocyanine dyestuffs,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3132137A,1960-11-18,Steroido [3.2-d] pyrimidines and preparation thereof,"['PROPN', 'X', 'NUM', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'X', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,11
US3132174A,1960-08-01,gamma-amino-gamma-cyanopropylsulfonic acid salts and method for making homocysteic acid,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3132179A,1959-08-27,Ethers of alpha-hydroxymethyl-beta-monocarbocyclic aryl ethyl amines and their preparation,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3132261A,1961-08-28,"Delay circuit employing feedback to hold normally-open switch closed, allowing capacitor to fully discharge","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'ADV', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,18
US3132339A,1961-01-03,Sideband cancellation system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3132358A,1961-10-03,Rod feed and cut-off control,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3132382A,1962-09-13,Resin foam insulated cabinet,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3132401A,1962-02-21,Barrel clamp for hand trucks,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3132469A,1961-12-05,Sampler clock with electric movement,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3132512A,1961-02-13,Gyroscopic mass flowmeter,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3132588A,1962-10-16,Buckshot shells for shotguns,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3132589A,1963-04-04,Buckshot shells for shotguns,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3132833A,1961-05-19,Jack,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3132871A,1961-10-09,Chuck,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3132873A,1962-11-15,Runner attachment for vehicles,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3132894A,1960-08-30,Recliner chair of the multiple position type incorporating improved head-rest control,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3132919A,1956-03-29,Increasing safe ironing temperatures of cellulsoe triacetate fibers with swelling agents boiling above 190deg. c.,"['VERB', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN']","['QUANTITY', 'PERSON']",1,1,17
US3133009A,1959-11-13,Continuous antidromic electrophoresis,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3133016A,1962-10-08,Continuous treatment of polluted water,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3133040A,1958-02-20,Polyvinyl acetate emulsions with unsaturated esters,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3133044A,1959-03-16,Continuous process for polymerizing bisphenols and phosgene,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3133072A,1962-01-16,Quaternary ammonium cyclic imides,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3133074A,1962-02-20,Quaternary 4-phenyl-4-carbalkoxy-piperidinium derivatives,"['PROPN', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3133076A,1961-04-06,"Phenyl-imidazo(1, 2-a)pyridine-6-car-boxylic acids and their esters","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'X', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,16
US3133175A,1960-10-05,Shockproof electromagnetic contactor having arc chute and blowout assembly and pivoted contact carriage means,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3133195A,1958-12-05,Neutron slowing down and absorption logging method,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3133242A,1960-10-28,Stabilized d. c. amplifier power supply,"['VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3133289A,1962-07-26,Cap with removable stiffener elements,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3133333A,1959-09-03,Mould for the manufacture of lightweight concrete blocks,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3133404A,1962-05-17,Traveler with frictional resistance means,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3133505A,1959-12-01,Impeller wheel,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3133628A,1962-12-24,Shaker conveyor trough line,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3133703A,1961-10-02,Desk lamp structure,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3133742A,1962-10-08,Stairclimbing wheelchair,"['VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3133792A,1964-05-19,Slip cast calcined magnesia products,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3133805A,1961-04-26,Glass bead making furnace,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3133850A,1960-11-17,Continuous making of plywood,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3133854A,1960-11-15,Polyvinyl fluoride laminates and process for making same,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3133872A,1959-03-10,Anode for electrochemical applications,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3133887A,1958-10-06,Neutron shields and methods of manufacturing them,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3133900A,1959-06-11,Bisphenol-ether-formaldehyde resins,"['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3133970A,1960-12-29,Dicarboranyl alkenes and method for their preparation,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3133982A,1962-03-30,Eyeglass sweat bands,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3133989A,1960-10-31,Amplifier control circuit,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3133993A,1960-04-18,Stereo fm transmission system,"['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3134042A,1959-02-19,Cap-shaped cathode for cathode ray tubes,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3134046A,1962-06-15,Amplifier and coupling circuit,"['ADV', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3134065A,1962-07-20,Positive-feedback d. c. motor speed control circuits,"['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3134070A,1960-07-20,Unitary control device for detecting the minimum levels of concentration in a multiplicity of caustic washing solutions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,18
US3134103A,1962-09-07,Altimeter,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3134153A,1960-09-13,Buckles,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3134199A,1960-05-19,Complexed refractory brick,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3134232A,1961-10-02,Jack,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3134308A,1962-08-06,Carton assembling machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3134340A,1962-09-17,Balancer assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3134407A,1962-05-16,Cartridge refilling device for caulking guns and the like,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3134509A,1958-02-24,Dispensing machine with protective atmosphere,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3134517A,1961-03-23,Cap construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3134529A,1961-10-05,Yarn threading mechanism for a pattern attachment for tufting machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3134540A,1962-06-25,Nomographic computing device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3134658A,1960-10-21,Breather trap,"['PROPN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3134659A,1959-08-24,Glass melting apparatus and method useful for the production of glass fibers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3134692A,1961-11-27,Carton gluing apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3134713A,1962-04-02,Vinyl phosphate pesticide,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3134733A,1961-01-09,Screens,['NOUN'],['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3134758A,1959-07-16,Vinyl esters and derivatives thereof and process of preparing same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3134764A,1961-10-18,Azo dyes containing a dihydroxyphenyl silver halide developing radical,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3134766A,1959-08-13,Azo dyestuffs of low water-solubility,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
