patent_number,date,title,spacy_pos,spacy_label,is_prpn_spacy,is_person_spacy,spacy_pos_len
US1200000A,1915-12-18,"Rod connection. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1200054A,1915-12-21,"Alfalfa and rice land checker. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1200118A,1915-09-08,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1200143A,1916-03-04,"Adjustable insulated coupling for motors and dynamos. 
     ","['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1200171A,1915-12-27,"Traveler's safety-vest. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1200354A,1913-12-13,"Cap for friction-top cans. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1200567A,1915-02-05,"Shears or scissors. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1200601A,1916-05-27,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1200636A,1913-12-22,"Barrel filling and packing machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1200889A,1914-08-31,"Glass-melting receptacle. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1201069A,1915-07-13,"Cigar-making machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1201158A,1916-04-21,"Jack for pumps and other purposes. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1201184A,1915-05-08,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1201195A,1915-11-30,"Coat hanger. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1201217A,1915-05-18,"Tailor's measure. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1201223A,1914-11-24,"Eyeglass construction. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1201254A,1915-09-14,"Cap-retainer for deformable tubes. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1201277A,1913-01-09,"Cap. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1201413A,1915-09-27,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1201474A,1915-01-05,"Cigar or cigarette case. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1201489A,1912-04-03,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1201515A,1914-07-15,"Glass-cutter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1201538A,1916-06-13,"Printer's quoin. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1201568A,1916-04-13,"Meter holder and connection. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1201576A,1915-10-25,"Cigar-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1201742A,1916-07-17,"Agar-agar biscuit and method of making the same. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1202080A,1916-02-18,"Cluster-lamp for inverted limp mantles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1202105A,1916-01-03,"Yarn-controller. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1202132A,1914-07-31,"Connector for garment and hose supporters. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1202179A,1915-12-15,"Morse transmitting-key. 
     ","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1202256A,1915-09-30,"Carpenter's plane. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1202271A,1915-12-11,"Clip for wrist-straps for watches, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US1202307A,1916-07-13,"Cap. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1202342A,1916-03-30,"Cartridge-pack for revolvers. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1202343A,1916-05-26,"Cartridge-clip. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1202514A,1915-07-26,"Miner's acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1202516A,1915-12-31,"Harrow attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1202518A,1916-03-14,"Unipod for camera-supports. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1202596A,1914-11-02,"Cap-making machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1202645A,1915-10-12,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1202718A,1915-04-16,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1202774A,1916-05-24,"Eyeglass-polishing device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1202847A,1915-01-25,"Composition for painting iron, wood, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1202858A,1913-04-12,"Knockdown barrel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1202981A,1914-12-19,"Cigar or cigarette holder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1202993A,1916-04-22,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1203022A,1915-11-18,"Cleaner for wind-shields. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1203141A,1916-05-06,"Antiskid attachment for automobiles. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1203151A,1914-05-21,"Periscope azimuth-indicator. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1203178A,1915-04-19,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1203198A,1915-10-15,"Cigar or cigarette holder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1203232A,1916-07-17,"Spark and throttle control mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",0,1,7
US1203345A,1915-05-14,"Beet-harvesting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1203376A,1913-03-13,"Boiler and fire-box construction. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1203412A,1914-01-22,"Hose-rack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1203535A,1916-05-09,"Reliquary memorial. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1203605A,1915-01-18,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1203607A,1914-07-15,"Hose-nozzle. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1203624A,1916-04-17,"Eyeglass-frame. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1203720A,1913-04-07,"Composition for treating rubber tires, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1203739A,1916-04-18,"Cotton ginning, cleaning, and bleaching mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1203826A,1915-09-20,"Glass-cylinder-capping apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1203888A,1915-03-12,"Continuous rolling-mill. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1204025A,1916-01-22,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1204039A,1915-11-10,"Glass-cutting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1204128A,1915-09-02,"Bench-plane guide. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1204237A,1916-06-19,"Cap for fountain or other syringes. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1204276A,1915-08-18,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1204352A,1915-03-13,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1204376A,1916-03-03,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1204393A,1915-11-20,"Dispensing and recording apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1204448A,1916-02-11,"Cleaner for carpets and the like. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1204449A,1916-06-14,"Eyeglass-mounting. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1204464A,1914-05-25,"Meter-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1204642A,1916-04-08,"Chin-rest for violins. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1204650A,1912-10-19,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1204863A,1916-02-09,"Antiskid device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1204864A,1913-05-16,"Jacquard-machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1204922A,1916-02-17,"Felt-skiving machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1204990A,1916-03-21,"Cigar-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1205021A,1916-11-14,"Antiskid device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1205094A,1916-03-22,"Cigar-vending machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1205279A,1915-07-14,"Carpenter's house-bracket. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1205473A,1915-08-10,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1205503A,1915-12-17,"Continuous heating-furnace. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1205522A,1915-08-30,"Bake-pan. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1205587A,1912-04-01,"Meter-gland. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1205695A,1915-12-28,"Grocer's cabinet. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1205704A,1915-03-31,"Continuous gas-calorimeter. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1205795A,1915-12-08,"Chuck or vise. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1205926A,1915-04-26,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1205942A,1915-04-08,"Cartridge-casing. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1205984A,1915-09-08,"Hose. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1205987A,1914-04-14,"Hose attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1206094A,1914-08-12,"Barometer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1206236A,1915-01-29,"Cap-feeding mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1206339A,1916-02-11,"Dimmer for headlights. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1206361A,1914-04-01,"Jack for automobiles. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1206393A,1914-04-10,"Meter test-block. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1206394A,1915-05-08,"Meter test-block. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1206420A,1916-07-27,"Yarn-coating device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1206514A,1915-09-15,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1206627A,1915-11-17,"Meter-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1206638A,1914-10-28,"Hacksaw and frame therefor. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1207064A,1916-06-13,"Plier-wrench. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1207089A,1915-10-28,"Antiskid device for vehicle-wheels. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1207167A,1915-04-09,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1207173A,1916-05-26,"Mill-liner. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1207174A,1916-05-27,"Mill-liner. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1207264A,1916-07-20,"Silencer for firearms. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1207333A,1916-01-05,"Torpedo construction. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1207357A,1915-09-30,"Carpenter's plane. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1207392A,1915-12-13,"Hose connection. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1207526A,1916-05-22,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1207540A,1914-11-12,"Antiskid tire-chain. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1207631A,1916-01-12,"Cigar-lighter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1207784A,1913-11-29,"Process of weighting silk with hæmatoxylin. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1207867A,1914-11-20,"Glass-casting table. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1207896A,1911-05-12,"Glass-grinding apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1207935A,1916-03-30,"Carpenter's square. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1208124A,1913-06-06,"Jeweler's crucible. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1208189A,1915-12-07,"Receptacle for powdered materials, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,8
US1208202A,1916-02-14,"Shears with detachable cutting-blades. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1208212A,1912-08-01,"Cap and seal for jars, bottles, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US1208224A,1914-08-21,"Chuck-coupling. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1208293A,1915-05-07,"Bill and correspondence sheet. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1208368A,1915-11-20,"Glazier's fastening device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1208417A,1915-09-25,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1208424A,1915-07-28,"Eyeglass-chain reel. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1208564A,1916-04-08,"Continuous trolley connections for bridges. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1208577A,1916-03-27,"Solenoid. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1208602A,1913-10-01,"Meter apparatus. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1208619A,1916-05-15,"Device for regulating incubators, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1208801A,1915-12-29,"Cleaner for wind-shields. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1208811A,1915-04-30,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1208849A,1915-07-23,"Scaffold-bracket. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1208978A,1912-10-21,"Glass-article discharge and cut-off mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US1209038A,1915-04-19,"Hose-rack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1209039A,1915-02-23,"Apparatus for pouring steel and producing ingots, bars, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1209123A,1916-02-21,"Miner's check-holder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1209136A,1916-06-08,"Cartridge receptacle or belt. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1209292A,1913-03-19,"Cigar-tip. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1209374A,1916-05-26,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1209423A,1916-04-01,"Dyad dye. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1209572A,1916-02-24,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1209596A,1916-02-07,"Cigar-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1209635A,1915-04-24,"Glass-blowing machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1209650A,1916-01-18,"Turret attachment for machine-tools. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1209870A,1916-05-04,"Bill-folder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1210022A,1915-11-15,"Dispensing and mixing device. 
     ","['VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210093A,1915-12-13,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1210120A,1916-05-27,"Rod connection for locomoitves. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210128A,1916-04-29,"Shears. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1210129A,1916-07-10,"Shears. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1210325A,1916-03-27,"Miner's pick. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1210344A,1913-08-11,"Knit fabric. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1210345A,1913-08-11,"Knit fabric. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1210363A,1916-05-05,"Boiler and other furnace. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210364A,1916-05-05,"Boiler and other furnace. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210399A,1916-03-14,"Cap-opening tool. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210586A,1915-06-26,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1210588A,1916-10-07,"Baker's mixture. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1210599A,1915-08-27,"Cap-retainer for deformable tubes, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1210600A,1915-10-22,"Cap-retainer for deformable tubes. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1210625A,1917-01-02,Joseph m ,"['PROPN', 'VERB']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1210634A,1916-04-15,"Glove-cleaning machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210694A,1915-11-30,"Runner for draft-tongues. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1210710A,1915-03-23,"Continuous controlling mechanism for vehicles. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1210776A,1913-06-10,"Jacquard embroidery-machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1210850A,1915-06-05,"Cleaner for kitchen utensils. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210879A,1913-11-26,"Gang lawn-mower. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1210881A,1912-09-26,"Yarn-changing mechanism for knitting-machines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1210931A,1916-06-29,"Oiler for die-stocks. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1210958A,1914-04-01,"Cotton-harvesting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1210965A,1913-12-10,"Boiler compound. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1211098A,1914-08-13,"Dish and kettle scraper. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1211111A,1916-03-01,"Cleaner for tumblers for metal castings, buttons, and other articles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US1211358A,1916-06-20,"Harrow attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1211372A,1914-07-24,"Yarn-changing mechanism for knitting-machines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1211466A,1914-05-14,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1211489A,1914-11-25,"Label cutting and folding machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1211506A,1916-04-27,"Moth-nest picker and retriever. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1211533A,1916-03-04,"Bill-fold and card-case. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1211601A,1916-04-21,"Wagon-jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1211613A,1916-02-28,"Rod packing-ring. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1211619A,1916-01-24,"Antiskid or antislip tread. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1211643A,1916-03-22,"Windmill attachment. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1211652A,1916-08-21,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1211684A,1915-07-20,"Glass casket. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1211698A,1915-04-12,"Cleaner for automobile wind-shields. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1211755A,1916-12-04,"Boiler and other furnace. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1211896A,1914-10-31,"Kite-trolley. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1211955A,1915-12-30,"Endless-film and reel device for exhibiting pictures, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1212212A,1916-05-18,"Bob-sled. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1212222A,1914-11-19,"Cap-spinning and cap-twisting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1212315A,1917-01-16,bjerre ,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1212656A,1916-06-19,"Pure-culture apparatus for yeast, mucorini, molds, bacilli, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,16
US1212665A,1915-08-31,"Cap-making and bottling machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1212671A,1915-09-14,"Clasp for hose-supporters. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1212817A,1915-03-17,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1212844A,1916-03-22,"Continuous filter-press. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1212870A,1916-06-15,"Device for picking up or lifting pins, needles, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1212994A,1916-02-18,"Dispensing match-holder. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1213094A,1916-05-11,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1213110A,1916-02-28,"Hose-coupling for cars. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1213167A,1916-09-26,"Magnetic chuck and casing. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1213191A,1916-03-10,"Method of attaching wooden or louis heels. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1213478A,1916-05-01,"Meter-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1213492A,1915-11-01,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1213513A,1916-05-03,"Butterfly-valve. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1213553A,1916-06-21,"Harrow attachment for gang-plows. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1213594A,1916-10-07,"Grinder counter-shaft. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1213602A,1916-05-23,"Tailor's iron. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1213832A,1915-05-01,"Staining and finishing cabinet. 
     ","['VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1214066A,1916-07-18,"Roof-crown for open-hearth furnaces. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1214078A,1915-05-01,"Meter-testing appliance. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1214089A,1913-01-15,"Glass-casting apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1214130A,1916-03-13,"Hose-clasp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1214153A,1915-11-29,"Cigar-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1214185A,1916-08-11,"Kieselguhr filler and method of preparing. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1214193A,1912-06-19,"Cigar-bunching machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1214194A,1914-06-06,"Cigar-wrapper moistener and container. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1214195A,1912-10-19,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1214202A,1915-04-12,"Glass. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1214331A,1916-09-30,"Hæmocytometer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1214340A,1915-11-15,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1214359A,1915-07-17,"Hose and garment supporter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1214388A,1915-05-24,"Kitchen utensil. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1214437A,1916-03-31,"Runner attachment for motor-vehicles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1214449A,1914-11-07,"Jacquard mechanism for looms. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1214456A,1910-02-03,"Unitary cigarette and match box. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1214460A,1915-09-04,"Corn-cutter, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1214500A,1915-08-17,"Anode for vacuum discharge-tubes. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1214517A,1916-05-03,"Shield for the use of soldiers and others. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1214631A,1915-01-13,"Kitchen utensil. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1214635A,1912-01-25,"Shears. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1214742A,1915-04-07,"Yarn-winding machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1214777A,1916-01-14,"Antiskid device for wheels. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1214895A,1916-07-21,"Cartridge-carrier. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1214918A,1915-06-09,"Jacquard. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1214998A,1914-11-10,"Yarn-sizing machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1215031A,1916-10-16,"Boiler or heater. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1215050A,1915-02-26,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1215119A,1916-07-22,"Handle for cutting-tools, die-stocks, &c. 
US1215128A,1912-11-06,"Collaret-strip. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1215193A,1916-05-31,"Tailor's measuring instrument. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1215212A,1917-02-06,"Continuous-process cooker. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1215260A,1915-03-03,"Cotton-treating apparatus and process. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1215359A,1916-07-29,"Dyes and process of dyeing. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1215444A,1916-03-22,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1215491A,1913-04-19,"Fuse or like device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1215707A,1915-03-13,"Label cutting and folding machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1215796A,1913-01-02,"Hose-nozzle. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1216009A,1916-09-18,"Bob-sled. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1216031A,1915-11-05,"Cigar-package. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1216412A,1913-12-31,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1216506A,1914-09-26,"Knit fabric and method of knitting the same. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1216565A,1915-09-10,"Silencer for combustion-engines of submarines. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1216635A,1916-08-14,"Cap. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1216703A,1913-09-08,"Baker's peel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1216756A,1916-06-12,"Dimmer for electric lamps. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1216827A,1914-05-09,"Thermometer-case. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1216991A,1916-03-02,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1217021A,1916-02-15,"Silencer for internal-combustion engines. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1217060A,1916-12-19,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1217102A,1914-08-06,"Glass-forming machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1217125A,1915-01-22,"Lingerie-clasp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1217136A,1916-06-05,"Runner attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1217142A,1913-06-09,"Glass-blocking machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1217238A,1915-06-22,"Dyes of the triphenylmethane series and process of making same. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US1217289A,1914-06-22,"Cartridge-fuse. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1217320A,1915-05-07,"Automatic jack for vehicles. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1217334A,1916-06-26,"Weigher and sacker. 
     ","['ADV', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1217351A,1915-05-12,"Breaker and drier. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1217408A,1916-09-18,"Cotton-harvesting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1217494A,1913-08-07,"Glass-working machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1217590A,1916-03-21,"Cigar-tip. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1217614A,1913-11-13,"Glass manufacture. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1217635A,1916-02-11,"Glass-molding machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1217647A,1916-06-02,"Traveler's trunk. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1217675A,1916-10-21,"Ornament for christmas trees, decorations, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['DATE', 'PERSON']",1,1,10
US1217899A,1914-12-21,"Meter for steam, air, or other gases. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US1217902A,1915-12-31,"Miner's blasting-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1217923A,1916-06-03,"Machine for packing match-books, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1217966A,1916-05-25,"Cartridge-holder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1217991A,1916-05-05,"Machine for assembling match-books, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1217992A,1916-06-17,"Machine for assembling match-books, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1218000A,1916-04-01,"Machine for assembling match-books, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1218031A,1916-04-05,"Thermometer-case. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1218104A,1916-02-25,"Dimmer device for automobile-headlights. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1218185A,1916-07-18,"Miner's lamp. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1218430A,1915-09-03,"Antiskid device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1218453A,1916-07-28,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1218507A,1916-06-08,"Wrist-pin lubricator. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1218521A,1916-03-21,"Shears for shearing metal. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1218532A,1915-07-07,"Beet-harvesting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1218539A,1916-01-13,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1218565A,1916-05-19,"Tailor's measuring device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1218570A,1916-08-17,"Miner's safety electric lamp. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1218639A,1916-11-04,"Steamer, cleaner, and presser. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1218657A,1916-12-07,"Antiskid device for vehicle-wheels. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1218717A,1913-04-10,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1218830A,1916-05-31,"Cigar-tip cutter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1218860A,1915-01-19,"Beet-harvesting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1218906A,1916-11-18,"Inhaler. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1218978A,1915-12-06,"Apparatus for cooling coffee, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1219083A,1914-06-23,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1219090A,1916-11-01,"Tailor's iron. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1219132A,1912-12-05,"Meter-testing cut-out. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1219299A,1915-12-28,"Bur for treating grindstones. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1219339A,1916-03-22,"Windmill construction. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1219372A,1912-03-30,"Azimuth-chronometer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1219399A,1915-03-08,"Yarn and thread holder for crocheters and knitters. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1219422A,1916-06-07,"Eyeglass-mounting. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1219537A,1916-08-08,"Tapping-chuck. 
     ","['VERB', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1219617A,1914-08-14,"Galvanometer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1219719A,1911-05-10,"Clasp for scarfs, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,7
US1219740A,1916-12-20,"Gear-grinding chuck. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1219846A,1915-11-11,"Dispensing-bin. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1219870A,1916-04-08,"Scaffold-bracket. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1219879A,1915-10-23,"Torpedo and submarine guard. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1219882A,1916-05-19,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1219916A,1914-06-10,"Cap-button. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1219980A,1915-08-10,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1219992A,1916-08-29,"Harrow attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1220010A,1916-08-12,"Process for emulsifying fats and patty substances. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1220090A,1914-08-03,"Mill for removing the shells of grain and the like. 
     ","['VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US1220196A,1915-11-10,"Windmill-engine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1220208A,1916-02-04,"Cartridge. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1220223A,1916-08-10,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1220307A,1916-06-19,"Moistener for internal-combustion engines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1220496A,1915-03-20,"Cigar and cigarette case. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1220597A,1915-05-03,"Marker for lathes and the like. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1220711A,1915-03-02,"Dimmer attachment for automobile-lamps. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1220718A,1915-09-08,"Stoking-door for furnaces, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1220746A,1913-09-03,"Process for the manufacture of aldol. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1220868A,1916-01-29,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1220925A,1916-04-07,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1220940A,1915-08-17,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1221025A,1915-04-23,"Cotton-comber. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1221090A,1916-03-11,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1221099A,1913-08-09,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1221235A,1915-07-19,"Subscriber's telephone-circuit. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1221275A,1915-11-18,"Cartridge fuse. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1221302A,1916-05-12,"Tailor's measuring or fitting coat. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1221398A,1916-05-11,"Cigar-case holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1221424A,1915-10-06,"Cigar-banding machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1221425A,1916-06-03,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1221485A,1916-09-11,"Cleaner for wind-shields and the like. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1221513A,1916-06-13,"Shield or protector. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1221575A,1914-08-03,"Dispensing-bin. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1221634A,1915-10-26,"Cigar. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1221641A,1915-03-10,"Glass. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1221712A,1916-12-28,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1221775A,1916-04-13,"Beet-toppig machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1221851A,1916-06-30,"Boiler-compound feeder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1221914A,1915-09-13,"Baker's peel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1221935A,1916-09-05,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1222008A,1914-12-11,"Cleaner and scalder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1222088A,1915-12-02,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1222253A,1917-02-19,"Method of sterilizing soil for tobacco-plant beds, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1222320A,1916-11-04,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1222322A,1916-09-02,"Bob-sled runner. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1222411A,1916-04-27,"Meter-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1222435A,1916-09-06,"Cigar-case. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1222564A,1915-06-12,"Boiler-skimmer. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1222719A,1915-09-30,"Cigar-can. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1222755A,1915-08-12,"Split safety-post and indicator for double-barrel guns. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1222975A,1915-07-08,"Jack-spooler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1222979A,1916-07-06,"Process and apparatus for refining clay, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1223075A,1914-11-10,"Stand or support for loose-leaf books, &c. 
     ","['VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1223152A,1912-11-08,"Wagon running-gear. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1223362A,1916-05-25,"Cigar and method of blending the same. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1223537A,1915-11-26,"Fabric for mats, rugs, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1223561A,1916-03-17,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1223640A,1915-08-17,"Shears attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1223676A,1916-07-21,"Machine for the manufacture of pipes, cylinders, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1223791A,1916-04-24,"Lineman's device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1223959A,1915-09-17,"Glass-melting pot. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1223991A,1916-12-05,"Miner's cap. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1224049A,1915-10-12,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1224062A,1917-03-16,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1224063A,1914-12-15,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1224342A,1909-05-20,"Multiplex telegraphy. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1224361A,1915-05-03,"Eyeglass construction. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1224406A,1916-09-07,"Mill for grinding or crushing cotton-seed or the like. 
     ","['VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US1224417A,1916-06-28,"Windmill attachment. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1224431A,1916-03-06,"Motorist's eye-shield. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1224537A,1916-08-28,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1224638A,1912-08-29,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1224654A,1914-07-25,"Volumetric meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1224780A,1916-03-14,"Lathe-chuck jaws. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1224889A,1916-02-19,"Turret-lathe. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1224945A,1915-05-20,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1224970A,1916-11-03,"Lineman's shield. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1224985A,1913-05-20,"Heilman comber. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1225016A,1916-08-18,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1225065A,1916-12-20,"Jacquard mechanism. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1225089A,1915-12-01,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1225092A,1916-11-02,"Cigar-case. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1225155A,1916-07-29,"Cotton glove. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1225304A,1917-05-08,Paul a ,"['PROPN', 'PRON']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1225430A,1916-08-03,"Kitchen utensil. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1225444A,1916-05-13,"Runner attachment for vehicles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1225480A,1916-06-12,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1225566A,1916-10-11,"Violin chin-rest. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1225724A,1915-04-23,"Vacuum lifting-cup. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1225822A,1916-12-16,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1225839A,1916-01-18,"Antiskid device for auto-tires. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1225864A,1915-07-16,"Baker's peel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1225952A,1916-02-08,"Holder for sewing-machine bobbins, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,10
US1225983A,1915-12-30,"Barrel calking and renovating machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1226169A,1914-12-21,"Roof-jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1226185A,1916-12-04,"Machine for making box-splints, veneers, shingles, &c. 
US1226237A,1916-11-18,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1226336A,1915-02-02,"Stand or support for loose-leaf books, &c. 
     ","['VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1226353A,1916-05-09,"Bake-pan. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1226394A,1915-11-15,"Iodin compound and method of preparing same. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1226522A,1916-07-10,"Bill-file. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1226592A,1917-05-15,"Continuous exhaust-box for preserve-containing cans. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US1226697A,1913-10-02,"Solenoid for driving adding-machines. 
     ","['ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1226748A,1915-07-01,"Solenoid. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1226897A,1916-03-16,"Label for bottles and other receptacles. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1227004A,1916-06-30,"Bank-check, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1227042A,1914-05-25,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1227333A,1916-05-26,"Shears. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1227354A,1916-01-10,"Steamer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1227359A,1916-10-07,"Violin chin-rest. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1227439A,1917-01-04,"Cartridge-magazine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1227448A,1914-06-06,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1227499A,1916-02-11,"Facing-tool for dressing valve-seats, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1227500A,1916-02-11,"Facing-tool for dressing valve-seats, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1227511A,1915-01-23,"Facing-tool for dressing valve-seats, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1227512A,1915-01-23,"Facing-tool for dressing valve-seats, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1227513A,1915-01-23,"Facing-tool for dressing valve-seats, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1227515A,1916-05-27,"Facing-tool for dressing valve-seats, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1227532A,1914-08-27,"Continuous wire-drawing machinery. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1227587A,1916-08-26,"Flagman's signaling kit. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1227608A,1916-04-11,"Cigar-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1227621A,1916-05-16,"Shearing mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1227652A,1916-10-24,"Cotton-threshing machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1227690A,1913-11-03,"Hose. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1227757A,1916-05-09,"Wagon-body. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1227795A,1916-06-06,"Dimmer for motor-vehicles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1227892A,1915-10-07,"Counter-bin. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1227902A,1916-11-04,"Hacksaw. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1228135A,1917-01-11,"Grinder mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1228185A,1916-05-24,"Silencer and condenser for gasolene-engines. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1228210A,1916-02-26,"Screw-jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1228389A,1916-12-15,"Ray-filter holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1228480A,1915-06-15,"Hose-supporter clasp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1228501A,1916-05-29,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1228503A,1916-11-07,"Apparatus for measuring the hardness of metal, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US1228525A,1916-10-17,"Continuous-rod cigarette-machine. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1228571A,1915-05-22,"Dispensing-carton. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1228660A,1915-06-14,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1228805A,1915-01-08,"Jack or device for spreading cables and the like. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US1228859A,1916-08-22,"Meter-switch. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1228943A,1916-09-06,"Screw-jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1229067A,1915-04-12,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1229100A,1916-05-19,"Automatic sanitary bin for grocers, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1229341A,1916-03-11,"Cap or cover for jars, bottles, glasses, or the like. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US1229369A,1915-07-22,"Knit fabric. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1229434A,1916-04-14,"Silencer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1229467A,1915-05-22,"Cartridge-loading machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1229514A,1916-03-31,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1229620A,1916-08-14,"Cabinet for sewing-machines, type-writers, &c. 
US1229660A,1916-05-29,"Cigar-package. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1229833A,1916-06-06,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1229937A,1916-12-06,"Eyeglass-case. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1229951A,1916-07-05,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1230019A,1915-10-27,"Hose-band. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1230067A,1914-12-14,"Cigar-wrapping machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1230100A,1916-07-31,"Bill-fold. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1230167A,1915-09-23,"Continuous-flow water-heater. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1230238A,1914-09-02,"Dispensing-bin. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1230388A,1917-01-11,"Marker for cigars and the like. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1230424A,1916-10-06,"Glass-feeding table. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1230432A,1916-07-05,"Cigar-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1230469A,1917-05-07,"Sprinkler for automatic fire-extinguishing systems. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1230504A,1917-06-19,Ke witt nelson ,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,3
US1230653A,1917-02-08,"Shelf-marker. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1230758A,1913-09-29,"Glass-securing device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1230854A,1916-08-31,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1230861A,1913-06-16,"Cashier's registering-machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1230867A,1915-02-04,"Hose and the process of making the same. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1230892A,1914-03-30,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1231106A,1917-04-03,"Cartridge-pack for revolvers. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1231114A,1916-06-19,"Shortener for baking foods. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1231181A,1916-10-17,"Antiskid device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1231213A,1915-02-02,"Ray-protector. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1231242A,1916-05-23,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1231322A,1917-01-15,"Chuck for machine-tools. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1231382A,1916-12-20,"Felt welt and method of making same for gloves and the like. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US1231787A,1917-05-22,"Inhaler. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1232027A,1916-01-22,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1232031A,1916-10-12,"Vehicle spring-gear. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1232193A,1917-04-17,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1232270A,1916-05-22,"Banana heater and ripener. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1232366A,1916-07-28,"Glass-cutter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1232385A,1917-02-03,"Kitchen utensil. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1232439A,1917-01-30,"Silencer and connecting medium for elevator-doors. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1232508A,1913-06-04,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1232572A,1917-04-26,"Miner's carbid-lamp. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1232712A,1917-03-03,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1232914A,1916-06-02,"Jack for shoes. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1232939A,1914-09-02,"Bake-pan. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1232992A,1916-07-06,"Cap-vizor. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1232999A,1916-01-19,"Turret tool-post. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1233041A,1916-02-19,"Yarn-package and method of winding same. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1233054A,1916-06-01,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1233071A,1915-09-07,"Cartridge-case for artillery-shells. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1233089A,1916-10-18,"Cranberry-harvesting apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1233158A,1916-10-10,"Eyeglass-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1233202A,1917-02-15,"Barber's hair-clipper. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1233401A,1916-01-19,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1233560A,1917-03-12,"Stay-bolt-heading attachment for pneumatic hammers, &c. 
     ","['VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1233570A,1916-09-30,"Eyeglass-mounting. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1233609A,1917-02-26,"Lingerie-clasp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1233629A,1917-07-17,Addick g ,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1233644A,1915-10-23,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1233662A,1915-06-08,"Cigar bunching and rolling machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1233663A,1916-08-28,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1233750A,1916-02-25,"Hose connection. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1233761A,1917-02-03,"Torpedo steering-gear. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1233902A,1916-11-22,"Oiler for elevator and weight guide-rails. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1233916A,1916-03-10,"Hose-holder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1233980A,1916-07-01,"Lineman's tool. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1234019A,1916-10-09,"Turret-indexing mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1234065A,1916-12-26,"Vulcanizer for rubber tires. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1234156A,1916-12-13,"Process of making aldol. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1234201A,1915-01-26,"Boiler-operating method and means. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1234209A,1915-09-10,"Cigar-mouthpiece. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1234243A,1916-03-02,"Combined post-puller, jack, and wire-stretcher. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1234257A,1917-02-03,"Continuous heat-treating apparatus. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1234266A,1915-04-12,"Composition of matter for cleaning textile fabrics, leather, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1234282A,1916-08-02,"Bricklayer's line-stretching gage. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1234338A,1916-08-14,"Hose-nozzle. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1234385A,1915-09-17,"Hammer-lock for tabulating mechanism. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1234392A,1914-12-01,"Meter for measuring the flow of liquids. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1234405A,1915-12-01,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1234507A,1913-07-02,"Dish and holder for ice-cream. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1234562A,1916-05-08,"Glass-grinding machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1234703A,1915-07-14,"Knit article and method of making the same. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1234735A,1916-09-19,"Cap. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1234744A,1916-10-30,"Split pulley. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1234768A,1913-07-12,"Cap-finger. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1234812A,1916-05-23,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1234918A,1916-04-19,"Monorail switch. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1235038A,1915-04-10,"Kitchen utensil. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1235088A,1916-04-04,"Cotton-tramper. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1235105A,1916-07-18,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1235111A,1916-11-21,"Multicylinder internal-combustion engine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1235200A,1916-01-26,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1235367A,1916-12-02,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1235466A,1917-04-13,"Hose-nozzle attachment for brushes. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1235517A,1913-08-25,"Silencer for flushing-tanks. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1235556A,1913-11-05,"Cotton tramper and baler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1235644A,1917-05-02,"Moistener for envelops, postage-stamps, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,11
US1235661A,1917-06-05,"Freezing fish and other goods in cases or freezing-molds. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US1235692A,1916-02-24,"Glass-cover. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1235801A,1914-02-16,"Carpenter's computing-scale. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1235862A,1916-04-04,"Cigar-vending humidor. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1235876A,1916-10-24,"Hose connection. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1235878A,1916-02-05,"Hose. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1235916A,1916-10-30,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1235921A,1917-01-19,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1235968A,1913-02-06,"Antiskid device for vehicles. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1236154A,1913-11-26,"Boiler-feeding means. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1236155A,1913-11-26,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1236175A,1916-09-18,"Jewel and pivot protector. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1236200A,1916-12-05,"Turret attachment for lathes. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1236231A,1916-09-27,"Boiler-stay. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236265A,1917-01-23,"Meter-reading device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1236312A,1917-03-03,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236343A,1917-03-13,"Runner attachment for automobiles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1236364A,1916-03-14,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236440A,1917-02-14,"Electric heating-pad for carbureters, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1236452A,1916-07-24,"Eyeglass-mounting. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236453A,1916-08-16,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1236482A,1916-01-28,"Split pin box for sorting-machines. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1236499A,1916-11-18,"Antiskid device for automobiles, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1236500A,1916-11-26,"Antiskid device for automobiles, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1236546A,1915-11-01,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236634A,1916-06-16,"Cigar-box. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1236734A,1916-05-26,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1236746A,1916-03-22,"Continuous liquid-separator. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1236809A,1916-11-06,"Dimmer for auto-headlights. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1236817A,1916-08-30,"Carpenter's square. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1236822A,1916-01-26,"Yarn-carrier. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236840A,1916-03-17,"Continuous trolley system. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1236997A,1916-09-01,"Turret tool-post. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1237040A,1916-09-13,"Kitchen utensil. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1237102A,1916-01-22,"Cigar-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1237162A,1917-04-20,"Gang bread-cutter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1237192A,1917-01-05,"Leucotriarylmethanazo dyestuffs and a process of making same. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1237233A,1911-10-23,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1237256A,1915-12-13,"Yarn-feeding device for knitting-machines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1237282A,1914-05-04,"Glass tank-furnace. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1237283A,1914-06-04,"Glass-tank. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1237289A,1917-03-23,"Meter-seal. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1237367A,1915-10-18,"Yarn-winding machinery. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1237379A,1916-12-04,"Meter-testing construction. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1237410A,1914-07-17,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1237449A,1913-05-20,"Miner's lamp. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1237450A,1916-04-06,"Miner's gas-lamp. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1237481A,1917-02-19,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1237516A,1916-04-28,"Cutter or miller for thread-cutting or milling machines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US1237559A,1916-08-22,"Balancer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1237637A,1915-10-15,"Acetylene-lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1237761A,1916-10-26,"Bottle cap and stopper. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1237762A,1916-01-17,"Wheelwright-machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1237770A,1916-08-24,"Antiskid device for vehicle-wheels. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1237946A,1917-01-25,"Wagon-body. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1237957A,1915-04-09,"Boiler fusible plug. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1237958A,1916-08-02,"Tailor's measuring instrument. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1238032A,1916-12-13,"Acetylene miner's lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1238052A,1914-06-18,"Yarn-feeding mechanism for knitting-machines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1238192A,1916-06-24,"Zigzag radiator. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1238301A,1915-11-20,"Antiskid device for automobiles. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1238314A,1917-01-27,"Cap or point for netting-needles. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1238340A,1915-11-08,"Adaptable or convertible cover or tarpaulin. 
     ","['ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1238400A,1917-02-16,"Barber's shears. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1238490A,1917-01-23,"Antiskid device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1238496A,1915-11-15,"Eyeglass-holder. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1238629A,1914-12-15,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1238669A,1916-12-20,"Glass-protector. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1238716A,1913-02-03,"Yarn take-up and tension for knitting-machines. 
     ","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US1238729A,1916-09-06,"Acetylene miner's lamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1238749A,1916-07-15,"Wagon-sign. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1238863A,1917-03-14,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1238928A,1916-01-27,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1239002A,1916-03-17,"Cigar and stogy bunching and rolling machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1239004A,1916-11-09,"Cigar and stogy making machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1239026A,1916-08-05,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1239028A,1917-04-09,"Rod packing-ring. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1239066A,1916-07-27,"Cleaner for conveyer-belts. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1239090A,1915-01-26,"Wheeled plow, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1239172A,1916-08-14,"Hose-coupling for railway air-brakes. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1239186A,1917-02-12,"Speeder mechanism for motor-boats. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1239246A,1917-05-02,"Baker's oven. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1239267A,1915-11-15,"Automatic water-feed device for steam-generators, oil-burners, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,17
US1239376A,1917-05-18,"Cap or head-covering. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1239432A,1917-03-27,"Cotton-cleaning apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1239546A,1916-06-21,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1239614A,1916-10-03,"Cotton harvesting and cleaning machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1239640A,1917-02-23,"Jack-truck. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1239680A,1914-09-05,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1239742A,1916-05-16,"Carpenter's square. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1239801A,1914-12-03,"Cigar-lighter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1239873A,1915-01-30,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1239939A,1916-01-05,"Jewel-grinding machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1239959A,1916-01-26,"Glove-former. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1239968A,1916-05-10,"Apparatus for applying fastenings to envelops, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1240104A,1915-03-25,"Protector for wound-yarn-mass supports, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1240106A,1916-12-21,"Sepulcher. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1240123A,1915-10-01,"Manometer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1240183A,1916-07-05,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1240185A,1917-04-09,"Continuous glass-drawing apparatus. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1240221A,1917-04-23,"Rod trimmer or reducer. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1240255A,1916-05-31,"Bill-payment form. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1240272A,1915-03-19,"Chlorate explosive of the sprengel class. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1240278A,1917-05-31,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1240283A,1917-01-02,"Dimmer-light-switch support. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1240292A,1917-07-13,"Strut for automatic sprinkler-heads. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1240299A,1915-01-02,"Glass-holder for headlights. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1240359A,1917-04-27,"Corpse-carrier. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1240363A,1916-12-04,"Meter-testing-switch construction. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1240533A,1916-11-23,"Eyeglass-mounting. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1240536A,1915-07-02,"Eyeglass-case. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1240625A,1917-07-06,"Yarn-moistening device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1240652A,1915-12-10,"Hose-supporter. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1240728A,1914-06-22,"Mitt. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1240789A,1911-12-19,"Split clencher demountable rim and locking and alining device therefor. 
     ","['VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US1240797A,1913-03-01,"Meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1240937A,1917-07-13,"Glass-tank floater. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1240957A,1914-06-26,"Manufacture of cylinders, pipes, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1241049A,1916-09-14,"Combined place-marking and advertising device for directories, &c. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1241066A,1916-12-16,"Antiskid device for wheel-tires. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1241070A,1917-03-09,"Apparatus for grading roads, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1241198A,1917-05-21,"Harvester for cabbage and similar plants. 
     ","['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1241221A,1916-02-18,"Pot for mustard, jam, marmalade, honey, &c. 
US1241432A,1916-11-20,"Split nut. 
     ","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1241590A,1916-10-20,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1241591A,1916-10-20,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1241597A,1916-05-05,"Boiler-repair plug. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1241626A,1914-10-26,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1241654A,1913-10-30,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1241657A,1917-02-09,"Clasp for hand-bags. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1241884A,1916-11-08,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1241918A,1916-11-09,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1241922A,1916-11-18,"Cartridge-carrier. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1242015A,1914-12-14,"Hose-storing apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1242047A,1915-09-18,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1242109A,1915-03-12,"Barber's chair. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1242110A,1915-03-12,"Barber's chair. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1242211A,1916-09-09,"Cap. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1242280A,1915-03-11,"Keyboard mechanism for cash-registers. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US1242444A,1914-02-19,"Glass manufacture. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1242599A,1916-04-14,"Eyeglass and spectacle mounting. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1242657A,1917-02-16,"Yarn-holding reel. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1242770A,1916-11-21,"Remedy for the bee disease called the european foul brood. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'ORG']",1,1,12
US1242807A,1916-09-27,"Split shaft for use on paper-machines. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US1242840A,1916-07-19,"Vacuum bean-picker. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1242869A,1917-03-26,"Volumetric meter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1243032A,1916-02-21,"Label folding and marking machine. 
     ","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1243046A,1917-02-26,"Cotton chopper or blocker. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1243058A,1915-03-08,"Bat-forming machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1243090A,1916-08-21,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1243158A,1917-03-19,"Cigar and cigarette holder. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1243180A,1917-01-23,"Grinder attachment for lathes. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1243253A,1916-07-27,"Cartridge. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1243466A,1916-01-28,"Oculist's testing-frame. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1243532A,1916-08-12,"Carpenter's work-support. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1243540A,1916-11-01,"Shears. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1243586A,1916-05-26,"Mechanism for operating air-compressors, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1243625A,1916-05-22,"Roach hive or trap. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1243848A,1917-06-07,"Torpedo or mine guard. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1244016A,1916-07-24,"Harrow and truck. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1244094A,1916-10-05,"Compositor's type-setter channel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1244253A,1916-12-21,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1244280A,1914-03-04,"Process for the manufacture of cement, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US1244465A,1916-11-03,"Hose suspension. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1244493A,1917-10-30,hamilton ,['PROPN'],['PERSON'],1,1,1
US1244494A,1916-05-01,"Chuck for jar-closures. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1244504A,1915-02-04,"Continuous zinc-smelter. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1244556A,1915-08-05,"Glass for headlights. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1244577A,1917-03-01,"Hose-clamp. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1244666A,1917-05-12,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1244685A,1916-03-25,"Transplit demountable rim. 
     ","['VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1244818A,1915-08-07,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1244964A,1917-08-08,"Jack-operating attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1245005A,1917-04-03,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1245009A,1917-10-30,van poindexter ,"['PROPN', 'PROPN']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US1245012A,1916-12-01,"Cigar-slitting machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1245038A,1916-11-17,"Meter-testing appurtenance. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1245049A,1917-02-24,"Knob bolt-lock. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1245108A,1917-01-05,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1245175A,1917-04-20,"Checkrein attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1245246A,1914-04-01,"Cotton-picking spindle. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1245262A,1912-07-16,"Glass-shaping machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1245345A,1917-07-09,"Hacksaw. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1245400A,1917-02-06,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1245423A,1917-03-02,"Clasp for spectacle-cases. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1245491A,1915-11-27,"Hose-reel. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1245530A,1916-12-30,"Spacing-table machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1245614A,1915-08-28,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1245683A,1917-03-07,"Windmill-coupling. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1245714A,1913-10-18,"Windmill pump connection. 
     ","['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1245829A,1917-04-02,"Removable heating plant for incubators, &c. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1245912A,1915-12-07,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1246003A,1917-03-29,"Continuous mixer. 
     ","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US1246008A,1917-07-25,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1246058A,1917-01-17,"Bass attachment for zithers. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1246231A,1916-02-28,"Printer's blanket. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1246234A,1917-05-03,"Gang lawn-mower. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1246484A,1916-12-30,"Windmill. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1246504A,1917-07-11,"Jack. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1246525A,1917-06-01,"Boiler-skimmer. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1246654A,1916-10-10,"Clasp for garters, wrist-bracelets, &c. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,11
US1246660A,1915-04-06,"Cartridge. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1246728A,1917-08-10,"Dimmer for automobile-lamps. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1246764A,1911-05-18,"Glass manufacture. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1247032A,1917-05-14,"Shovel, scoop, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US1247390A,1916-09-20,"Bill-posting blanking device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1247399A,1916-06-23,"Solenoid-operated switch. 
     ","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1247464A,1916-02-17,"Hose-coupling. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1247476A,1916-11-06,"Hem and tuck gage for skirts. 
     ","['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US1247529A,1916-02-23,"Antiskid attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1247568A,1916-06-01,"Assembler-box elevator for type-line-casting machines. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US1247576A,1916-10-23,"Cigar-vending machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1248000A,1916-12-18,"Cotton-threshing machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1248174A,1916-04-12,"Yarn-measuring device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1248206A,1912-12-05,"Yarn cutter and holder mechanism for circular-knitting machines. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US1248212A,1916-01-14,"Antiskid device. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1248260A,1916-01-19,"Meter protective device. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1248356A,1916-03-27,"Boiler. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US1248372A,1917-04-26,"Glass-feeding system for drawing apparatus. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US1248664A,1912-11-18,"Glass-blowing machine. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1248673A,1916-10-05,"Harrow attachment. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US1248680A,1917-01-06,"Vacuum conveying apparatus. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US1248893A,1917-06-21,"Eyeglass-case. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1248896A,1917-02-28,"Combination automobile jack and roller. 
     ","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1249028A,1917-04-28,"Bricks and other molded articles. 
     ","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1249038A,1917-01-30,"Hose-protector. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US1249074A,1916-11-03,"Hose-coupling lock. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US1249105A,1916-11-10,"Cigar case and cutter. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1249107A,1917-07-06,"Torpedo guard-net. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1249182A,1916-12-27,"Headlight shield or dimmer. 
     ","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US1249246A,1917-02-14,"Cleaner for wind-shields. 
     ","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1249289A,1917-04-04,"Dispensing-top for containers. 
     ","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US1249290A,1906-06-23,"Process for making concrete structures, dams, walls, bridges, conduits, sewers, pavements, &c. 
US1249300A,1916-07-29,"Chuck. 
     ","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US1249357A,1916-05-16,"Fastener for shoes, gloves, &c. 
     ","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US1249380A,1916-01-03,"Hose-coupling. 
