patent_number,date,title,spacy_pos,spacy_label,is_prpn_spacy,is_person_spacy,spacy_pos_len
US3800001A,1972-09-28,Ethyl chloride pyrolysis and use of ethylene and hydrogen chloride in alkylation,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3800031A,1972-04-06,Process for preparing silica hydrogel,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3800218A,1973-02-07,R. f. impedance bridge for measuring reflection coefficient,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3800224A,1973-02-20,Automatic frequency control for f. m. transmitter,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3800262A,1971-12-28,Fuse cartridge,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3800325A,1972-08-14,Disc drive for memory disc cartridge,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3800362A,1971-10-12,Patty machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3800425A,1972-03-20,Boom orientation and load capacity indicator,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3800501A,1972-02-03,Cap feeding apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3800564A,1971-10-13,Yarn plating method and apparatus for circular knitting machines,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3800565A,1972-08-31,Continuous yarn dyeing machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3800631A,1972-05-11,Fe Al Cr Y Co ALLOY,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3800634A,1972-01-31,Hose clamp tool,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3800639A,1972-12-29,Glass cutter,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3800642A,1971-03-23,Yarn cutting device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3800666A,1972-06-12,Solenoid operated servomotor,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3800741A,1973-02-12,Chuck for crown closure lining apparatus,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3800779A,1973-02-05,Melt cycle control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3800885A,1972-12-21,Bulldozer lift cylinder arrangement,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3800958A,1972-08-11,Bookrack,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3800981A,1972-05-08,Cartridge loading golf tee dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3800982A,1972-06-20,Metered liquid dispenser,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3800984A,1971-11-26,Sampler and diluter,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3800993A,1971-02-18,Capstan tensioner,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3801030A,1970-06-30,Yarn winding process and a machine adapted for carrying out same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3801034A,1972-09-13,Yarn traversing drum used for yarn winders,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3801038A,1972-09-07,Chuck for a tube or sleeve and serving as a bobbin support,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3801059A,1971-06-22,Mould for use in filling of hollow bodies with foam and for the production of hard-foam articles,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,20
US3801063A,1971-01-25,Solenoid actuated valve for anhydrous ammonia flow meters,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3801221A,1970-09-21,Impeller and method for manufacturing said impeller,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3801295A,1972-08-01,Mica glass-ceramics,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3801355A,1971-04-27,Plasma deposition of thin layers on substrates,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3801411A,1971-08-20,"Glass drawing method,apparatus,and glass article","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3801466A,1971-12-02,Uric acid assay and reagents therefor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3801519A,1972-09-21,Aqueous suspension polymerization in the presence of c3-c4 hydroxyalkyl carboxymethyl cellulose ethers as dispersing agents,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,18
US3801556A,1972-06-19,Vinyl chloride based polymers manufactured by initiators prepared in-situ,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3801560A,1972-02-23,Continuous emulsion polymerization of copolymerization of vinyl chloride without heavy metal salts,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3801566A,1970-06-17,Removal of lactams from a medium which contains concentrated sulphuric acid or sulphur trioxide,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PRON', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3801641A,1966-05-31,Quaternary ammonium salts,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3801676A,1971-08-12,"Polyetherpolythiols,method of preparation and mixtures of polythioether-polythiols with epoxide resins","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3801862A,1972-11-06,Plasma cell voltage control circuit,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3801878A,1971-03-09,Glass switching device using an ion impermeable glass active layer,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3801887A,1973-04-10,Brushless variable speed drive for a. c. synchronous motor,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3801920A,1972-10-16,A. c. control circuit,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3801921A,1970-06-05,Amplifier arrangement,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3802029A,1972-10-13,Scallop eviscerator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3802036A,1972-09-05,Yarn bulking jet,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3802091A,1973-05-07,D.c. shutdown circuitry for i.c controlled dryer,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'PERSON']",1,1,9
US3802144A,1972-08-16,Through- and under-draining flooring modules,"['X', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3802150A,1970-09-04,Mill liner handler,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3802270A,1971-10-01,Sampler and method of sampling,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3802323A,1971-06-14,Piston and piston rod assembly for hydraulic jack,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,9
US3802342A,1971-07-06,Armor piercing fragment and launcher,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3802436A,1971-06-30,"Colostomy, ileostomy or ureterstomy bag","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3802543A,1971-09-13,Jewel bearings for printer heads and the like,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3802658A,1972-07-19,Jack stand,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3802670A,1970-11-05,Continuous mixer for thermoplastic resin,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3802713A,1972-03-22,Lever operated collet chuck,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3802744A,1972-08-24,Split rim assembly for earthworking vehicles,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3802953A,1970-12-16,Glass fibers treated with alkaline compatible chromic complexes and reinforced elastomers produced therefrom,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3802962A,1971-01-20,Neutron flux measurement installation for liquid-cooled nuclear reactors,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3802964A,1970-11-27,Continuous measurement of pulp properties,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3802980A,1962-03-19,Continuous filament web and method of manufacturing the same,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3803069A,1968-05-03,"Glass fiber size of curable,blocked polyurethane emulsion with amino silane","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3803077A,1972-06-28,Resin molding composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3803086A,1973-02-05,Vinyl-substituted siloxane and siloxazane polymers,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3803306A,1970-04-06,Animal feed composition containing antibiotic am374 as a growth promoter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3803399A,1972-07-20,Target illuminator,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3803413A,1972-05-01,Infrared non-contact system for inspection of infrared emitting components in a device,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3803503A,1973-05-11,Neutralized driver amplifier circuit,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3803527A,1971-09-07,Fuse construction and mounting,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3803620A,1973-04-20,Continuous scanning waveguide antenna,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3803876A,1970-10-15,Glassware dimpling,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3803878A,1971-04-08,Yarn cutter for circular knitting machines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3803914A,1972-06-09,Flow meter for parenteral solutions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3804034A,1972-05-09,Armor,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3804112A,1972-07-20,Surge control for a compressor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3804128A,1972-11-14,Dobby for looms,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3804147A,1971-03-30,Continuous rotary method of casting metal utilizing a magnetic field,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3804284A,1972-03-30,Cap for storage vessels,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3804335A,1973-05-21,Vaneless supersonic nozzle,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3804345A,1972-09-15,Jaw crusher die mounting,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3804494A,1971-10-01,Telephoto lens systems having small telephoto ratio,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3804569A,1972-09-08,Spinneret wiper,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3804703A,1970-04-21,Glass-to-metal seals comprising relatively high expansion metals,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3804704A,1971-12-27,Mica paper laminates,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3804706A,1970-07-29,Inorganic fiber board with binder of thermosetting resin and thermoplastic vinylic resin,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3804729A,1972-06-19,Electrolyte and process for electro-depositing copper,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3804785A,1971-02-15,Polyvinyl alcohol compositions containing amylose and/or amylitol of low molecular weight,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3804813A,1971-02-23,Continuous process for forming polylactams,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3804814A,1970-12-23,Vinyl chloride copolymers suitable for crosslinking,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3804830A,1968-11-26,"Alkyl 1,n-(substituted alkylene)-2-benzimidazolecarbamates","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3804905A,1969-05-28,Phenyl propargyl thioethers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3804920A,1972-03-29,Resin compositions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3805165A,1972-06-08,Heterodyne amplifier circuits,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3805166A,1972-10-20,Squelch circuit with time constant controlled by signal level,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3805177A,1972-11-24,Amplifier circuit having variable automatic gain control,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3805343A,1972-03-30,Yarn treating apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3805368A,1970-07-27,Barometer capsule and method of manufacture,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3805389A,1971-12-17,Cotton roll holder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3805433A,1973-01-02,Cartridge feeder attachment,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3805434A,1972-07-11,Barrel adapter for shot gun to rifle conversion,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3805441A,1971-01-08,Strut members and connector rings with imperforate pierceable walls,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3805443A,1973-01-12,Yo yo construction,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3805516A,1971-01-21,Cartridge actuated tools,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3805560A,1972-06-23,"Steamer, more particularly loop steamer","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3805607A,1971-08-27,Yarn changing mechanism,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3805609A,1970-10-24,Flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3805697A,1971-10-01,Cartridge for printer character strip,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3805732A,1972-10-04,Intruder repeller and burglar alarm,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3805745A,1972-05-31,Boiler for use with gaseous fuel or oil,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3805770A,1971-07-22,Endoscope guide and lubricating means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3805811A,1972-06-29,Styler dryer for hair curling,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3805848A,1971-12-22,Hose construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3805877A,1972-09-15,Continuous casting apparatus employing an oval-ended pouring spout,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3805985A,1970-10-01,Resin coated glass article having improved anti-shock durability,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3806010A,1972-09-22,Scabbard mount for motorcycles and other vehicles,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3806049A,1972-08-09,Cartridge roller bearing roll mounts for roller mill,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3806054A,1972-07-28,Ribbon de-reeler,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3806069A,1971-06-10,Aircrew escape systems,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3806122A,1973-03-09,"Target disc, tethered ball & game initiating spinner","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3806165A,1971-06-14,Continuous manifold assembly,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3806260A,1971-12-14,Mitt,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3806329A,1971-07-14,Glass drawing method and apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3806331A,1970-12-23,Glass heating and tempering apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3806369A,1968-11-13,Light metal-sulfur organic electrolyte cell,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3806395A,1972-09-15,Label applicator support structure,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3806447A,1972-08-03,Continuous low pressure catalytic reforming process,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3806460A,1972-01-10,Cleaner compositions,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3806550A,1972-05-08,Method and apparatus for separating and concentrating diethyl ether and ethyl mercaptan from a composite stream thereof,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,18
US3806785A,1969-06-10,Brushless d. c. electric machine,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3806832A,1972-12-21,R. c. oscillator,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3806862A,1969-08-26,Amplifier for sonar transmitter,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3806913A,1971-06-23,Gyroscopic north-seeking device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3807080A,1970-02-03,Fish de-hooker,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3807086A,1971-12-08,Bending figure,"['VERB', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3807214A,1972-05-01,Bending machine,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3807460A,1972-10-12,Heald motion for looms,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3807475A,1971-03-17,Bias ply tire with carcass reinforcements,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3807571A,1972-04-12,Membranes for reverse osmosis,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3807601A,1972-09-15,Tablet dispenser using a flexible partition,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3807604A,1972-02-24,Frozen gel slicing method and apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3807621A,1971-04-02,Dispensing spout of a carton box,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3807647A,1972-06-15,Yarn take-up arrangement,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3807694A,1972-03-06,Vehicle service jack,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3807745A,1973-03-15,Keyless drill chuck,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3807869A,1971-12-07,Split field leveling instrument,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3807871A,1972-06-12,Tristimulus filter colorimeter with improved meter zero setting means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3807883A,1970-03-17,Label holding device for loose leaf binders,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3807924A,1971-04-10,Volumetric injector particularly for delivering batches of fluid plastics material,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3807979A,1972-05-08,Quaternary ammonium silicate for polishing silicon metal,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3807983A,1971-04-02,Quaternary ammonium aquatic herbicides,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3808013A,1972-07-13,Alumina refractory composition,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3808015A,1970-11-23,Alumina fiber,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3808023A,1972-06-27,PIGMENTARY TiO{11,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3808027A,1972-03-29,Silica surfaced films,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3808033A,1970-01-27,Continuous metallic strip hot-dip metal coating apparatus,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3808078A,1970-01-05,"Glass fiber cable, method of making, and its use in the manufacture of track vehicles","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,18
US3808103A,1970-08-11,Bacteria receptacles,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3808117A,1970-02-13,Continuous leaching-precipitation method and apparatus,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3808154A,1970-11-16,Glass used for face panels of color television picture tubes,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3808158A,1971-07-20,Amphoteric thermally regenerable ion exchange resins,"['ADJ', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3808175A,1967-02-16,Polyvinyl dicarboxylic acid resin products and uses,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3808212A,1970-07-30,N-(1-bicyclic aryl-propyl-2)-n'-bicyclic aryl-piperazines,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3808235A,1970-03-26,Alkyl beta-(n'-2-tetrahydropyranylureido)acrylates,"['PROPN', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'X', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3808244A,1968-05-27,Perfluoroalkylamido-alkyl and alkylthio esters of fumaric acid and other ethylenically unsaturated polybasic acids and polymers thereof,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,19
US3808255A,1970-09-30,Styryl dyestuffs,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3808288A,1971-12-06,Pressure-sensitive adhesives based on epihalohydrin polymer and polyketone resins,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3808293A,1972-01-05,"Vinyl chloride polymer,acrylic polymer and acrylonitrile/butadiene/styrene polymer compositions","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SYM', 'PROPN', 'SYM', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3808324A,1970-08-31,Continuous process for scrubbing so2 from a gas stream with h2 regeneration and co2 stripping,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3808325A,1970-02-09,Continuous process for scrubbing so2 from a gas stream with co regeneration and co2 stripping,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3808452A,1973-06-04,Power supply system having redundant d. c. power supplies,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3808640A,1970-06-03,Card clothing arrangement,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3808651A,1972-11-21,Clasp,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3808688A,1971-07-26,Centric relating device and inspection means,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3808726A,1972-07-24,Spinner lure rig,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3808842A,1972-03-15,Manufacture of lady{40 s panty hose,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3808886A,1972-09-25,Volumetric flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3808937A,1972-04-19,Screw head,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3808959A,1971-10-26,Carton assembling apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3809131A,1970-06-24,Yarn carrier for a weaving machine,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3809148A,1972-11-30,Continuous casting die with compatible lining and jacket,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3809234A,1971-11-08,Glass shipping rack,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3809326A,1971-10-22,Bobbin support chuck,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3809370A,1972-05-23,Bottle cap seal,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3809403A,1969-01-13,Shaft for conventional golf club,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3809410A,1971-02-16,Continuous card form,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3809430A,1972-05-18,Slope cave leaching of exposed or near-surface mineralized deposits,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3809440A,1971-10-28,Shaft for depositing fibre flock,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3809542A,1971-02-19,Glass ceramic materials,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3809839A,1972-01-19,Momentary switch with serpentine movable and coil spring stationary contacts,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3810032A,1971-11-19,Amplifier device with remote power supply,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3810074A,1972-06-14,Electrical (h. v.) distributor cap contacts for spark ignited combustion engines,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3810311A,1972-06-15,Locating stop for work to be machined or the like,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3810489A,1973-02-05,Solenoid latched diaphragm fuel shut-off valve assembly,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3810490A,1972-10-30,Hose support,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3810507A,1969-05-30,Continuous casting plant for slabs,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3810588A,1971-07-28,"Dispensing container enabling a coil of a resilient, edged metal band to be formed therein","['VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PART', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3810591A,1972-07-13,Dispensing machine for coil stock,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3810594A,1971-09-04,Cartridge for motion picture film,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3810603A,1972-06-09,Bumper jack,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3810610A,1972-09-11,Bosh construction for metallurgical furnaces,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3810641A,1972-09-01,Collet chuck for router head and the like,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3810671A,1972-08-30,Jettison device for helicopter load carrying system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3810698A,1972-06-16,"Analyzer for simultaneously determining the rx, photochromic, and hardening characteristics of lenses","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,15
US3810747A,1971-09-17,Glass molding apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3810748A,1971-12-17,Glass processing lathe,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3810756A,1971-03-24,"Method of making valve seat rings from a mixture of c,pb and a pre-alloy of fe-co-ni-mo by powder metallurgy","['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,30
US3810803A,1971-11-05,"Continuous fiber reinforcement,cross-ply test specimen","['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3810814A,1972-12-18,Asymmetric polymer membranes of reduced elastic modulus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3810825A,1971-05-13,"Resin and process for curing by exposing to ionizing radiation a mixture of a vinyl ester resin,an alkenyl aromatic monomer and a 2-oxazoline or guanidine","['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,30
US3810856A,1970-11-05,Chloroprene polymer processing,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3810912A,1970-04-27,Alkylhydroxyphenylcarboalkoxy-substituted phthalimide,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3810930A,1971-10-29,Bis-(beta-amino acrylyl thiocarboxylate)of cyclic hydrocarbon alcohols,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3810932A,1968-03-18,Styryl dyestuffs,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3810976A,1970-05-20,Lung scanning 99m technetium macroaggregate and method of preparation,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,11
US3811006A,1972-10-30,Breather cap with valve depressor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3811024A,1973-05-03,"Momentary contact, non-bounce switch","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3811139A,1972-10-24,Stretcher,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3811148A,1972-10-13,Screw conveyor steamer for scallop processing,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3811225A,1972-11-01,Slidable door fastener for weatherproof housing,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3811244A,1971-12-22,Hose winding and packaging machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3811264A,1972-04-10,Yarn creeling and transferring process,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3811296A,1970-09-14,Circular knitting machine with jack removal slots,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3811441A,1972-02-10,Cartridge syringe,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3811490A,1971-03-16,Continuous casting of rimming steel,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3811531A,1971-12-06,Silencer,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3811579A,1972-09-25,Mechanized van loading and unloading apparatus and system,"['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3811610A,1971-08-02,Rod handling apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3811634A,1972-03-15,Cartridge stripping,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3811636A,1972-12-05,Yarn bobbin support device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3811648A,1973-07-09,Azimuth readout system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3811693A,1972-05-15,Drill chuck,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3811694A,1972-05-31,Collet chuck,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3811758A,1971-08-06,Cartridge-loaded motion picture projector,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3811774A,1972-04-20,Continuous wave radar for range and velocity measurement,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3811812A,1972-05-04,Mill for manufacture of plaster concrete articles,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3811821A,1971-12-03,Powder image fixing device for xerographic copying apparatus and method,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3811862A,1970-10-22,Glass heat treat machinery,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3811864A,1970-12-28,Diphenyl ether herbicidal compositions,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3811881A,1971-10-29,Photographic processes and products employing naphthol sulfonamidonaphthalides as optical filter agents,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3811917A,1970-10-05,Boron deposition on carbon monofilament,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3811969A,1971-03-08,Fuse powder composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3812020A,1969-08-11,Electrolyte and method for electroplating an indium-copper alloy and printed circuits so plated,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3812039A,1971-02-25,Electrolyte for electrolytic capacitor,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3812047A,1971-03-10,Dihalobutene diol containing compositions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3812056A,1972-07-05,Continuous encapsulation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3812081A,1973-05-03,Quaternary ammonium salt catalyst,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3812097A,1972-07-17,Yranuronosyl)oxy)olean-12-en-30-oic acid,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3812174A,1970-07-14,Substituted aryl carbamates,"['VERB', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3812203A,1969-09-24,Chloroprene rubber composition and method of producing the same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3812269A,1971-08-10,Propionic acid coated silica as a food preservative,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",1,1,9
US3812444A,1972-04-17,Hose connector having means for operating electrical contacts,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3812537A,1972-11-14,Tape cartridge player cartridge magazine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3812575A,1971-12-02,Electret microphone,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3812691A,1969-10-07,Jack and needle actuator for a circular knitting machine,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3812694A,1970-11-30,Bending machine for metal rods,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3812742A,1972-08-10,Jar opener,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3812748A,1972-10-17,Glass cutting device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3812800A,1973-07-31,Label attaching machine,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3812851A,1972-11-21,I. v. arm rest and support,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3812956A,1969-07-29,Screw conveyor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3812958A,1970-10-30,Carton for plurality of containers,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3812996A,1972-06-08,Bottle carrying case,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3813020A,1973-05-25,Yarn aspirator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3813061A,1973-04-02,Parachutist{40 s glider,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3813077A,1972-06-29,Hose clamp,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3813097A,1972-10-27,Batsman box for a baseball diamond,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3813129A,1972-07-11,Antiskid control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3813130A,1971-11-18,Antiskid control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3813433A,1971-03-11,"16-methyl and ethyl pge1 and 16,16-dimethyl and diethyl pge1","['NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['CARDINAL', 'PERSON']",1,1,14
US3813583A,1972-01-28,Yarn break detection system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3813608A,1973-03-06,Amplifier device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3813626A,1972-12-15,Fuse retainer and extractor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3813737A,1971-07-02,Clasp for bola tie with interchangeable mount,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3813751A,1972-11-22,Hydraulic chuck,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3813823A,1969-06-25,End mill grinder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3813827A,1973-05-25,Chuck assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3813857A,1972-10-12,Cotton harvester,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3813916A,1973-03-19,Meter proving system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3813986A,1972-03-03,Sleev-lok anchors,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3813996A,1971-04-15,Continuous filter rod making machines,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3814002A,1973-04-26,Powder spray booth,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3814077A,1972-02-17,Snorkel tube burner construction and method of making the same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3814083A,1972-05-24,Apparatus and method for processing korotkov sounds,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3814103A,1973-03-08,Binasal pharyngeal airway,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3814133A,1971-11-19,Solenoid operated compressed air valve,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3814135A,1972-03-02,Hose and tubing assembly closures,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3814138A,1972-10-18,Hose construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3814190A,1972-11-29,Dragline cleaner for open drainage ditches,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3814239A,1972-05-15,Tree root container,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3814299A,1972-06-14,Rod stock feed means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3814341A,1973-09-07,Yarn winding apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3814373A,1971-03-22,Core apparatus for molding nasal cannulae,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US3814376A,1972-08-09,Solenoid operated valve with magnetic latch,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3814400A,1971-12-22,Impeller replacing device for molten metal stirring equipment,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3814416A,1971-05-25,Playground climbing structures,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3814423A,1972-06-12,Racquet construction and method of making same,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3814448A,1972-10-16,Hydraulic chuck,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3814449A,1972-10-05,Hydraulic ring chuck,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3814465A,1972-12-22,Meter bar construction,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3814559A,1972-10-27,Spinneret with inert gas metering ring,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3814612A,1971-06-11,Glass useful for forming a reed switch sealing tube,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3814620A,1971-10-18,Method of applying fused silica coating to a substrate,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3814650A,1971-12-23,Extruder head for sealing containers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3814651A,1971-06-05,Labeler,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3814715A,1969-05-21,Glass fiber size containing polyolefin emulsion,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3814772A,1970-09-08,Ortho-amino benzoyl hydrazine derivatives and process for preparing the same,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3814842A,1973-04-09,Rgb amplifier,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3815041A,1972-06-14,Amplifier circuit having a multiplicity of discrete operative states,"['ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3815056A,1971-08-11,Continuous surface wave device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3815071A,1972-12-08,Fuse clip,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3815072A,1973-01-16,Fuse and holder with rejection feature,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3815197A,1972-11-08,Glass lehr roll and method of manufacture,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3815257A,1973-04-04,Continuous laundry dryer,"['ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3815289A,1972-08-14,Gem grinder having a pivotable rack and gear assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3815346A,1973-06-01,Harvester pickup,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3815541A,1972-01-19,Houseboat powered by smaller boat,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3815549A,1973-04-19,Split level bird cage,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3815649A,1970-08-06,Cartridge pack for trash compaction machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3815672A,1972-11-17,Split fin heat exchange unit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3815683A,1972-11-15,Ripper assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3815722A,1971-03-15,Solenoid controlled paper handling mechanism,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3815735A,1972-06-28,Carton,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3815763A,1972-02-24,Grinder feeding system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3815784A,1972-08-14,Dispensing nozzle arrangement providing electrical lockout,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3815789A,1971-02-05,Continuous machines for the instantaneous production of whipped cream,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3815869A,1972-02-24,Butterfly disc valves,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3815891A,1972-05-30,Jig for positioning the studs for the quarl tiles,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3815898A,1972-05-24,Label handling mechanism,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3815909A,1967-01-30,Split detection system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3815970A,1973-02-26,Stereo attachment accessory for cameras,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3816015A,1971-01-15,Quick-change chuck,"['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3816088A,1970-10-22,Glass heat treat machinery,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3816089A,1970-10-01,Glass sheet press shaping apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3816093A,1970-05-28,Halogenating method of reducing iron and titanium content of alumina-silica ore,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3816154A,1973-05-18,Silica gel flatting agent,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3816161A,1970-10-19,Glass-ceramic decoration,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3816220A,1972-05-15,Carton sealer,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3816235A,1972-08-18,Glass fiber size composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3816251A,1971-05-07,"Process for producing adenosine-3,5 -cyclic monophosphoric acid by fermentation","['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3816331A,1972-07-05,Continuous encapsulation and device therefor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3816364A,1968-11-29,Epoxy base ink composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3816376A,1971-03-02,Continuous manufacture of amino resin solutions,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3816388A,1968-11-05,Azo compounds from alkyl alpha-anilino toluates,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3816392A,1968-11-01,Azo compounds containing a triazolylthio group,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3816466A,1971-12-22,Flavanoid ring systems,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3816585A,1969-07-28,Continuous motion container molding method,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3816654A,1972-05-02,Solid state camera tube embodying a fixed iris,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3816767A,1973-03-23,Schmitt trigger circuit,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3816868A,1971-12-21,Glass cleaning apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3816895A,1973-03-14,Chuck assembly for fasteners,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3816937A,1972-06-22,Slope control console,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3816989A,1973-08-08,Yarn driven friction falsetwister,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3816995A,1972-06-29,End mill grinder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3817065A,1973-03-20,Loc n{40 bolt,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3817069A,1972-05-25,Continuous hydrostatic extrusion die assembly and method for using it in forming extruded parts,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3817101A,1971-07-23,Flow meter,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3817126A,1972-07-17,Decapper,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3817133A,1972-02-05,Glass shear,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3817148A,1970-05-02,Cartridge feeding mechanism for firearms,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3817152A,1971-03-18,Hydraulic jack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3817239A,1972-05-12,Urine monitor,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3817288A,1970-01-26,Hose pipes,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3817345A,1971-07-30,Continuous bit positioning system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3817357A,1971-10-12,Torque converter with throttle controlled fluid clutch,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3817465A,1972-06-15,Winder traverse for filamentary material,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3817493A,1972-07-21,Hydraulic jack for trailers,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3817648A,1971-09-03,Drill shank and chuck assembly for a drill press,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,10
US3817682A,1971-10-06,Carton forming apparatus with simultaneously ignited heaters,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3817775A,1972-12-04,Glass fiber reinforced elastomers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3817878A,1969-12-11,Polyol polymethacrylate crosslinked strong base anion exchange resins,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3817906A,1971-02-08,Epoxy resin composition,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3817968A,1972-11-28,Method of producing equibinary (cis 1.4-1.2) polybutadiene,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NUM', 'SYM', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,12
US3818007A,1970-03-18,Hydroxyalkyl esters of quinoxaline-di-n-oxide-2-carboxylic acid,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'SPACE', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3818035A,1971-01-27,2{8 (2-ALKYLBENZO{8 b{9 {11 FURAN-3 yl)METHYL{9 -{66 {11 IMIDAZOLINE,"['NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'CARDINAL', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,15
US3818125A,1971-10-26,Stereo television microscope,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3818348A,1971-05-17,Unique word detection in digital burst communication systems,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3818372A,1972-11-30,Multifrequency laser oscillator for holographic contouring,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3818408A,1972-09-11,"Fuse, more especially a weak-current fuse for motor vehicles or the like","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADV', 'ADV', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,16
US3818488A,1973-01-18,Shipboard yardarm half-wave antenna,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,7
US3818563A,1971-06-15,Work-holding chuck and cartridge-case trimmer employing same,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3818746A,1971-07-06,Rod end cold forming process,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3819044A,1971-10-29,Container cooperable with a like container in an empty nesting relation and a plurality of article containing stacking relations,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,20
US3819096A,1971-11-30,Glass breaking,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3819207A,1973-02-05,Meter riser assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3819236A,1971-11-04,Antiskid control arrangement,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3819253A,1972-05-15,Telephoto lens system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3819560A,1972-01-06,Vinyl halide polymer/epoxide resin powder coating compositions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SYM', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3819581A,1973-04-02,Epoxy resin compositions containing aromatic disulfonamide salts,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3819603A,1970-06-30,Sulfaguanidines,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3819769A,1968-01-03,Split fibers from blends of polypropylene and polyethylene,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3819843A,1972-05-11,Keyboard electronic music instrument with step-wise variable volume control responsive to key-touch,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,17
US3819923A,1973-02-06,Seal off around ge3952 lamp,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3819960A,1972-05-01,Controller circuit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3820158A,1972-05-22,Cartridge loading and positioning mechanism for tape playing device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3820255A,1973-03-08,Rigid boot construction with self cleaning sole,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3820266A,1972-02-07,Cartridge case ejector for bolt gun,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3820302A,1973-04-05,Carton casing apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3820305A,1972-10-03,Cap supply mechanism for a rotating bottle closing device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3820417A,1972-08-10,Controls for sequentially engaging transmission torque convertor lockup and master clutches,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3820430A,1972-05-26,Yarn transporting apparatus,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3820484A,1972-07-26,Cap making apparatus and method,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3820518A,1972-08-28,Automatic manifold vacuum spoiler,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",0,1,5
US3820559A,1973-06-22,Hose reel,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3820562A,1973-01-22,Continuous liquid chemical injector,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3820706A,1973-01-26,Fiberboard container,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3820735A,1971-10-19,Hank carriers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3820842A,1972-11-17,Slip tongue with inflator band,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3820957A,1972-03-22,Continuous polymerization reactor,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3820966A,1970-05-05,Diamond grinding layer for honing segments,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3821171A,1971-07-01,"Continuous,solid-phase polymerization of polyamide granules","['ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3821277A,1964-10-30,"Ypsilon-methoxy-ypsilon-carbanilino-alpha,omega-dicyanopentane","['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3821330A,1969-12-22,Continuous polymerization of acrylics,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3821432A,1971-07-26,Bland amino acid compositions,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3821523A,1973-05-07,Aircraft locating system using agile tacan vortac dme,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['NORP', 'PERSON']",1,1,9
US3821646A,1969-04-02,Scatter communication system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3821772A,1971-10-22,Schottky diode with minimal metal guard ring overlap,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3821809A,1973-06-07,Cartridge opener device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3821830A,1972-08-03,Cleaner for carpets and the like,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3821910A,1972-08-08,Glass cutting mechanism,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3822112A,1969-06-26,"Dyeing live human hair with an aqueous solution of a direct dye,2-phenoxy-ethanol and ethyl glycol acetate","['NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,21
US3822148A,1970-07-15,Lithium-metal molybdate organic electrolyte cell,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3822234A,1973-10-19,Vinyl chloride polymers containing alkali metal zinc ferrocyanides,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3822246A,1972-05-15,Azo compounds containing an imidoalkanoylamino group,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3822262A,1969-02-20,Phenyl acetylimino-imidazolines and-hexahydropyrimidines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3822327A,1970-03-27,Neutralized polycondensed vinylphosphonates,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3822331A,1971-12-10,Continuous process for making low density thermoplastic foam,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3822361A,1972-03-06,Continuous preparation of cheese,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3822538A,1973-10-31,Yarn splicing apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3822550A,1971-03-18,Multicylinder thermodynamic reciprocating machine in which the fuel supply to burner devices is controlled by means of temperature-sensitive elements,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,22
US3822675A,1972-03-28,Boiler for heating non-boiling heat transfer liquids,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3822828A,1973-03-13,Refiner network controller,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3822973A,1971-10-01,Cartridge oil seal for rotating combustion engines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3823032A,1972-07-27,Glass bottles coated with multiprotective film layers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3823050A,1971-10-04,Label applicator head,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3823107A,1971-03-11,"Epoxy resin curing agent compositions,their preparation and use","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3823147A,1968-05-24,Thiophenyl-substituted quinophthalone dispersion dyestuffs,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3823150A,1971-02-08,"2-(furfuryl-methyl)-6,7-benzomorphans and acid addition salts thereof","['NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3823169A,1970-04-14,Quaternary anthraquinone dyestuffs,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3823177A,1971-06-25,Insecticidal esters of spiro carboxylic acids,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3823230A,1970-10-29,Aldehyde condensation products of fluoroaliphatic phenols in skin protective compositions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3823273A,1971-12-17,Subscriber's telephone circuit,"['PROPN', 'PART', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3823430A,1973-02-07,Tent stake jack,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,4
US3823435A,1973-04-16,Sweeper assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3823539A,1973-01-02,Yarn spinning apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3823612A,1971-08-20,Trip mechanisms,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3823615A,1973-04-19,Sampler for bulk grapes,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3823674A,1971-12-20,Bin type freight car,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3823697A,1971-11-18,Multicylinder motor or engine with double-acting pistons,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3823749A,1972-04-12,Bending machine for wire or strip,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3823921A,1972-11-14,Continuous processor for treating material,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3823958A,1973-05-10,House trailer stabilizer and jack system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,7
US3824057A,1972-09-20,Continuous molding conveyor with side clamping and release,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3824107A,1972-01-28,Mortar compositions containing mixtures of hydroxyalkyl celluloses,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3824122A,1971-07-02,Continuous diffusion coating,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3824133A,1971-12-02,Fabrication of electrically insulating regions in optical devices by proton bombardment,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3824214A,1973-03-20,Halovinylidene arylene polymers and process for making the same,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3824222A,1970-11-05,Flameproof modacrylic fibers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3824346A,1971-04-21,Fm stereo demodulator,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3824599A,1972-12-13,Tv/fm/am antenna coupler,"['PROPN', 'SYM', 'PROPN', 'SYM', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,8
US3824603A,1972-12-18,Solenoid actuated recording apparatus,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3824668A,1973-01-26,Continuous stroke tube insertion and expanding device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3824903A,1971-11-26,Vacuum control drive,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3824912A,1972-12-29,Powder spray booth,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3824999A,1972-09-18,Tracheotomy mask,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3825002A,1972-02-07,Cartridge syringe and crimped needle assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3825031A,1972-08-28,Line vacuum controlled manifold vacuum spoiler,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3825061A,1971-05-13,Leak protected heat exchanger,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3825083A,1972-02-02,Drill bit and stabilizer combination,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3825167A,1972-12-26,Expanding mandrel or chuck,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3825196A,1972-01-15,Hank reeling machine,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3825208A,1972-12-27,Cartridge and storage apparatus,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3825263A,1972-10-19,Rod and resiliently projected ring,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3825379A,1972-04-10,Melt-blowing die using capillary tubes,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3825380A,1972-07-07,Melt-blowing die for producing nonwoven mats,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3825423A,1969-12-24,Image transfer process and also known as d/2888,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3825478A,1972-10-30,Electrolyte and method for electrodepositing microporous chromium-nickel composite coatings,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3825516A,1971-12-14,"Glass fiber-reinforced,terephthalic acid-containing polyamide molding compounds","['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3825527A,1970-12-04,Azo dye of a 3-aminophthalimide and containing carbamoyl moieties,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NUM', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,12
US3825847A,1970-12-07,Amplifier system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3825853A,1971-12-06,Amplifier tube for power amplification,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3825854A,1970-12-10,Amplifier with substantially zero distortion products,"['ADV', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,7
US3825870A,1970-11-11,Fuse element and a high voltage current-limiting fuse,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3825949A,1971-11-17,Cartridge changer with cartridge sensing means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3825957A,1972-08-08,Pivoting disc heart valve with rod guide,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3825981A,1972-11-13,Cartridge-type cutoff and grooving tool,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3826074A,1972-03-01,Glass fiber reinforced elastomers,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3826110A,1972-04-03,Yarn feeding and control means for circular knitting machine,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3826210A,1973-05-21,Torpedo antiself homing(ash)system,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3826248A,1971-09-21,Laryngoscope,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3826275A,1972-09-18,Hose reel construction,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3826298A,1969-11-25,Polyvinyl alcohol cord tires,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3826445A,1971-12-23,Yarn tube,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3826540A,1973-03-21,Powder hopper for electrostatic powder spraying apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3826592A,1971-06-02,Split locking piece for circumferential dovetail on turbine wheel,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3826597A,1972-10-19,Compressor with cartridge assembly,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3826611A,1969-10-10,Continuous treatment of a polyacrylonitrile at elevated temperatures on a porous roll,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3826635A,1973-01-05,Glass melting,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3826650A,1968-08-20,Epoxy photopolymer duplicating stencil,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3826689A,1971-03-09,Austenite type heat-resisting steel having high strength at an elevated temperature and the process for producing same,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,20
US3826811A,1971-07-12,Sulphur removal from natural gas,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3826888A,1973-03-05,Deep narrow gap welding torch,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3827011A,1973-03-08,Fuse assembly for oil-filled transformers,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3827045A,1972-12-18,Angle digital converter system,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3827085A,1972-04-06,Zipper stringer for fly systems and system employing same,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3827230A,1970-04-13,Glass fiber size,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3827261A,1972-05-08,Knit yarn package,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3827423A,1972-07-05,Unitary cellular-structured cooking fire apparatus,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3827504A,1973-03-21,Rod weeder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3827547A,1971-04-16,Glass sheet conveying apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3827597A,1973-03-05,Blade dispenser,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3827610A,1972-08-09,Volumetric filling device,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3827615A,1972-07-29,Knitting machine selector jack butt removal apparatus,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3827654A,1971-12-16,Yarn caddy,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3827759A,1972-01-22,Antiskid brake system with power assistance,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3827785A,1971-12-25,Glass lens having reduced chromatic aberration and refractive index gradient,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3827872A,1972-08-18,Glass tempering method,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3827951A,1969-12-10,Continuous forming of anodes for capacitors,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3828020A,1971-08-27,Alkoxyalkylamino salts of disazo acid dyes,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3828113A,1973-07-06,Unitary electrical receptacles,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3828252A,1971-11-29,Meter with audible read-out,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3828345A,1973-01-04,Amplifier buffered resistance network digital to analog and analog to digital converter system,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'PART', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3828386A,1971-09-07,Rug care implement,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3828487A,1972-12-01,Grinder attachment for a lathe,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3828494A,1973-06-13,Roof jack,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3828585A,1972-11-13,Denim sock and method of knitting same,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3828643A,1973-02-20,Scanner for electronic musical instrument,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3828735A,1973-01-15,Boiler tube shielding wall,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3828826A,1971-06-19,Jacquard mechanism,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3828990A,1972-12-27,Holster for pistols,"['ADJ', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3829019A,1972-02-02,Spinner assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3829078A,1973-08-10,Manually operated spring loaded jack lock assembly,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'DATE', 'PERSON']",1,1,8
US3829091A,1973-06-18,Kick putt device,"['VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3829304A,1971-02-02,Glass drawing conditioning means,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3829330A,1969-08-27,High rate li/moo3 organic electrolyte cell,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SYM', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3829364A,1970-09-14,Continuous anodic oxidation method for aluminum and alloys thereof,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3829396A,1966-09-08,Vinyl chloride resins stabilized with metal compound-epoxy compound-phosphite combinations,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3829402A,1972-01-05,Process for the preparation of compositions comprising polyvinyl alcohol and a finely dispersed solid,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3829445A,1972-12-11,"3-(3'-lower carboalkoxy-4'-hydroxy-1'-naphthyl)-3-(3""-carboxy-4""-hydroxy-1""-naphthyl)naphthalide","['X', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3829470A,1972-01-13,Alkylphenol disulfonation process,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3829501A,1968-10-29,"Polyetherpolythiols,method of preparation and mixtures of polythioetherpolythiols with epoxide resins","['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3829508A,1969-07-14,Halogenoalkyl-polyglycol ethers and process for preparing them,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PRON', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3829543A,1972-07-14,Melt spinning of polymers,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3829576A,1971-08-12,Method of treating neisseria gonorrhoeae with dihydroampicillin,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3829593A,1970-02-24,Continuous preparation of pastry,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3829615A,1972-10-04,Quaternary stereophonic sound reproduction apparatus,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3829641A,1970-03-19,Puffer-type electric switch,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3829642A,1973-02-08,"Tee connection for high voltage,high pressure oil,pipe type cables","['DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,14
US3829669A,1972-05-19,D.c.analog calculator for rapidly generating electric power system loadflow solutions,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3829695A,1971-08-26,Rod guide assembly for continuous rod making machines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3829735A,1972-01-28,Airfield lighting circuit arrangements,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3829775A,1972-01-28,Meter with electrically selectable scales,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3829779A,1972-02-04,Multilevel code transmission system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3829808A,1973-02-14,Fuse housing construction utilizing extruded terminals and process for making same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3829830A,1972-03-16,Circuit for switching d. c. power,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3829862A,1973-04-20,Ridge scan antenna,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3829880A,1973-01-05,Schottky barrier plasma thyristor circuit,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3829896A,1972-11-08,Bias means for batch fabricated magnetic head and method of manufacture thereof,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,13
US3829897A,1973-05-04,Cartridge clamp,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3830000A,1973-05-16,Cartridge expelling mechanism for firearms,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3830051A,1973-04-02,Yarn guiding flyer mechanism for a textile yarn processing machine,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3830071A,1972-10-13,Jack-up drilling platform,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3830092A,1972-08-10,Meter proving apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3830100A,1973-02-22,Strain gauge transducer transient voltage protection,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3830157A,1972-10-31,Cartridge case,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3830163A,1972-11-29,Monorail vehicle switching arrangement,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3830267A,1972-05-25,Filler nozzle vapor seal and collector,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3830386A,1972-02-22,Bin dumper,"['NOUN', 'X', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3830428A,1972-02-23,Plasma torches,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3830452A,1973-06-22,Monorail traverse system,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3830478A,1973-01-10,Continuous metal wire annealing furnace,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3830496A,1971-10-14,Bat,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3830545A,1973-08-01,Shield tunneling machine with orbiting cutterhead,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3830584A,1972-12-22,Turret system for machine tool,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3830617A,1971-09-14,Melt spinning apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3830654A,1970-01-30,OPTICAL DEVICES UTILIZING SINGLE CRYSTAL GaP OR GaAs FILMS EPITAXIALLY GROWN ON CaF{11 {11 SUBSTRATES AND METHOD OF FABRICATING SAME,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,22
US3830731A,1972-03-20,Vacuum residuum and vacuum gas oil desulfurization,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3830761A,1971-10-26,Vinyl chloride-ethylene-vinyl acetate resin binders,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3830839A,1968-03-07,Imidoyl ureas,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3830848A,1970-10-01,Diphenyl derivatives,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3830876A,1970-10-26,Dicyclopentadienyl iron compositions and methods for curing polyester resins,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3830882A,1972-11-16,Semicarbazono phosphorus compounds,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3830885A,1968-09-27,"Dialkyl n,n-dialkoxymethylcarbamylphosphonates","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3830901A,1968-09-09,Continuous process for extruding cellular thermoplastics,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3830935A,1972-07-24,Method for the control of the douglas fir beetle,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3831099A,1972-01-27,Controller having gain selectable independently of controller output,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADV', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3831123A,1973-10-31,Yoke removal from a bonded yoke-cathode ray tube assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3831369A,1972-08-11,Yarn structure and method of making same,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3831401A,1973-08-30,Slip clutch for outboard motor,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3831444A,1972-01-26,Yarn quality assessment method and apparatus therefor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3831466A,1972-02-08,Glass blade and glass blade blank,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3831516A,1971-10-26,Continuous press,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3831585A,1972-07-19,Retrograde renal biopsy device,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3831729A,1971-11-30,Solenoid having increased throw capability,"['PROPN', 'AUX', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3831738A,1973-08-01,Bottle orientation apparatus,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3831784A,1972-05-15,Carton magazine and means for loading the same,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3831818A,1972-05-15,Fertilizer distributor,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3831833A,1972-09-25,Dispensing carton,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3831874A,1971-09-22,Yarn drive roller,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3831876A,1972-12-11,Continuous unwinding apparatus for web material,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3831891A,1972-03-07,Rod supports,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3831892A,1973-09-04,Jack lock,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3831901A,1972-10-19,Vehicle jack with locking means,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3831953A,1970-01-05,Solenoid operated valve assembly,"['ADJ', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3832009A,1971-06-07,Antiskid control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3832012A,1972-01-21,Antiskid braking circuit,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3832025A,1972-11-20,Cartridge tape player door mounting assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3832030A,1973-05-23,Delay equalizers for multimode optical fibers,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3832148A,1971-12-08,Bimetallic material for electronic tube applications,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3832208A,1972-03-09,Nacreous pigments treated with methacrylatochromic chloride for improved humidity resistance,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3832286A,1971-02-03,Sisomicin and methods for its production,"['PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3832332A,1971-10-22,Polyamide polymer of diamino methyl adamantane and dicarboxylic acid,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON']",1,1,10
US3832343A,1971-09-22,Process for obtaining an extract of arnica montana,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3832372A,1972-10-12,Continuous process for preparing aromatic isocyanates,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3832409A,1970-10-29,Aldehyde condensation products of fluoroaliphatic phenols,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3832449A,1971-03-18,Crystalline zeolite zsm{14 12,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'NUM', 'SPACE']","['ORG', 'PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,5
US3832583A,1973-03-08,Squirrel cage motor with improved rotor bar securing arrangement,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3832637A,1973-06-22,Fsk modem,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3832658A,1973-07-23,Solenoid actuated switch,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3832717A,1972-03-03,Dish reflector for a high gain antenna,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3832806A,1971-12-01,Multiedge lapping,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3832879A,1972-03-15,Bending machines,"['VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3832912A,1973-02-22,Handlebar safety shield,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3833038A,1973-05-07,Drapery pin inserter,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'NORP']",1,1,4
US3833077A,1971-02-12,Diamond drills,"['NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,3
US3833105A,1970-05-15,Printer head assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3833231A,1972-02-01,Chuck,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3833232A,1970-06-11,Chuck jaw insert assembly,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3833351A,1973-02-15,Continuous preparation of pure metals by hydrogen reduction,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3833370A,1973-01-05,Color diffusion transfer with development controlling polymeric salt,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3833395A,1972-09-11,Continuous form computer print-out document protection system,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3833459A,1970-02-20,Felt backing for vinyl floor covering having a binder comprised of synthetic rubber latex and a reactive thermoset resin,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,20
US3833523A,1970-02-13,Rigid cellular materials having a good mechanical strength at low temperatures,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3833597A,1971-06-09,Quaternary ammonium compounds,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3833640A,1968-07-29,"Prostaglandin e1,f1,and a1 analogs","['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3833642A,1969-04-30,Alkenyloxy benzoic acid and esters thereof,"['PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADV', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3833693A,1970-05-26,Dispensing of a material into a mould,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3833727A,1972-03-06,Hydralazine and beta-adrenergic blocking agent compositions for treating hypertension,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,12
US3833738A,1971-01-25,Alfalfa extract process,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3833809A,1973-05-09,Neutron logging of formation porosity and chlorinity,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3833860A,1972-04-20,Amplifier system having pseudo summing junction,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3833875A,1972-12-07,Fuse receptacle,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3833919A,1972-10-12,Multilevel conductor structure and method,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3834020A,1971-11-19,Shears,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3834157A,1973-02-05,Spinner de-icing for gas turbine engines,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,9
US3834186A,1973-11-09,Knit contour unit for a knitting machine,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3834188A,1971-06-08,Spring loaded pattern drum for ease of pattern jack insertion,"['NOUN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3834266A,1973-11-23,Cartridge string guitar assembly,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3834267A,1973-09-27,Capo for five string banjo,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",1,1,6
US3834276A,1970-09-08,Rams,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3834311A,1971-06-01,Cartridge,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3834314A,1972-12-29,Puller sabot ammunition with slip seal,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3834347A,1971-06-16,Tablet coating apparatus,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3834433A,1971-11-22,Cartridge-actuated device for inflating tires and the like,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3834445A,1971-09-20,Continuous casting mold having a breakout sensing and control device,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,11
US3834446A,1972-04-10,Mould for electroslag remelting of metals,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3834468A,1971-05-07,Hammer-drill,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3834669A,1973-02-12,Knockdown jack assembly,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3834705A,1973-09-26,Footsie bird game device,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3834720A,1973-02-07,Self-centering jaw chuck,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3834725A,1972-03-18,Trolley adapted to hold or to exhibit things or articles of different kinds,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'PART', 'VERB', 'CCONJ', 'PART', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,14
US3834818A,1972-03-29,Continuous measurement of the fineness of a pulverulent material,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,10
US3834831A,1973-01-23,Blade shank cooling arrangement,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3834833A,1972-02-18,Blade construction for axial-flow turbo-machines and method of protecting turbo-machine blades against stress corrosion cracking,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,22
US3834911A,1972-05-31,Glass composition and method of making,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3834980A,1969-06-17,Glass-filled thermoplastic pellets suitable for blending with thermoplastic,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3835075A,1971-06-29,Butadiene resins and process for preparation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3835101A,1972-04-13,"Melt blends of carboxylic acid terminated,low molecular weight polyamide and polyvalent metal compounds","['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,16
US3835110A,1972-02-08,Vasopressin peptides having psychopharmacological activity,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3835116A,1973-06-25,Vinyl halide plastisol compositions containing a carboxylic polymer,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3835230A,1972-05-02,D.c. arc furnace for steelmaking,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,7
US3835406A,1972-10-02,Neutralized amplifier circuit,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3835409A,1973-09-25,Amplifier distortion circuit for electric guitars,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3835432A,1973-02-12,Fuse holder,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3835459A,1972-03-06,BIREFRINGENCE READ Bi{11 Ti{11 O{11 {11 DISPLAY AND MEMORY DEVICE,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'DATE']",1,1,12
US3835462A,1972-06-07,Fishing rod beeper,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3835681A,1973-03-16,Continuous rolling mill,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3835695A,1972-01-20,Meter proving apparatus and method,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3835718A,1972-07-24,Impeller mechanism,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,3
US3835842A,1972-07-03,Endoscope with continuous irrigation,"['VERB', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3835879A,1973-04-09,Hose rack assembly,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3835917A,1972-11-27,Continuous casting of non-ferrous metals,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3835975A,1971-09-10,Printer head assembly,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3835989A,1972-04-27,Carton with two covers,"['NOUN', 'ADP', 'NUM', 'VERB', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL']",0,1,5
US3836007A,1972-05-16,Eyeglass display holder,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3836012A,1973-07-09,Removable outrigger assembly with rotatable jack,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3836020A,1972-11-11,Container/cargo handling plant,"['PROPN', 'SYM', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3836045A,1972-11-14,Dispensing container of folded disposable towels,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3836049A,1973-07-12,Clasp,"['NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,2
US3836086A,1972-07-19,Yarn winding apparatus and method,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3836097A,1972-12-04,Silencer,"['PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,2
US3836197A,1972-11-24,Recliner with vertically movable headrest,"['PROPN', 'ADP', 'ADV', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,6
US3836208A,1971-11-12,Antiskid control system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,4
US3836215A,1973-02-15,Shaft vibration dampening means and method,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'VERB', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3836224A,1972-11-03,Holdgram memory readout system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3836234A,1972-05-17,Fully closing iris diaphragm,"['ADV', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
US3836255A,1972-04-06,Spectrometric substance analyzer employing temperature modulation,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,7
US3836324A,1973-08-06,Continuous rotary heat treating furnace,"['ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3836375A,1972-04-06,TiO{11 {13 P{11 O{11 {13 Na{11 O{13 WO{11 {11 OPTICAL GLASSES AND METHOD,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'NUM', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']","['PERSON', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG', 'CARDINAL', 'ORG']",1,1,17
US3836389A,1966-06-09,Glass coated electrical steel sheet and articles prepared therefrom,"['PROPN', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'ADP', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3836432A,1969-09-25,Continuous process for the hydrolysis of raffinose,"['ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,8
US3836486A,1971-01-13,Vinyl chloride polymer recovery process,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,6
US3836490A,1970-10-08,Flameproof polycarbonates containing an alkali metal salt soluble in the polycarbonate melt,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'ADJ', 'ADP', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,13
US3836510A,1972-12-27,Vinyl halide terpolymer and bulk process for preparation,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,9
US3836535A,1970-08-27,N-methyl-n'-(2-amino ethyl sulfonyl)-piperazine,"['NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'PUNCT', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,10
US3836594A,1969-11-27,Hydrocarbon conversion process and silica and/or alumina-containing catalyst therefor,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'VERB', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3836642A,1966-02-22,Granaticin b and method of preparing same,"['PROPN', 'PROPN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'VERB', 'ADJ', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,8
US3836785A,1970-07-15,Neutron generator having a target on which a beam of hydrogen ions is incident,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'PRON', 'DET', 'NOUN', 'ADP', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'AUX', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,15
US3836868A,1973-06-27,"LAER GLASS HOST COMPOSITIONS COMPRISING TeO{11 , B{11 0{11 ZnO","['VERB', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,11
US3836871A,1973-06-27,"LASER GLASS HOST COMPOSITIONS COMPRISING TeO{11 , Li{11 O AND ZnO","['NOUN', 'PROPN', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'PROPN', 'INTJ', 'CCONJ', 'PROPN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3836872A,1973-09-21,Avalanche diode oscillator,"['NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,4
US3836883A,1971-12-08,Fuse and resistor device,"['NOUN', 'CCONJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],0,1,5
US3836892A,1972-06-29,D.c. stable electronic storage utilizing a.c. stable storage cell,"['PROPN', 'PUNCT', 'ADJ', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'VERB', 'PROPN', 'PROPN', 'ADJ', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,12
US3836951A,1960-05-05,Heterodyne autocorrelation guidance system,"['PROPN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'NOUN', 'SPACE']",['PERSON'],1,1,5
